<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_supernatural_artifacts">
        <item>A small round (5" diameter, 1/2" thick) obsidian mirror framed in silver. The frame is formed as a stylized snake biting its own tail. [Looking into the mirror while letting moonlight fall on it will, after a brief disconcerting moment when the mirror\'s surface seem to give off smoke, reveal a brief glimpse of the immediate (24 hour) future. The vision usually focus on life-threatening (to the viewer) events, but a strong-willed viewer may roll against his or her SAN to force a vision of a specific time and place (within 24 hours). Doing this costs 1d6 SAN.]</item>
        <item>A duffel-bag with internal dimensions much larger than its external dimensions.</item>
        <item>A heavy metal box, approximately 1\' long, high and deep. The box is locked with a rusted padlock, no key can be found. Anyone managing to open the box will find that it is not possible to see the inside as it seems filled with an inky darkness. Probing the darkness will reveal that no sides or bottom can be found. There is a 15% chance that any hands (or similar appendages) inserted into the box will be savaged for 3d6 HP as "something" takes notice of the tasty morsel. Anything dropped into the box will disappear, but will re-appear close (within 100 feet, but possibly inside a wall or the ground) to the box present location either 1d100 years before the present time, or 1d100 years after. Breaking the box cause a violent explosion of strange black flames dealing 4D10 damage to everything within 100 feet.</item>
        <item>Near the front of the storage unit is a box that used to contain printer paper. Inside protected by old newspaper is a glass sculpture of an octopus crawling along the sea floor. The octopus is made of green glass and the sea floor is made up of pieces of marble. Studying the sculpture will reveal it is actually a lamp, the parts roughly matching what would be available in the 20s. I\'d take some work but a handyman or electrician could get it working again. It doesn\'t light up a room and appears to just be a decorative piece. However, those who sleep in the same room with it on, have a higher chance to receive dreams from Cthulhu. This is the original function the item served. Searching for the history of this lamp will return nothing, it was hand made by some unknown artist.</item>
        <item>A black blindfold which, if worn by the target of a firing squad or similar execution, will allow the wearer to miraculously escape harm. However, the shooters will all believe the target is dead, to the point of untying and hauling off a hallucinated corpse while completely ignoring the still-living victim walking away unscathed.\n1/1d6 SAN loss to actually survive a firing squad this way, otherwise no loss. Note that while this artifact may or may not work in battle, it is still a blindfold, and therefore a rather serious tactical hindrance.</item>
        <item>A large tooth (approx, 3 inches long) on a leather cord. Natural history or similar rolls are uncertain of its origin but reveal to have characteristics of both Orca and shark teeth. A Mythos roll reveals it to be from a Deep One, a BIG one.</item>
        <item>An 8 1/2" soapstone carving of a tentacle-faced man-thing. Those versant in the Mythos recognise it as an impression of Cthulhu himself. Hanging around the statue for too long has been known to cause nosebleeds, headaches, tinnitus and, in some cases, cerebral edema.</item>
        <item>A skittering pile of spiders, cockroaches and ants. Brushing them aside reveals the remains of a plastic evidence bag and a sealed test tube containing a milky white liquid. [The test tube contains Mother\'s Milk, a substance associated with Shub-Niggurath. It is highly mutagenic, and will greatly increase healing, growth and fertility in any living creature it comes into contact with, plus some slight side-effects like insanity and deformity ...]</item>
        <item>A sealed jar full of a yellow milk like substance. It has a bio-hazard sign on it. This is the Milk of Shub-Niggurath. Drinking or even touching it should have interesting and perverse effects.</item>
        <item>A large (1\'x1\'x3") Star-Stone of M\'nar in a velvet lined, wooden presentation box. Whether it works as advertised is up to the Keeper.</item>
        <item>A long-distance/international telephone card for an Indian telephone company. If its prefix code is entered, no matter the number dialed, all calls are immediately picked up - free of charge - at the other end.</item>
        <item>A pair of dog-tags threaded to a silk cord. The particulars imprinted on the metal are unreadable, but anyone holding them feels a sense of reassurance while doing so. While asleep there is a 75% chance of the wearer waking up 30 seconds before anything life-threatening happens to them (be it a fire, an assassin, alien abduction etc.).</item>
        <item>A small statue representing an unknown deity - looks like Shiva but something is off (not the right number of arms, head slightly larger, etc.).\nOn the statue, a post-it reads: \'DO NOT FUCKING TOUCH\'. The post-it looks like it will come off at the smallest gust of wind. The effects of touching the statue are left to one\'s appreciation.</item>
        <item>A computer. Anyone who touches the screen is sucked inside. 1d10 SAN loss for anyone who witnesses this.</item>
        <item>A box of "Lucky Charms" breakfast cereal, but with Stephen Alzis\'s maniacally grinning face on the box where Lucky the Leprechaun\'s should be. Close examination of the box shows that it was, in fact, printed this way. The contents of the box are magically delicious.</item>
        <item>A pair of red and black kidney-shaped divining blocks linked with a piece of red twine. Used by Peranakan (mixed-race Singapore Chinese-Malaysian) diviners, these blocks are known as \'pak puay\' and the way they fall signifies a "yes" or "no" answer to a question.\nEach time this set are actually used someone close to the diviner will die.</item>
        <item>A Hittite-era copper bowl looted from Mosul Museum, Iraq, during the 2003 invasion. It\'s been recently defaced with sigils allowing it to be used for the spell Send Dreams.</item>
        <item>An iron collar with a heavy lock on one side, sized to fit a human male of average build, and a key to same. If placed on a subject and the lock is closed, the subject enters a trance state where they are highly suggestible and will follow all non-suicidal orders without question, no matter who gives them. The collar can only be opened by the included key or by cutting it off.</item>
        <item>A scuffed tuning fork. When struck and placed on an object you can hear voices whispering. The voices gives you information about the object but its not always useful.</item>
        <item>A stone sarcophagus. Inside is an atrophied human cadaver, its skin flaking, rippling with green fungus, and suffering from a huge hole in its chest.</item>
        <item>3 vials containing a clear fluid. The fluid is an experimental muscle relaxant developed by Majestic-12. Once injected, it allows the user to perform incredible feats that only a profesional gymnast or contortionist might be able to manage. The user can easily climb and jump onto roofs, stretch their limbs to a limited degree or fit into small places (+35 to Jump, Climb and Dodge). The drawback is that it is developed from Mi-Go technology, and is created from microscopis bacteria. For every incredible feat, the agent must make a Luck roll. If he succeeds he manages the feat unharmed, but if the roll fails, he suceeds in doing in his aims, but the fluid consumes 1 point of Strength.</item>
        <item>An old AN/PRC-77 combat-net radio transceiver as used by US troops during the Vietnam War. On the side of someone has painted the words: "Gung Ho!" in white paint. It seems functionable, but the batteries are long dead. Anyone replacing the batteries will have a hard time receiving a stable signal. No matter how much adjustments are made the signal seems to drift into white noise after a short while. [Someone listening to the noise for more than 5 minutes and failing a SAN roll will start discerning faint transmissions in it. It is hard to hear exactly what is said but listening closely (and losing 1d4 SAN) makes it clear that the messages were sent during the Vietnam War. Someone losing 3 or more SAN can hear that they all seem to circle around a set of particular coordinates deep in the Vietnamese jungle. An investigation into the coordinates find no official information on any US troop movements in that area, though the area for some reason was targeted with an ARCLIGHT carpet bombing.</item>
        <item>A stone tablet with several symbols carved on it. The symbols exert 1G worth of force in a cone out to 10 feet and 10 feet across at the end with no corresponding counterforce. It\'s lying face down in the back of the green box with a post-it note on top that says "Do not move without proper precautions." 0/1d2 SAN to see effects of tablet.</item>
        <item>A plastic ziploc bag containing a folded up piece of parchment and a small plastic box with lid. The box contains a brownish powder. The parchment seems to be a single page from an old 16th-century german book and describes (in german) how to protect oneself from "The Burning Ones" by making a protective circle using "The Ash of Ah\'Zid". [Using the brownish powder a 6\' diameter circle can be created which keeps Fire Vampires at bay.]</item>
        <item>A massive tire, nearly the size of a man, suspended by chains from the walls to keep it from touching the floor. A pilot or other similarly knowledgeable person would recognize it as being from a Boeing 747\'s front landing gear.\nIt is splattered with a faintly shimmering gray-green mold of some sort; anything that touches it begins to dissolve as though from powerful acid, including another tire, although this tire shows absolutely no signs of damage from hosting it.</item>
        <item>A finger bone from a T. rex. A successful forensics or natural history will tell an agent that the bone is not fossilized. In fact, it\'s rather fresh...</item>
        <item>A pewter locket, one designed to carry small pictures of loved ones inside. If a picture of a human is placed within, any time the holder squeezes the locket in their hand, the object of the photo will be compelled to think about the locket holder, regardless of distance or recognition (possible SAN loss for repeated use up to the Keeper). If the locket holder is foolish enough to put a picture of themselves inside and squeeze, they will have a panic attack (SAN cost 1/1d3).</item>
        <item>A series of carved chess pieces: a knight, a rook and a bishop. If the investigator stays in the presence of the pieces for longer than 4 hours, they will first begin to whimper, and then scream with the investigator\'s voices. 1d4 san loss.</item>
        <item>A pen that is engraved H.P Lovecraft. If a person picks up the pen there sanity drops to zero as they see all thing as they are. If a person drops the pen there sanity returns to half normal however if a insane person picks up the pen they are nolonger insane. Stabbing a monster, or any supernatural thing with the pen turns the being in to a stack of paper detailing the encounter up until the creatures demise.</item>
        <item>A clay stovepipe. If lit, the smoke casts intricate shapes that appear to be screaming faces. (Sanity loss: 0/1d3)</item>
        <item>A small spool of 550-lb parachute cord, color construction-vest orange. Although it looks to be around 300 feet of cord, any attempt to unwind it all the way will fail; at some point or another, more cord somehow appears on the spool without anyone noticing.\nNo SAN loss for normal use of the line; however, if someone deliberately tries to unspool it to the end, or to an amount large enough to clearly notice it isn\'t running out, SAN loss is 1/1d4+1.</item>
        <item>A locked metal container 1\'x2\', slightly cold to the touch. If forced open, the container is revealed to contain a large symmetrical white crystal. The crystal is several degrees below room temperature. In fact, the crystal is an Elder Thing artifact, and contains 12 magic points for those with the ability to harness its power.</item>
        <item>A poncho. Should anyone wear this faded poncho and sleep during daylight hours, they will enter into a deep sleep, envisioning themselves as a hawk, osprey, or similar bird perched on the shoulder of their sleeping form. They can then move about freely in this dream-form, and the world they perceive is precisely the same as the real one, save that the bird is non-corporeal and does not exist. After two hours, the dream ends.</item>
        <item>A bronze disc about the size of a quarter dangling from a frayed black silk cord. The disc has a slightly shaky looking Yellow Sign engraved on it. Wearing the medallion on the outside of one\'s clothing might make it possible to pass oneself off as a member of a Yellow Sign cult. Wearing the medallion against one\'s skin for longer than 12 hours activates a subtle curse bound into the amulet; for each 12 hours of constant contact with the amulet (cumulative; taking the amulet off periodically only suspends the curse\'s effects), the wearer gains a -1 penalty to not join a Yellow Sign cult encountered later.</item>
        <item>A thick bundle of moth-eaten blankets. Unravelling them reveals an immaculate steel tuning fork. If struck against something solid, it produces a perfect C# note, and will not stop unless pressure is applied by human tissue. In the third round the note is allowed to ring out, everyone in audible range will start experiencing great discomfort and ear pain if they are not wearing ear protection, but with no lasting damage. In the fourth round, solid inanimate objects (walls, floors, ceilings, furniture etc) will start vibrating, and stopping the fork by touch will cause the individual 1d4 points of burning damage on contact with the metal. In the fifth round, everyone in audible range without ear protection will begin bleeding from the ears as their inner ears begin rupturing, for 1d6 points of damage. In the sixth round, this increases to 1d8 points of damage for those unprotected, and 1d4 for those with ear protection. Nearby structures will also begin to split and crumble. What happens in further rounds is the decision of the Keeper.</item>
        <item>A large blue-red conch-shell with an intricately wrought metal mouthpiece and receiver attached. Its provenance is unknown, though its style has similarities to that of certain pre-19th century South Caribbean cultures.\nIf blown at an expanse of sea-water during high-tide there is a 50% chance 1d3 Deep Ones will appear within 1d3 hours.</item>
        <item>A pair of antique glasses, brass framed with round glasses. Tiny latin lettering can be seen if examining the frames closely, indicating some sort of incantation. Wearing the glasses in daylight gives a slight headache as the world seems to grow vaguely distorted. Wearing them in moonlight and/or starlight makes the distortion go away and everything within sight can be seen as if affected by the Powder of Ibn Ghazi. But there is one great danger ... watching the full moon through the glasses will let the wearer see a monstrous multi-lobed Eye open on the surface, making the wearer instantly lose 1d6/4d10 SAN.</item>
        <item>A small leather pouch containing a fine, grey, ash-like powder. The powder rapidly decays anything it touches, regardless if it is living or not. Only the pouch is immune.</item>
        <item>A pair of mirrored sunglasses in a felt carry-case that make the wearer completely unmemorable and physically indistinguishable. It doesn\'t affect video recordings, fingerprints or DNA, however.</item>
        <item>25 feet of barbed wire spooled on a hickory stick carved with hobo signs. The signs indicate the wire is a deadly animal sent from God. They also convey the animal makes a safe home or shelter from devils. If strung from hard points, the wire will animate, snag, and entangle mythos creatures passing within three feet. The wire turns white hot and inflicts burning damage until a creature can untangle itself from the constricting coils.</item>
        <item>A large flat box is on top of something needed in the green box. It will take two people to safely lower it down. If not properly lowered or if purposely opened, the playyers will find a disk covered in cloth wrappings. A note pinned to the cloth says "Do not unwrap.Shield of Alexannder the great. It turned two agents to stone the last time."</item>
        <item>A collection of six small urns containing a blue-grey foul-smelling powder. Each urn is marked by the roman letters "I" to "VI". These are essential salts, unfortunately someone have used at least two of them as ash-trays</item>
        <item>A piece of pottery that seems to show one of the investigators worshipping a vast, toadlike thing. That investigator suffers 1/d6 SAN loss.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a 6" long iron rail spike. The spike emits a faint bluish glow which can be seen in darkness. Touching it with bare skin brings a tingling feeling which spreads through the whole body and then fades away. [Whoever touched it has now had his or her DNA subtly changed and will no longer match any previous samples. Extended exposure may cause cancer.]</item>
        <item>A blue bottle-cap bearing the words "Ankaran Cola". When placed in any kind of opaque container, its temperature increases until it burns through or melts whatever it has been placed inside.</item>
        <item>A palm sized shard of mirror, if viewed indoors it reflects normally. Outside the surface reveals a dramatically different background, a sky the colour of drying blood filled with burning black stars, tall glassy trees, buildings replaced with crumbling stygian spires. This costs the 1/1D4 San</item>
        <item>One highly magnetized glass sphere, 3 cm in diameter. Anyone inspecting it and making a physics or chemistry roll loses 0/1 point of Sanity.</item>
        <item>A jet-black cord of about 7 feet, ending in a hangman\'s noose. Anyone hanged in this noose will remain mentally aware of their surroundings, though exhibiting all physical signs of death, for weeks, until they eventually lose mental faculties entirely from their brain literally decaying to the point of uselessness.</item>
        <item>A spherical black stone, about the size of a human eyeball, and run through with red mineral veins. If carried by a human, it will summon and bind a Creature of the Wind - an ice-cold, immaterial and inhuman monstrosity that rides the ethereal winds. Whenever the carrier sleeps, the Creature will hunt down those who have upset the carrier, even in a trivial way, and feed upon them.</item>
        <item>A Brunton Mil-Spec compass. What makes it unique is that it no longer points north. If used it will point you straight towards an area favorable to contacting Yog-Sothoth.</item>
        <item>A wooden case lined with felt padding and containing two 1" glass spheres (there are spaces for six). Each sphere is filled with an unusual silvery powder (Dust of Suleiman). There is a label, in French, on the case, which says "Property of D. Helcimer".</item>
        <item>The hand of an adult human male with candle wicks in place of finger tips. If all of the wicks are lit they shine a 20 foot radius of stable light around the hand, far much more light than small candle fires should be able to produce. When lit, the hand also emits a strong smell of burning flesh. The hand is an actual human hand, not one made of wax and the fingers do not melt, catch fire or otherwise become damaged by the flames. SAN 1d2/0 on first use.</item>
        <item>A VHS tape which, when played, turns out to be footage from a police dashboard camera. The officer is driving quickly on dark backwoods roads, with lights and siren on, and can be heard saying he is responding to some call. He turns onto a gravel driveway, and a burning home comes into view at the other end.\nSuddenly, a massive black form lurches into view, and a black tendril-looking shape smashes down on the hood of the vehicle, almost flattening the engine block through sheer force. As the vehicle cuts out, the officer can be heard screaming in terror, and several gunshots (by their volume, evidently being fired by the officer from inside the vehicle) seem to do nothing to stop the colossal beast (recognizable to those versed in the Mythos as a Dark Young). The camera eventually cuts out, but not before showing the officer being torn limb from limb by the monster.\nSAN cost: 1d3/1d10; CM +4</item>
        <item>A ring that fits easily on the thumb of anyone who tries it on carved out of some kind of bone (Keeper\'s choice). The ring beras an enchantment such that the wearer will go unharmed by the next attack from whatever creature whose bone was used to make the ring before shattering and becoming useless forevermore. For example, if the ring was made from a human thighbone then the wearer would miraculously avoid taking damage from the next attack from a human being; the ring would either take the hit itself or \'accidentally\' shatter as a result of the near-miss.</item>
        <item>Three empty bottles of microbrew cask ale called "Mother\'s Olde Peculiar". Imported from Severn Ales, of Clotton, UK, its unlisted secret ingredient is the transformative Milk of Shub-niggurath...</item>
        <item>A lantern, when lit, reveals the true face of anyone (or anything) caught in its glow.</item>
        <item>A clammy green-black spine, about three-feet long, sticky to the touch, and snapped at its base. The point is incredibly sharp (inflicts 2D6+4 impaling damage if used as a spear).\nA successful Cthulhu Mythos roll recognises it as a tine snapped from the Great Old One, Glaaki. Sanity loss for this is 1/1D2+1</item>
        <item>A \'Get Out of Jail Free\' Monopoly card.\nIt is signed on the back, \'Rip in half to use. Good any time. ~S.A.~\'\nIf ripped in half, the agent\'s phone rings.....</item>
        <item>A fragment of black coral, carved into a humanoid shape in a plastic baggie. The bag is half-filled with sea water. If the carving is dried off it will slowly \'perspire\' more salt-water until it is wet again. Only keeping it in a heated environment like an oven will keep it dry - and it will still inexplicably cake with salt.</item>
        <item>A small (2" diameter), and slightly pitted, iron sphere covered in strange swirling symbols. There is a chance (15%) that anyone within 3\' of the sphere may experience strange light flashes, though mostly if in the dark. [The area within 3\' of the sphere is filled with a continuous stream of heavy cosmic radiation, much more than is common this far inside the earth\'s magnetic field. Long-term exposure may lead to radiation sickness and/or cancer.]</item>
        <item>A bronze breastplate, covered in gold leaf. Beside it is a sheaf of papers, which describe the unearthing of the object in a Roman burial in the mid 20th century dig, but also the research indicates the object to be of Greek origin, from ~330-320 BC.\nWhile worn, the breastplate deflects all non-magical weapons that attempt to hit it. Melee weapons simply bounce off or stop short, and missiles will either miss the target (as if deflected by an unseen force) or bounce harmlessly off. Carefully aimed attacks can still hit areas not covered by the plate.</item>
        <item>A Yithian Temporal Communicator, fashioned from random junk. It appears to be broken, but a set of successful Electrical and Mechanical repair rolls will allow it to be turned on to contact the target Yithian.</item>
        <item>A mill stone. When not being rotated it appears to be a regular mill stone. However, when rotated it shows a story related to the cult of Shub-Niggurath. San damage is up to DM.</item>
        <item>A clear glass canister, seemingly empty, with a cork stopper. However, if opened, it will begin to draw all the air from the room into itself, as if it contained an infinitely large vacuum. If not eventually resealed, it could conceivably consume the atmosphere.</item>
        <item>An ornately carved canine tooth from a large animal, suspended in a silver pendant on a silver chain. Anyone who wears the chain has dreams of flying blindly through total darkness; the dream always ends upon landing. (Sanity loss 1/1d4 first night, 0/1 each subsequent night). If the wearer grasps the tooth while standing atop a high hill or building on the night of the full moon a nightguant appears and carries them off to Carcosa. (Sanity loss 1d6/2d8 for onlookers, 2d6/4d8 for the person so carried).</item>
        <item>A small octagonal whistle, carved from onyx and engraved with elaborate angular geometric designs. Blowing the whistle will summon a Hound of Tindalos, characters with a sorcerous bent my use this opportunity to bind the creature and sick it upon someone. Failure to do so will result it in hunting them down through space and time.</item>
        <item>An unmarked disc placed within a Roadwar 2000 (Strategic Simulations, Inc., 1986) case. If inserted into any machine that displays images and has multiple controls (including a remote), a video game will appear on the screen. The game\'s controls will be mapped to the machine\'s controls, disabling any functions those controls had for the duration. If played, the game (different every "use") will represent a current event and allow the user to decide the event\'s outcome. This outcome will come about within the next few months exactly as portrayed. If the game is not completed for any reason, the event immediately worsens, resulting in large-scale loss of life.</item>
        <item>A two-meter wide by one millimeter thick, rolled up black piezoelectric disc with a built in microphone and transmitter. Unfurling the disc and walking in a circle on it transfers sufficient kinetic energy to power the unit. The microphone picks up the slightest sounds to transmit strong radio signals into space. While transmitting, images of bursting nebulae coil and twist under the feet. A page ripped from an archeologist\'s field notebook indicates this was recovered from a tomb in Jordan, listing specific GPS co-ordinates. The tomb had been sealed for at least 3000 years.</item>
        <item>Someone has packed sack lunches for the agents in brown paper bags, writing either their real first names or their childhood nicknames on them with Sharpie. Each sack contains a lunch that they personally would have been very happy to get at the age of 8 or 9; 0/1d2 SAN loss to think about who or what would have done this for them.</item>
        <item>A jam jar filled with screwed-up bits of paper. Paper removed and unravelled reads, in typewritten text, either "Innocent" or "Guilty" depending on the individual\'s guilt or innocence.\nWhat "guilt" or "innocence" the paper actually measures is unknown, but it is 100% accurate. The jam jar never runs out of paper.</item>
        <item>A small wooden case containing three sealed glass vials with a sulphur-yellow powder in them. The vials are marked with hand-written notes in arabic, which in translation means something like "The Soothing Sand". Inhaling the powder will temporarily increase the subjects SAN with 2D10 points as a feeling of safety, warmth and contentment washes away the worries of the subject. The gained SAN points disappears at a rate of 1 point each hour.</item>
        <item>A dried wax seal of a symbol unknown to anyone, regardless of roll. Breaking the wax seal will summon a basketball-sized stone of hail to fall from the skies, which will then attempt to land atop the nearest person to where the seal was broken. A failed dodge roll will result in 2d6 damage, and the hail will melt away within 1d4 minutes.</item>
        <item>A series of various sized and colouered glass lenses held in an over-complex contraption made of burnished copper. Looking at written texts through the lenses will reveals hidden meanings, though the veiwer will not consciously understand or remember them. The user can still glean esoteric secrets from the painful after-images that torment them.</item>
        <item>A storage crate captured from the Nazis at the end of World War 2. Inside is a whole collection of effigies of Cthulhu in a lot of styles, matters and crafts, coming from most parts of conquered Europe and the colonial French empire. San damage is at the gms discretion. However, due to the volume effigies it would probably not be wise to stack San costs.</item>
        <item>An old chinese opium-pipe in skillfully carved as an eastern dragon. It has been lacquered red and has a small brass bell attached to the end of it. Anyone smoking opium in it will experience wondrous and horrifying visions of faraway places. An experienced dreamer [used it at least six times] may gain some control of what places he or she views. But the risk of seeing things you don\'t want to see is always high. [lose 0/1d6 SAN]</item>
        <item>A pair of glasses with cracked lenses. When worn the world looks fractured and split. Sometimes people split by the cracks don\'t appear all that human.</item>
        <item>A small wooden box containing a brooch made from verdigrised bronze. It is shaped as a stylized butterfly with swirling designs covering the wings. [The wearer of the brooch become the locus of a probability crossing, making the results of actions taken more extreme. In practice this means that any skill (or attribute) roll of 01-05 gives an extremely good result (dealing maximum damage, gaining instead of losing SAN, convincing insane Cultists to release their sacrifices and surrender etc), but a result of 95-00 gives a catastrophic result (gun exploding in hand, driving the car straight into a gasoline truck which explodes, losing twice the maximum SAN for an encounter etc).]</item>
        <item>A .357 SIG round with a copper jacket. Engraved on it is some very small writing and some cryptic symbols. If examined the writing turns out to be the players name. As long as the player has this bullet in their possession they cannot be harmed by gunfire.</item>
        <item>A metallic rod that turns any flesh it touches unnaturally black. The blackened flesh,while still functionial causes immense and unrelenting pain.</item>
        <item>A white Cleveland Indians pennant covered with intricately-interlocking occult symbols relating to various elder gods, all of which subtly draw attention to the center where a stylized depiction of Y\'golonac seems to reach out towards the viewer. 0/1 SAN if the viewer does not recognize the imagery, 0/1d4 if they do.</item>
        <item>A small metal bottle covered in small semi-precious stones. It is sealed with wax and contains a foul-smelling concoction which will for a brief time (1D10 minutes) grant its imbiber a +20% bonus to the following skills: Swim, Sneak, Track, Hide, Listen, Jump and Climb. A laboratory analysis of the liquid shows it to contain alcohol, unknown plants and human DNA, specifically brain matter.</item>
        <item>A green soapstone carved in the shape of a seven pointed star. No matter what the ambient temperature is it is always covered with frost; anyone touching it with their bare skin takes 1 point of cold damage per round.</item>
        <item>A wrought iron Celtic cross, about three feet high, warped as if exposed to high heat. Each of its four ends is caked with a smooth violet substance that will not come off.</item>
        <item>An antique music box. This dark blackish-gray box is ornately worked pewter, measuring 8" long, 5" wide, and 5" tall. The carved relief on each side depicts the sun halfway clear of the horizon, but there is nothing else in the reliefs that reveals whether it\'s setting or rising. There is a small yellow post-it note stuck on the flat, featureless lid. "DO NOT WIND TWICE IN A ROW !" If the box is opened, a plain looking figure will arise. It is very simple, and could be either a male or female. Once the box is wound up (20 turns of the key) and opened, the figure will emit bright light as it spins to a haunting tune; the brightness being equivalent to that of a 60 watt electric bulb. If wound to its maximum, the box will function for exactly 4 minutes, 37 seconds. If it is wound a second time or more, it will function exactly as before, but anyone within 50\' will begin to suffer the same cognitive effects as becoming intoxicated. Each time it is wound and played after the 2nd time doubles the effects, the severity remains at the GM\'s discretion.</item>
        <item>A handful of coins bearing the colorful sheen of anodized niobium plating, marked by age to varying degrees. The obverse of each features a stern man with bristly hair and the value "21 Zhai", and the reverse bears a bird rising from a sunrise or sunset.\nIf flipped, the coins will only ever come up heads, despite being balanced enough to stand on-edge.</item>
        <item>A small silver locket, containing the face of a young girl and an older woman, presumably the girl\'s mother.\nWhenever this locket is picked up, the next time it is opened it will display the person holding it instead of the mother. If the holder has never killed anyone, the other frame will be blank; if they have, it will be a picture of the person they most recently killed, their expression locked at the moment of death.\nSeeing this is 1/1d2 SAN loss (if no victim is displayed) or 1/1d4+1 (with a victim), with additional penalties tacked on for bringing up any specific trauma concerning the event.</item>
        <item>An attractive mid-19th century fiigree locket, entwined with painted roses and sinuous vines, all bound in yellow insulating tape.\nThe locket contains a miniature gate about the size of a human thumbnail, leading to the swirling nuclear abyss of Azathoth\'s throne. If peered into, the gate gives a direct glimpse of the Blind Idiot God itself (SAN 1d10/1d100). Thankfully the gate\'s small size should stop anything coming through...</item>
        <item>Three 500 mg vials of golden tan powder, the black shiny labels read "Turrandy" and are marked with skillful and flourishingly elaborate calligraphy using a golden paint marker. The glass screw-on caps are marked with a plainly visible and fully charged Yellow Sign against the same undulating black label material. The Carcosan sigil will bloom like a golden lotus, sprinkling the minds of stunned observers like the lyrical alien poetry of a forbidden cloud of glowing pollen. Any insanity connected to the powder or Carcosan madness may well manifest in a maddening urge to dose oneself with the Turrandy Powder.\nForensic and Scientific analysis of the label will reveal the paint to be rather normal, but the label material will be partially identified as an unknown species of reptile, probably a serpent. If the powder is immersed in water it coagulates into clear cubes of gelatin, each with a tiny gold snake in the center. This costs 0/1 SAN to experience. The source of the powder itself will be revealed as the roots of an African herbal plant known as "Devil\'s Claw." However, the powder also seems to include various unidentifiable alkaloids.\nAnyone who ingests the material in whatever form will immediately lose 1/1d3 SAN and experience 1d6 mild Carcosan hallucinations over the next few days./nThey will also have all math/physics skill rolls count as "easy" for double skill.\nUnmarked bottle containing blue viscous fluid. (It\'s one ounce of fluid retrieved from the body of a victim of an attack by a Hound of Tindalos.)</item>
        <item>Surveillance photos of various druidic type meetings being held in the parking lot of a supermarket near the Green Box. It couldn\'t have been hard to miss: there are enough cowls and flaming torches, but despite the dates showing it took place every weekend for a month, no police or newspaper reports talk about it.\nIf checked out, the leader of the group in the photos is Reggie Cornell, a middle-aged ex-con and deliveryman who has been tentatively tied to worship of Ithaqua.</item>
        <item>A cobalt blue glass vial containing approximately 1.5 liters of a clear liquid. It is stopped by a cork whose top is painted with black lacquer and an unidentifiable red sigil. The vial sits inside a wooden pail that has a larger version of the sigil painted on the inside bottom.</item>
        <item>Anything placed in the pail and bathed in the liquid will dissolve entirely at a rate of 1 point of SIZ per hour. While this occurs, there are no detectable byproducts, and the volume and weight of the liquid does not change. Any liquid spilled or poured outside the pail will dissolve quickly, and it does not appear to be poisonous if ingested. Small animals forcibly kept in the pail decompose five times slower - making the process extremely difficult. Parts of larger animals and humans placed in the pail while still alive effectively be confined long enough for the process to work, although it is mildly painful to the subject.</item>
        <item>Chemical analysis of the liquid reveals a mindbogglingly complex organic structure. Successive attempts to analyze it will yield different, yet no less intricate, formulae. Any attempts to recreate the chemical end in combustible, if not outright explosive, failures.</item>
        <item>A baseball-sized chunk of rock that is obviously granite, which will be backed up by any and all geological testing. However, it is completely weightless in the hand, and if dropped will fall so slowly as to be imperceptible; unless recorded via multi-day time lapse it will seem to just hang in the air. 0/1 SAN when picking it up, 1/1d4 if dropped.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a small chinese puzzle box made from black wood with silver details. The details show dragons, cranes and strange flower-like creatures that a successful Mythos-roll will identify as stylized Elder Things. Anyone managing to open the box, through force or skill, will find a small piece of folded-up parchment upon which a swirling Mandala is painted. Looking at the Mandala will make the watcher _temporarily_ lose 1D100 SAN as he or she suddenly gains a horrifying insight into the real nature of the universe. The lost SAN returns at a rate of 1 point each hour as the insight fades into a distant dream, unless the total SAN loss exceeded the character\'s remaining SAN in which case the "negative" SAN is permanently lost, and the same amount of Mythos-skill is gained.</item>
        <item>A set of normal-looking surgical tools, including scalpels, hemostats, retractors, etc. If used in an actual surgery, the patient will always die horrendously from general organ failure some hours later, without fail. No autopsy or medical examination will concretely connect the tools to the death, or show any tangible signs of malpractice or sabotage by the surgeon (unless there actually was malpractice or sabotage), though obviously the fact that surgery recently occurred is suspicious.</item>
        <item>A mirror that isn\'t actually a mirror. It\'s like looking at someone else - you\'re not inverted. Harmless, a curiosity, but a tiny bit creepy. (0/1 SAN loss).</item>
        <item>An average gunmetal-gray reading lamp, with goose-neck flexible stand. The power cord has been cut about two inches from the base, but it inexplicably still works. Agents disassembling it looking for backup power supplies will suffer 0/1d2 SAN loss, as they discover there is literally no electricity going into the lamp. Otherwise, it is completely normal.</item>
        <item>A computer. If touched, pulls in the person touching it. 1d4 SAN to see this.</item>
        <item>A Tillinghast Resonator has been manufactured out of junkyard material and currently takes up much of the Green Box. Starting it up would, naturally, be a very bad idea...</item>
        <item>A rather handsome-looking black leather pouch held closed with a length of rawhide and a bead. The contents of the pouch are a handful of unassuming-looking black stones, definitely glass of some kind. If placed equidistant from one another in a ring the stones form a magical ward that makes the location they demarcate a less attractive site to commit violence (POW vs. POW of 12 to think about committing violent acts inside the ring, POW vs. POW of 10 to cross the ward and start a fight). Note that creatures outside of the ward do not necessarily have to know it\'s there, the reaction is instinctive.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a heavy silver ring, with seven small deep-violet stones set into it. Something like sea-weed has been engraved around the ring. [Anyone wearing the ring has an increased chance (+10%) of being spotted by Mythos-creatures, or zero SAN cultists. The required MP\'s to cast a summoning spell is also reduced by 1 for the wearer.]</item>
        <item>A set of spy-plane photographs of what is identified as a Romanian castle codenamed "GRAY SOLSTICE". It appears to be from the mid-1950s, and handwritten annotations identify what seem at first to be prisoner transports entering the gates. However, later the commenter becomes convinced they are human sacrifices, and semi-crazed speculation begins to bloom regarding their purpose. Subsequent analyses by the annotator identify bizarre photographic anomalies, misplaced shadows, and a general sense of wrongness pervading the location.\nEventually a set of photos reveals the castle suddenly being leveled by Soviet artillery during what could only be described by the pilot as a \'localized solar eclipse\', and the handwriting becomes both nearly illegible scribbling and completely unintelligible ranting.\n1/1d4 SAN loss if the investigators buy into what they see; 0/1 if not.</item>
        <item>In the top shelf of a fridge-freezer, a Ziploc bag with a note written in permanent marker; "WARNING: Keep frozen, do not thaw". Inside the bag is another bag, containing an irregular black pebble an inch and a half across.\nIf removed from its bag, the pebble maintains a surface temperature ten degrees colder than the surrounding air at all times. If it is warmed above 80 F, it melts into an amorphous blob of thick black liquid; it does not re-freeze unless its surroundings are below 50 F. The blob is able to move under its own power, and will attempt to move towards the nearest source of heat (or away from an extremely cold object). If poked or prodded by an inorganic substance, it will recoil. If poked or prodded by an organic substance, it will consume it and absorb its mass, growing larger. If given the opportunity, it will attach itself to an organic source of warmth (such as a person) and begin to consume it.\nBLACK BLOB\nSTR 02 SIZ 01 POW ??? DEX 04 Move 2 HP 10\nDamage Bonus: not applicable\nWeapon: Consume 100%, damage 1D2 in the round following successful Attach, and thereafter.\nSkill: Attach 20%.\nSanity Cost: 0/1D3 SAN.\n??? = passive but enormous POW\nIf the blob grows sufficiently large, it will begin to adopt physical characteristics of whatever it has consumed; for instance, if it has eaten a rat, it will grow stubby legs and a tail. As the blob grows, its stats (and sanity loss) likewise increase. Once its size exceeds 12, it begins to psychically "sing"; humans in its vicinity must pass a POW x5 roll or involuntarily flee, losing 0/1d6 SAN in the process.\nPhysical attacks are effective against the blob, but merely break it into smaller pieces. If any quantity of the blob is reduced to less than a pound, it will dissolve into a tarry and highly caustic, but otherwise inert mass. If an ambulatory piece comes into contact with the dissolved mass, it will reanimate and reabsorb it.</item>
        <item>A large evidence bag containing a folded up old-style straightjacket. It is quite worn and smells of old urine, sweat and vomit, but otherwise seems functionable. Someone examining it closer will find strange squiggly runes sewn onto its inner lining. [Anyone wearing the straightjacket have a 5% chance each midnight of getting the attention of the invisible (and predatory) Things that exist out of sync with our reality. If this happens he or she disappears without a trace.]</item>
        <item>Two matched brooches. If both brooches are worn by different people, each of them will be able to communicate telepathically with the other as long as they remain with 500 feet of each other. SAN loss 1/1d4 when properties are first discovered.</item>
        <item>A simple white ceramic bowl, filled with dried-up red stains. At closer examination, the bowl appears to be a common soup bowl, albeit lacking any maker\'s marks, and the stains inside it seem to be dried-up chili or other reddish stew. If tidied up properly, scrutiny will reveal that the inside of the bowl is decorated with a few slight indentations that fashion the bowl\'s appearance into what can be seen as a frightened face. Furthermore, if the bowl is filled with water, and one concentrates on examining the face beneath the surface, visions that may or may not be beneficial hints towards a mythos-related issue at hand may be gained. 0/1d3 sanity loss for using.</item>
        <item>A collection of six-sided dice which, without any visible or otherwise tangible means of tampering, always come up in whatever result the owner currently desires. Should they be used in the presence of a psychically receptive individual, though, that person will be shocked to see spectral, demonic-looking hands drifting up from the floor and altering the roll.</item>
        <item>A small, weathered pocket Gideon\'s Bible. The inside is hollowed out, and has a lock of red hair wrapped around a strike-anywhere match by a length of red ribbon. If the match is struck, the character will immediately lose 1d3 Sanity, but be immune to suggestion, hypnosis, or mesmerization of any kind for 24 hours.</item>
        <item>A leather pouch containing a small (3 inch) monkey carved from black wood (presumably Ebenholz). It seems quite old and worn, but it is still possible to discern its leering features.\n[Anyone sleeping within 10 feet of the monkey will have horrible nightmares of a black stalking creature creeping closer and closer. SAN loss is 1/1d4 each time. If reduced to zero SAN in this way the victim also suffers 5d6 of damage as his or her flesh is torn as if by invisible claws.]</item>
        <item>Brown hard-acoustic guitar case. The first time it\'s opened, it is empty. Every subsequent time, a different guitar is inside.</item>
        <item>A stone tablet with a crude outline of a man with bear-traps in place of hands, as if drawn by a child. Engraved above the man is the name "Aidan". The tablet is covered in various liquids, the only identifiable one without passing an Occult check is human blood. Passing an Occult check allows you to identify the other liquids as inhuman entrails of who knows what. Touching the object causes an amount of Sanity loss, TBD by the Keeper.</item>
        <item>A large envelope containing a human finger-bone wrapped in dirty rags and sealed with wax. Written on the front of the envelope: "Don\'t unwrap this. Use as necessary. And put it back - it\'s my dad\'s finger. ~ P"\nSo long as the seal and wrappings are not removed, anyone carrying the artefact will find doors open as if they were unlocked, windows swing open at a push, and electronic keypads and swipe-cards will allow immediate access.</item>
        <item>A home-made Mi-Go communication device built out of stage-lighting and multi-colored lenses. The entire thing is about the size of a DJ\'s sound-mixing deck, complete with toggles and buttons, but the scanty handwritten notes on how to convey basic messages, like "greetings", "acknowledged" and "negative", implies the process is mostly trial and error.</item>
        <item>A lacquer box, with jade inlay. The inside of the box is filled with a scrawl of Chinese characters that anyone who passes an Occult or Mythos check can guess is some kind of ward or containment.\nAlso inside the box is a small piece of rock, roughly the size of a human eye, that is not so much black colored, as it absorbs all light that touches it. Any living creature that comes in direct contact with it is instantly killed, with no apparent cause of death. If they handle the object indirectly, such as through clothing, or protective gear will take 2d6 damage every round while the hold it, which ignores all forms of protection. If the examine the skin under the area where they touched the stone, they will find it necrotized and black, like some extreme cases of frostbite. Non-living but organic substances, such as leather, organic fibers and wood will decay rapidly in contact with the stone, and appear on analysis to show extreme effects of aging. Even non-organic substances are eventually worn down by touching the stone.\nA PC who can read Chinese characters can study the inside of the box for two weeks, then make and INT x 5 roll to learn how to copy the warding symbols. If they succeed, they are able copy the characters onto another object to ward it. This requires the spending of 1 point of POW and an INT x 5 roll (POW is spent regardless of if the roll passes or fails) to etch or paint the characters onto an object, such as a glove, bag or other container, which then becomes shielded to the stone\'s effects.</item>
        <item>A Mi-Go brain cylinder. There are no communication devices available, but someone has managed to jury-rig a one-way interface with a bunch of copper, electrician\'s tape and a light emitting diode. If attached to the cylinder, the light will begin to blink in morse code. Once transcribed, it\'s clear that it\'s just a long unending line of profanity and ranting.</item>
        <item>A jar containing the preserved remains of a minor unspeakable servant. Sanity and Mythos rolls are at DM discretion.</item>
        <item>A chair made out of fragments of unknowable and alien skeleton. The skulls are particularly inhuman, more insectoid than man. Sitting in it is uncomfortable (and may cost 1 HP if done for too long) and evidently not designed for human ergonomics. Seeing the seat for the first time costs 0/1D3 sanity loss.</item>
        <item>You have found an offcut of rough old wood 4" by 4" by 3/4" thick. A cleanly severed human tongue has been nailed to it using three very new flat-headed nails, whose points protrude from the other side of the offcut. The tongue appears very new; it is still wet with saliva, and there are traces of unclotted blood at its root. A small (1/2" diameter circular glyph has been scratched carelessly near each corner of the upper side of the piece of wood. The tongue stays fresh and moist indefinitely. The whole object is completely fireproof.</item>
        <item>A thin rod, made of what appears to be driftwood covered with strands of what appears to be copper, one end almost encased in the copper like metal. Anything coming within 4.5mm of the encased end is neatly incised. This includes flesh, bone, stone, steel... anything. 1/1d3 San loss to witness the effect.</item>
        <item>A 1914 Magnavox desk-telephone. Though disconnected and unpowered, if lifted from the cradle the receiver rings a drug-store in Lynchburg, Tennessee on a random day in 1927. Sometimes someone answers...</item>
        <item>A smooth streamlined back pack that has black wires coming from it and connecting to a bracelet. If the back pack is worn and at least an hour messing with the bracket the investigator can make a luck roll to figure out the device. If the device can be activated to allow the where to turn near invisible this causes 1d6 SAN the first time and 1 SAN every time after.</item>
        <item>A ouija board constructed out of newspaper clippings glued to the back of a ceral box. Seems only to communicate with a dead (though friendly) Toledo, Ohio, car mechanic named Frank, who died in 1979 and knows very little about life outside mundane Mid-West America.</item>
        <item>An old set of Tibetan Buddhist religious objects. A Phurba (ritual knife, three bladed knife), kapalamala of miniature bone skulls (108 "carved" skulls, close examination suggests that these are actually skulls that have been shrunken somehow; 0/1 San), a rKangling (bone trumpet made from a human thigh bone which has been tightly fitted with leather, and the metal encasing has been enhanced by a turquoise), and thodpa aka kapala (A cup made from the top of human skull and lined with silver, and fitted with a ruby in the base of the cup). Antique and worth thousands, these are piled in a bottom crate. No special abilities, save perhaps in the hands of a Tibetan priest or servant of one of the Dharmapalas.</item>
        <item>An ornate 16th century jewelry box containing a small silver needle. A bloody post-it note attached to the box reads \'DONT LOOK\' in a rushed, uneven scrawl. A subject that touches the needle with their bare hands will make it disappear. The needle will reappear the next morning floating a few inches away from the waking subject\'s face. Trying to grab the needle will only make it dart away, always returning to the same place. No one else can see or touch the needle. Every day, the needle draws ever so slightly closer to the subject\'s right eye causing SAN loss of 2/1D6 per day. The subject knows they must claw out their eyes or an extremely painful death will occur in ten days. No marks will be left on the body and the needle will reappear in its box. An autopsy will reveal the cause of death as cardiac arrest due to extreme psychological trauma.</item>
        <item>a black bracelet if death is in 24 hours it heats up releasing a small black knife, the knife can heal any one it pierces if it becomes hot if it becomes cold it can kill anyone instantaneous , the tempeture changes randomly so use quickly and with caution. The inscribing on the bracelet is ,"i wish this dream never ends i love you" the previous owners and story is unknown</item>
        <item>A basket-ball sized egg-shell hued sphere. In good light its mottled plasticky exterior seems to flicker with an interior light, rippling through an undercurrent of translucent veins. If queried on its existence, A-Cell reports it was recovered from a segregated public swimming pool in Nevada in 1953. No other information is available.\nThis is actually a Traveller\'s space-craft (as described in the Delta Green scenario "Puppet-Shows and Shadow-Plays"). It is impervious to all known damage, and currently beaming a tracking beacon into the cosmos - guiding more Travellers to Earth.</item>
        <item>A black iron fife, roughly eight inches long and one inch in diameter. Attempts to play it reveal it to be badly out of tune. If played outdoors on a windy cloudless night under a full moon a byakhee will appear and carry the player to whatever destination he specifies, at a cost of 1d4/1d8 SAN for anyone who sees this for the first time and 0/1 for each subsequent viewing.</item>
        <item>A Hex sign of Pennsylvania "Dutch" manufacture on a joined series of wooden boards. It looks to have been cut from some larger structure and consists of a red twelve pointed star inset with a circle. The sign will accurately predict the weather, with the color of the inset circle changing to reflect the next days weather. The correlation between the sign and weather can be understood by anyone studying the pattern of changes over a few days who can make an idea roll. The color will change only when the sign is not observed.</item>
        <item>A small black flash drive, devoid of any exterior markings. The only file on it is a virus, executed automatically when plugged in. The virus (which can bypass nearly any antivirus software) flashes onscreen a large Yellow Sign (SAN loss as usual) and the phrase "The Last King Is Come" so quickly that it is practically read subconsciously.</item>
        <item>A badly scratched vinyl record. The label indicates it was made in the 1940\'s and apparently it contains two songs by the blues singer Ramblin\' John Hastur. On the A side "Rise! Rise! Rise!" and on the B side "In The Heart". [If played, the first mournful song will make any human corpses within hearing distance rise as a murderous zombie for 1d10 minutes; the second rattling song, on the other side, will reduce any listeners SAN by 1d6 every round. No SAN roll necessary.]</item>
        <item>A Garmin dashboard-mounted GPS navigator which, when plugged in, will automatically map a route to a nearby recent murder scene (although never quite recent enough to allow capture of the murderer).</item>
        <item>A digital camera with a dead battery and a full memory card. All pictures are of the agents between the ages of 7 and 12.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>