<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_weird_weapons">
        <item>A cardboard box containing five one liter glass bottles filled with an oily liquid. Each bottle is wrapped with paper held in place with rubber bands. These are self-igniting molotov cocktails; when ruptured, the sulfuric acid within the bottle ( combined with motor oil and gasoline ) contacts the paper which is impregnated with potassium chlorate.</item>
        <item>A black polymer tube, roughly the dimensions of a rolled-up poster, which could be dismissed as a telescope or container. A small hole in the center of the bottom is revealed to be a muzzle after further investigation, and the top contains a well-concealed rolling-block mechanism opening up to the breech of a single-shot weapon which is fired by a sharp smack to the back end of the tube. It accepts a single 9x19mm round, and half of its 1 1/2 foot length is an extremely efficient suppressor. Combined with its lack of moving parts, the weapon makes very little sound, but the lack of sights and trigger makes it essentially a point-blank-only weapon.</item>
        <item>A traditional forged katana with a sheath and the fangs of an unknown serpent each as long as a human hand and smell like sea water, the blade has the name "serpent slayer" poorly inscribed on its blade the katana deals 2d10 and 1d4 poison damage.</item>
        <item>A Mosin-Nagant 91/30 Rifle shortened to 10 inches in length. Аn inscription on the side reads "ОБРЕЗ"</item>
        <item>What appears to be a captive bolt pistol incorporated into the point of an umbrella. The umbrella is decorated with strange, slightly hypnotic patterns over its surface when open.</item>
        <item>An extremely ornate Saiga-12 and a 7-round magazine loaded with FRAG-12 high-explosive rounds.\nThe stock has been removed and the barrel has been shortened to 8", causing the weapon to resemble an oversized pistol. "The emperor protects" is engraved on the receiver in illuminated script.</item>
        <item>This is a Beretta 92fs 9x19mm Parabellum handgun. The markings, and serial numbers have all been scratched out, though if the wielder was ever enlisted in the military, they may be able to make out the smallest hint that the weapon bears his units insignia.\nWhen disassembled, the weapon is in pristine condition, and fits back together easily. No matter what sort of treatment the weapon receives, it will always be this way.\nIf the weapon is forgotten somewhere, it will appear in the strangest of places, almost as if it were placed there by mistake, such as a pocket, or nightstand drawer.</item>
        <item>A strange device resembling an M72 Light Anti-armor Weapon strapped into a remote turret; this is an ARGES mine, designed to act as an autonomous long-distance landmine. It can be programmed to strike a specific target in a convoy, or controlled remotely.</item>
        <item>A bloodstained bat with nails in it. DNA searches will reveal the blood belongs to three casino owners in Las Vegas, all of whom died last year (The year the agents open the box) from \'natural causes\'.</item>
        <item>A survival knife with hollow storage handle. Searching the handle will find seven male human molars.</item>
        <item>An ancient Japanese katana, in the sheath. Drawing the sword from the sheath causes a single leaf to fall out. If examined, it can be identified as a leaf from plants native to Japan, and can be dated to around the year 1300. The leaf looks like it fell off the tree yesterday.</item>
        <item>A rusted Italian Bodeo revolver with a small crucifix attached to the lanyard ring. The grips have been replaced with crudely hand-carved wood, which carbon-dates to 500 years old.</item>
        <item>A gold-plated AKMS rifle of unsurpassed craftsmanship, apparently handmade by a master gunsmith, and covered in gorgeously-engraved Arabesque patterns. A small note suggests, "Saddam probably won\'t miss just one, eh?"</item>
        <item>A small wooden crate marked "Experimental. Use at own risk!"</item>
        <item>Inside are what initially appear to be 4 standard issue flash bang grenades. However, if they are used, they instead engingush</item>
        <item>Six crude-looking, obviously homemade directional antipersonnel mines, approximately equivalent to US M18A1 "Claymores," using bank-style paper rolls of old pre-1965 silver dimes as preformed shrapnel, embedded in blocks of plastique. The detonators and booster charges are also homemade and the fourth one is faulty; make a DEMOLITIONS roll to notice it while handling it or it won\'t go off; critical failure means it goes BOOM when disturbed.</item>
        <item>An HK P11 Underwater pistol. This weapon has five barrels, each holding a 10cm long dart in a cartridge, which are fired electronically using a battery in the handle. Once all five barrels are empty, the weapon must be sent back to the factory for reloading. As far as anyone can tell, it is fully loaded.</item>
        <item>A Steyr-Mannlicher M1895 bolt action rifle. There are carvings in the stock in an unknown language and dried green stains on the butt.</item>
        <item>In a corner of the Green Box are two matte-black cases made of plastics and ceramics. The first case is just over seven feet long, like a long rifle case, and is extremely heavy. Outside is a "WARNING! ELECTROMAGNETS." sticker. The other case is shaped roughly like it contains a large backpack, like the more expensive kind for hiking or survival. It bears both a High Voltage and "CONTENTS CONTAIN RADIOACTIVE MATERIALS" warning. Both cases declare "Property of Rivermore National Labs, inc". Investigation of the company will discover it was a Defense Contractor based in VA, that went under in 2005, and no further records exist.\nThe smaller case contains a heavy black ceramic shell of some kind of back-pack unit, with an inner lead shield. Inside are two highly experimental Nuclear Batteries, with a half-life of around 75 years, producing large amounts of electricity. While the case is designed to be very stable and secured, it still carries a risk of being breached. 1/1d4 SAN is an investigator sees the power-pack be ruptured. It lacks the fuel to reach critical mass, but is still highly radioactive if the batteries themselves are exposed.\nInside the long case is a 6+ ft bulky weapon, which has a vague shape of a rifle, with an advanced electronic sight mounted on top. An appropriate skill roll (Or a KNOW if nobody has any skills appropriate) will be able to tell this is some manner of man-portable Rail Gun, which is very clearly beyond any current technological level to build. The weapon fires steel cored tungsten jacketed 2mm darts at high velocities, and has a magazine holding 50 of them. The weapon is long, heavy, bulky and requires the external power-source provided. The weapon is technically semi-automatic, but requires some time to cycle the magnets between shots. The current charge strength is displayed on a HUD in the sight, which also features up to x5 zoom. 0/1 SAN if a character realizes how advanced this is, and how it CANNOT have been built with today\'s technology, as far as they understand.\nThe weapon uses the Rifle skill, requires minimum one turn of combat to charge before firing, max charge is at 3 turns. At one charge, it does 2d6+4 damage, and travels with enough velocity to penetrate most basic body armor. At two charge, it does 4d6+8 damage, and has enough force to punch through any body armor, and most vehicles, and at maximum charge, it deals 6d6+12 damage, and will penetrate the defenses of any target not immune to mundane weapons. KEEPER\'S NOTE: This is a prototype, and thus has several construction errors or bugs in the scope software. When ever it is used, roll a d6, and on a 1, the user of the weapon needs to make a LUCK check or the weapon experiences some error, such as the round not striking the target, not having enough force to travel the distance or penetrate the target, or having to much force, and the round vaporizing en route doing little more than shower down-range with some hot metal bits. Also, while someone with sufficient knowledge and equipment can manufacture more ammunition, after about 100 shots, the rails of the weapon will begin to deteriorate, which will ultimately result in the weapon being inoperable. This damage cannot be repaired, and the parts cannot be replaced unless one of them has some PhD level education in something like Electrical Engineering or Physics, and can get access to some expensive materials.</item>
        <item>A full-sized British Brown Bess musket, seemingly dated 1818. However, it bears impressive silver scrollwork all over, and several languages appear on it that have no right to be there. This includes classical Sanskrit, Babylonic cuneiform, and even the occasional string of ancient Egyptian hieroglyphics. Several other artistically-executed series of crude shapes clearly resemble languages, but seem to be so ancient as to be completely unrecorded in modern studies.</item>
        <item>A horribly rusted and corroded LeMat revolver, which looks as though it spent the time between the American Civil War and now at the bottom of a salt-water estuary. Any gunsmith (or layman, for that matter) will insist there is no way it will function, although it inexplicably does.</item>
        <item>An exquisitely-crafted mahogany display case, containing four firearms. Each of them have a beautifully-rendered engraved name on them. The first, a suppressed SR-25 rifle, is named "THE HUNTER"; the second, an Arsenal SGL 31-94 model Kalashnikov, is named "THE SOLDIER"; the third, a Luger P08 pistol, is named "THE GENTLEMAN"; the fourth and final is a short-barreled Remington 870 named "THE BRAWLER". All four weapons are lovingly maintained, of immaculate quality, and lie in specially-molded velvet depressions in the display case.</item>
        <item>A heavy hockey stick, with razorblades superglued to the inside of the crook as if someone had attempted to convert it into a homemade scythe. The razorblades and the crook are somewhat corroded, as if coated with acid.</item>
        <item>You find a golf club bag containing several single or double barrel(side byside or over/under) sawed off, 12gauge shot guns. Each chamber holds a Dragon\'s Breath round. Several of the guns were turned in during a local gun buy back program &amp; reported destroyed. Others were stolen from private collections, after the owners died. None can be traced. In the pockets of the bag are 2 dozen loose Dragon\'s Breath rounds.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a pale yellow scarf with a stack of four 1 dollar Silver Eagles sewn into one end, making the scarf a modern version of the Rumals used by the eradicated Indian Thugee-cult.</item>
        <item>An M72 LAW rocket launcher with an un-fired rocket. The surface is covered entirely with fine white text scrawled on with paint, reading the word "Pig" over and over.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a single 5.56mm rifle round enclosed in bubble plastic. Closer inspection reveals that the point of the bullet has been drilled out and then re-sealed with lead. A Geiger-counter will reveal that the bullet is slightly radioactive. [The narrow channel drilled into the bullet has been filled with the radiocative, and highly toxic, isotope Polonium 209.]</item>
        <item>A Chilean 6 Pounder Q.F. canister shot shell, spraypainted with tiger-stripes and a snarling feline face.</item>
        <item>A bizarre weapon which somewhat resembles an over/under shotgun, sawed down into the classic \'lupara\' design (extremely shortened barrel and pistol grip). Closer examination reveals the top barrel to be chambered for a 10-gauge shotgun shell, while the bottom is chambered for a .416 Rigby big-game round. Anyone familiar with antique firearms would perhaps call this a Howdah pistol, but the calibers it fires are simply irresponsible; shooting either barrel could very easily fracture the wrist of the average person.\nIn addition, there appears to be a bayonet lug running underneath the bottom barrel, and a sticky, discolored bayonet is wrapped in a cloth nearby. If anyone were to make appropriate checks, the blade is coated with curare, a paralyzing poison typically used in blowguns.\nThere is, in fact, some ammunition lying loose on the floor, but it is clearly as old as the gun, dating to before the First World War. Attempting to fire them would be either pointless or dangerous, depending on the Keeper\'s sadism preference.</item>
        <item>An old M1911 pistol, fires .45 rounds, hold 7 rounds. Oddly enough, there seems to a strange cylinder mounted, with a cross in front of it. Whatever it was, the attachment is inoperable. In a small bag are several bullets, all modified. 7 of these are filled with holy oil in their points, and 5 made of silver.</item>
        <item>A Kalashnikov AK74 type rifle in caliber 5.45x39mm with six spare magazines. It bears no serial number or manufacturer\'s markings and in fact the only markings present on it are on the receiver beside the safety selector: safe is marked "0," semiauto is marked "1," and full-auto is marked with an infinity symbol. A successful ARMORER roll will tell the player examining it that it appears to have been cobbled together from parts from different variations of Kalashnikov rifles made in different countries, and even single parts combine traits not normally seen together: it has a Chinese cellType side-folding stock with plastic cheekrest, but the plastic is the dark purplish plum-color polyamide plastic normally seen on Russian rifles manufactured during the early 1980s, the heat shield inside the handguards is aluminum instead of stainless steel, etc. It is used but well maintained and currently clean and lightly oiled, ready for use. No ammunition for it is present, however.</item>
        <item>A taliban suicide vest, it has undetonated explosive satchels on the front and a small screen with the IED status in red text, the screen is an old mobile phone with odd wiring that shouldn\'t make sense.\nThe oddest thing about it is that the IED status says that the vest has already been detonated.</item>
        <item>A 12-pounder Napoleon cannon from the Civil war, it lacks a limber and is therefore just a slab of metal weighing roughly 1,220 lbs.</item>
        <item>A knife with a foot-long bronze blade and a leather-wrapped bone handle. Examination by a skilled investigator will reveal that the bone handle is a human tiba, taken from an adult. The whole thing looks brand new.</item>
        <item>A Rapier, which, upon closer examination, has a blade not made of steel, but wrought iron.</item>
        <item>A plain cardboard box with dozens of rolls of toilet paper that have been soaked in human blood, which has since dried. Each toilet paper roll\'s cardboard tube core has been packed with Semtex plastic explosive and an electronic detonator of Czech manufacture.. "BAIT" has been scribbled on the side of the box in red lipstick.</item>
        <item>A Ruger 10/22 semiauto .22 caliber rifle with threaded muzzle and silencer, plus several 10-round magazines and a few boxes of ammunition, plus thirteen individual .22 cartridges in a plastic baggie--these thirteen have silver bullets. Neither rifle nor silencer bears any serial number or manufacturer\'s markings. Rifle is equipped with electronic red-dot optical sight and mounted in a European-style anatomically adjustable stock of the sort used in Olympic biathlons and other competitions. Stock has been painted matte black and has a red Post-It note stuck to the buttstock with the single word "STORMBRINGER" written upon it in felt-tip marker.</item>
        <item>A Missouri state police evidence bag containing a crudely-made improvised weapon, which consists of an extremely jagged pane of broken glass lashed onto a stick with electrical wiring. The entire weapon is crusted with dried blood, and case notes stapled to the bag indicate it was found in the possession of an insane (and currently unidentified) man who was found wandering aimlessly in a state park. They go on to report that he was found completely nude, attacked multiple police officers on sight with animal-like ferocity, and had to be shot four times with a high-powered rifle before he went down.</item>
        <item>A box of five 12 gauge hollow point slugs. An attached note says simply "Now With Cyanide" followed by a smiley face. An inspection of the slugs reveals that the hollows in the nose have been filled with something and the ends sealed with glue.\nIt is left to the keeper to decide how effective this is as a poison delivery system.</item>
        <item>One STEN gun, MKII, with wire stock and five loaded 32 round magazines. The receiver of the submachine gun appears to be made from plumbing pipe. No serial numbers or makers marks are present.</item>
        <item>A powerful recurve bow, plus a quiver holding a dozen handmade wooden arrows. The arrowheads are made from old silver coins and each has a crude approximation of an Elder Sign cut into it.</item>
        <item>A cheap Renaissance fair longsword of middling-quality stainless steel. The grip on the hilt has been replaced with a cleaned and well-sanded but still recognizable length of human vertebrae. 0/1d2 SAN loss.</item>
        <item>A cheap hatchet of the sort sold at Wal-Mart, spattered with old dried blood, with bits of hair still stuck to the sides of the blade. Analysis of the blood and hair will result in a DNA match for a person killed in a brutal ritual slaying in Miami, Florida in 2004. The fingerprints on the handle, however, are a match for those of long-dead former President Lyndon B. Johnson.</item>
        <item>Four M4A1 carbines wrapped in clear plastic sheeting. Upon examination, all of them have suffered serious jams, none of which could easily be cleared in combat conditions.\nA note affixed to one of them says,\n"I\'m not sure I did the math right, but it looks like the odds of all these jamming at the exact same time are 466,948,881 to one...what the fuck WAS that thing?"</item>
        <item>Wrapped in oiled cloth and stowed away in a long wooden box, you find an 1852 pattern Prussian light cavalry Saber. Small dots of rust are evident near the base of the blade, but otherwise the sword appears to be in excellent shape. Anyone with knowledge of such weapons will see that the sword\'s hilt has been fitted to the hand of a specific person. Anyone else will find the grip uncomfortable. Engraved near the base of the blade is the name Vogel, just under the image of an eagle..</item>
        <item>A chest rig of wiring, straps, and explosives, quite plainly a suicide vest. However, an explosives expert examining the vest will discover that the explosives are shaped charges, and the force of all is directed inwards rather than outwards. The remote detonator next to it only adds to the horror.</item>
        <item>A crudely-forged, amateurish stainless-steel broadsword, with a butane lighter incorporated into the hilt. Nearby are hastily scribbled and somewhat incomprehensible instructions on how to create a napalm-like coating to apply to the blade, in order to get a genuine flaming sword.\nIn addition to this clearly being a terrible idea, a Psychology roll while reading through the instructions, and the attached printouts of e-mails sent to A-Cell by an agent Ulysses advocating the standardization of this weapon, reveal its creator, agent Ulysses, to be clinically insane. He evidently began regarding Delta Green to be a modern day Camelot, complete with King Arthur and the Knights of the Round Table (he begins referring to himself as \'your Merlin\' as time goes by). None of Ulysses\' e-mails appear to have been answered, and if asked, A-Cell will inform the investigators that he became a danger to DG security and had to be terminated.</item>
        <item>Six canisters of pepper spray in a plastic box labelled "FACTORY DEFECT- DISPOSE OF IMMEDIATELY".\nUse of these canisters on a target results in permanent blindness, not just temporary.</item>
        <item>A HK69A1 40MM Grenade launcher, alongside 1d8 smoke, frag, flare, and non-explosive training grenades. The grenades are completely indistinguishable from one another, and require a 1d4 roll to determine the effect of the grenade. A note taped to the launcher reads: "On loan from our Al\'iikhwas in Riyadh - see about getting A-cell to ship this back. - F, 1992 ". If A-cell is contacted, they immediately demand that the launcher is destroyed.</item>
        <item>A Smith and Wesson M1917 .45acp revolver in an olive green canvas flap holster. There are 18 .45acp rounds in half moon clips with the weapon. It appears to be in perfect condition and smells faintly of gun oil.</item>
        <item>A weapon that looks like a crowbar, but feels alien. The metal is a naturally cold to the touch, and blacker than space. What normally would be the curved ends with a fork base, like that of an Egyptian Was scepter.\nAnyone holding the Bar feels more energetic and slightly more aggressive. But no permanent changes occur.</item>
        <item>A cheap looking plastic thermos container 16 cm long and 10cm in diameter. Picking it up, you realize it weighs much more than it should. Hidden inside are a ring of very strong permanent magnets at the bottom and a sealed metal cylinder. A wire protruding from the top of the cylinder is attached to a cicuit board with several DIP switches. On a successful idea roll, an investigator will recognize this as some kind of bomb. A successful demolitions roll will reveal this to be a copy of a Mossad magnetic bomb used in the November 2010 assassination of Iranian nuclear scientist Majid Shahriari. In this incident, the magnetic bomb was attached to the car door of the target by motorcycle riding assailants and detonated seconds afterwards by remote. This particular device contains a shaped charge designed to defeat NIJ level IV armored door panels.</item>
        <item>A cattle prod, complete with a USB charger.</item>
        <item>A painstakingly constructed, fully-functional replica of an MA37 rifle from the popular Halo video game series. This includes a functional ammo counter and compass display on the top, and a magazine which holds 32 7.62mm NATO rounds. Anyone attempting to fire the weapon should take a small penalty, due to it\'s complete lack of iron sights.</item>
        <item>An Ulu, a traditional knife used by Inuit women for carving igloos. Suspiciously, this Ulu has a handle made from unidentifiable bone, and provides the user with a strange sense of warmth, as if a large polar bear had decided to cuddle...</item>
        <item>A well-wrought and polished set of brass knuckles. Inspecting them more closely, or attempting to wield them, reveals that they are very small in size, and the holes appear to be sized for very thin, dainty fingers. It will also be noted that they are unusually dented, as though used by someone with superhuman strength.</item>
        <item>A pair of Nazi jackboots with retractable blades hidden in the toes.</item>
        <item>A vintage USMC Ka-Bar jammed through a cinderblock with almost superhuman force; graffiti beside it refers to it as "The Sword in the Stone".\nGetting it out the obvious way would take 16+ Strength, and have a 25% of breaking the knife. However, it is a normal cinderblock, and it\'s certainly possible to chip it away around the knife if the PCs are so inclined.</item>
        <item>What first appears to be a normal kitchen knife upon closer examination has a a handle carved from black stone, and a blade made of pure silver. The edge of the blade seems slightly darker than it should, like it has been stained with blood, but analysis shows no trace of such.</item>
        <item>A police evidence bag containing a rather elaborate prison weapon. It consists of several spoon-handles sharpened down one end, affixed onto opposite sides of half an aluminum broom handle with rubber cement. It bears an extraordinary resemblance to the obsidian maquahuitls used by Aztec warriors.</item>
        <item>A palm sized wireless detonator used in military demolitions with a faded happy face sticker. No explosives seem to be present, but the detonator is armed.</item>
        <item>Several corked wine bottles filled with ash. The ash has a strange tint to it that never the same when you look at it again. When the ash is sprinkled on something inhuman it begins to slowly burn away even though there is no fire. It even works under water and in a vacuum</item>
        <item>A colorful bag with the text "Happy Birthday!" splashed across in big letters. Inside is a pair of brand new spiked brass knuckles.</item>
        <item>A large black umbrella. Along the spine of the umbrella (hidden by the fabric when closed) someone has fastened a crude 12 gauge single-barrel shotgun fired by a simple trigger on the handle. It is not loaded.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing a six-pointed japanese "throwing star" (Shuriken). The small weapon is made from stainless steel and the points are needle-sharp. A stylized etching of a many-headed Hydra adorns its sides, though the heads are very small and simplified, making the appendages more like tentacles.</item>
        <item>An extremely crude crossbow fabricated from a prison-style lunch tray, cut up soup and soda cans, and several tightey-whiteys\' worth of elastic waistbands. Three projectiles lay beside it, consisting of a sharpened toothbrush, a rubber-cement-hardened stick, and a small sliver of sheet metal. All three of them have been \'poisoned\' with human feces.</item>
        <item>A rusty steak knife. A note is wrapped around its plastic handle, and reads: "Ghost-slayer, brah". The blade is brittle, but while liable to snap if used for mundane purposes it can - and will - cut through spectral and Mythos creatures with ease. (Regular damage + automatic impale against ghosts and intangible beasties).</item>
        <item>A german zweihander, or two-handed sword. Has the word "SEELE" engraved on the blade. The weapon is large, and deals more damage than a normal sword, but requires some strength and skill to use.</item>
        <item>A strange improvised weapon consisting of a double-barreled 20-gauge zip gun made from pipe and plumbing parts, which has been welded lengthwise down a steel crowbar. The gun-barrels are fired by pulling back and releasing one (or both) nails, which are then driven into the shells\' primers by a chaotic entanglement of rubber bands and springs.\nIt should be noted that this is extremely unsafe, and in the case of a very bad roll, the nails could punch too far through and reach the powder. In this case, the nails could be propelled backwards into the firer.</item>
        <item>One Sykes-Fairbairn dagger, pitted as is from acid. This knife constantly emits IR radiation, viewable via common digital cameras as a glowing white light.</item>
        <item>An exact replica of a Photon Torpedo from Star Trek.The casing is hollow, and inside is enough plastic explosives to level a large building.</item>
        <item>An otherwise average-looking woodcutter\'s axe whose perfectly functional steel bit has been replaced with a row of vicious-looking shark teeth.\nNote that this is an entirely style over substance approach, which actually lowers the amount of damage it does and raises the risk of breaking it.</item>
        <item>A Bushmaster AR-15 with a laser/flashlight combination module mounted on a quad rail; it is currently loaded with a 100-round Beta C-Mag, and 2 30-round magazines sit next to it.\nFor some reason, someone has carefully and professionally welded a Smith &amp; Wesson Model 500 .50 caliber revolver to the spot where an under-barrel grenade launcher would be mounted.</item>
        <item>A sawed-off Browning Auto 5 shotgun, in the style commonly used in WWI trench warfare. The business end of the shotgun is darkly stained and corroded.</item>
        <item>A row of .32 ACP bullets stood to attention, each casing displaying the name of an investigator present. The paint is gummy to the touch.</item>
        <item>A bizarre piece of machinery that only vaguely resembles a shotgun; inscribed on the wide, rectangular receiver is "M150 DEMOLITION GUN". The weapon appears to be of falling-block design, but the bore is much larger than any weapon the investigators are familiar with. The weapon itself appears to be the only one of its kind, and no information on it can be found by any amount of research.\nNext to it are twenty massive shotgun shells, and an extremely plain booklet, which appears to be an operator\'s manual. It bears no manufacturer\'s markings, date, copyright information, and features the same text reprinted in English, German, Russian, and Chinese. Important excerpts:\n"M150 Demolition Rifle- for use against critical machinery including but not limited to: electrical transformers, communications equipment, storage tanks, railway switches, etc. Ammunition is 6 gauge proprietary shells, manufacturing specifications included in back. Avoid firing from shoulder, dislocation or other injury may occur."\nA handgun (of the Keeper\'s choice) in a ziplock bag. Written on the bag in permanent marker is the word \'Gun-ade\'. The handgun is in fact not a handgun, but an explosive device. When the trigger of the gun is pulled the device detonates, fragmenting and badly injuring whoever was unfortunate enough to have pulled the trigger.</item>
        <item>The barrel of an M2HB heavy machine gun. Just the barrel. Judging by the electrical tape wrapped around the muzzle end, and faint bloodstains all over, it was probably used as a club of some form. If somehow repatriated to an M2, minute warping of the barrel will cause catastrophic failure when fired.</item>
        <item>A bear-sprayer, but the pepper spray replaced by a butane can. A Zippo lighter has been duct-taped to the sprayer in front of the barrel.</item>
        <item>A small ziploc bag containing four .25 rounds. A small post-it note on it says: "Blessed!". [No special effects when used.]</item>
        <item>A Nintendo Entertainment System Power Glove peripheral. For all intents and purposes it looks completely ordinary, and is in excellent condition, but when worn the wearer will notice that the gloved hand indeed feels more powerful. Any melee attacks making use of the gloved hand will do an extra 1D3 damage.</item>
        <item>A large (3\' long) hook-like dagger made from sulphur-free black iron. The handle is quite long and weirdly shaped, as if meant for hands broader than a human\'s. Finely wrought sea-shells and small octopuses has been carved into the dagger\'s metal.</item>
        <item>A single shot 12 ga pistol. There are 3 12 ga shells labeled \'Minnows\' \'Cum\' and \'?\'</item>
        <item>A museum-grade replica of an ancient Roman "gladius" short-sword. It is made of modern steel, much better metal than the wrought-iron originals, and is very sharp on both edges.</item>
        <item>An exquisite jade box containing a dozen wickedly sharp acupunture needles. These are Tcho-Tcho matrimonial needles. Base attack is Punch, damage is 1D2+db, and automatically impales. A failed Luck roll from the victim results in 1d6 rounds of painful paralysis.</item>
        <item>A fully-functional, average CRT monitor, with the exception of a shaped charge tucked away into a safe area of its casing. When the monitor is turned on, the charge is triggered, sending a shower of steel nails (plus screen shards and monitor parts) directly into its user\'s face.</item>
        <item>What appears to be some form of improvised flamethrower; however, closer examination reveal that several refrigeration coils cover the entirety of the design. The presence of several tanks of liquid nitrogen nearby suggest this is some kind of hare-brained scheme to develop what could only be described as a \'freezethrower\'.\nNo rolls are necessary to pick up on the wanton stupidity of the idea, but the Keeper is free to suggest it just might possibly be stupid enough to work.</item>
        <item>A small lead linked box marked with radiation hazard stickers. Inside is a foam lining containing four (the lining has spaces for five) rounds of .308 Winchester (7.62mm NATO) ammunition with bullets made out of depleted uranium. There are no manufacturers marks on the rounds.</item>
        <item>A 9mm Lanchester submachine gun. Its arsenal markings indicate that it was manufactured in 1944 for the British Royal Navy and later sold out of military service. In the intervening years, someone covered the stock and brass magazine housing with fairly elaborate carved scroll work.\nThe weapon comes with one 50 round magazine containing 11 bullets. A thorough examination would determine that the bullets are compressed iron filings that have been silver plated.</item>
        <item>A Husqvarna 385XP gas-powered chainsaw with a 24" blade; 15lbs, low-vibration, quick-start. Despite being cleaned after its last use, a forensics exam of the chainsaw will reveal specks of human gore and blood. DNA from the samples will match 10 year old twins missing since 2001; the twins are on the NCMEC list.</item>
        <item>A super-soaker-type water gun, with a tank filled with gasoline and a BBQ grill lighter taped to the front of it, positioned so the stream of fuel will pass through the flame, making it a makeshift flamethrower\nPlease note, this is actually a terrible idea. Anyone attempting to use this device will be able to fire one shot, as per a normal flamethrower, at which point either the heat will melt the plastic and seal the nozzle of the water gun, or the fire will chase the fuel stream up into the gun and it will explode (Character using the flamethrower is entitled to a Luck roll to see what happens).</item>
        <item>A bottle of silly string with the label thermal dragon taped on it. If sprayed it spews military grade napalm that deals 2d10pluse 1d10 for 1d6 turns. If the cab is shot, stabbed, beaten, shaken too much or made fun of it will explode dealing 5d6 to every one in the room, house, wharehouse, or complex, if done outside it only burns what the keeper chouses to live or die.</item>
        <item>A damaged Colt AR-15 carbine fitted with a Trijicon ACOG sight; the weapon has been warped somehow, rendering it inoperative. The stock is covered with dried blood in an arterial spray pattern covers.</item>
        <item>A Nitrochemie/Rheinmetall DM72 ballistic artillery charge turned into a crude time-bomb by the addition of two AA batteries, an egg timer and some American Tape. Looks rough and dangerous.</item>
        <item>A chainsaw with a full tank of gas; for some reason, a powerful hand-held spotlight has been mounted on the side and its bulb has been replaced with a blacklight projector.</item>
        <item>An ammunition crate containing a large number of M590 Antipersonnel Canister rounds, for the M67 recoilless rifle. There is, of course, no recoilless rifle present, but an enterprising investigator might be able to figure out a way to rig them into a booby trap.</item>
        <item>Several poison-tipped needles hidden inside normal-looking cigarettes. The poison is highly heat-resistant, meaning that they can actually be smoked until the point is exposed, then stabbed into the target.</item>
        <item>A four inch steel ball covered with needle-sharp steel spikes, which appear to be coated with oil. The oil is in fact linseed oil, used as a rust preventative. There does not appear to be any way to safely handle it without damaging it.</item>
        <item>Five slightly rusty but still functional bolt action rifles with slings, filed off serial numbers, no ammunition and fixed bayonets. One of the rifle\'s slings is broken, and it bears four deep gouges in the grip. all the bayonets have dried green blood on them. An appropriate check reveals them to all be world war two era Chinese issue type 24s.</item>
        <item>A large piggy-bank containing a few pounds of plastic explosive.</item>
        <item>An assorted woman\'s purse full of shotgun shells with various words, such as "CONFETTI" and "DIMES" written on the sides with a marker.</item>
        <item>A sleek black pump-action weapon not recognizable as any commercial model or manufacturer. The only markings on it are the words "Assassin\'s Whisper" in small print, engraved on the receiver in Russian, English, Chinese, and Arabic.\nThe weapon is chambered in a caseless subsonic round comparable in performance to the Russian 9x39mm, which when combined with its integral suppressor makes it surprisingly quiet, in addition in the lack of ejected casing (also obviously giving the advantage of leaving no spent shells) and the manually-cycled nature of the weapon. Its tubular magazine holds six rounds, loaded one at a time, and it has rails for optics, though none are attached at the moment. In addition to the six in the chamber, there are twenty-four rounds loose on the floor next to it; the high-tech and proprietary nature of the ammunition means that finding more will probably be impossible.</item>
        <item>.36 caliber black powder revolver. It is fully loaded. It\'s grips are wooden and ornate, but well worn. The metal components have some rust, but the weapon is functioning perfectly. The name \'Eliza\' is carved into the grips. If the weapon is examined, it can be determined that the gun is a Remington Model 1858, made in 1861.</item>
        <item>A chest-high wooden shipping crate. Any mention of the crate\'s contents have been wiped out with black paint, but it shows several shipping and custom labels from countries in South and Central America, Eastern Europe, Asia, and most recently, one to location of the Green Box, in care of a "Mr. Green".\nOpening the crate requires a prybar or similar tool, or a STR check. Inside is a GE M134 Minigun, modified to be carried by a single person, with a rear pistol grip trigger, and the hand-guard from an M60 mounted under the barrels. On the grip is the sharkmouth art common to nose art on old warplanes, and the word "Tyrannosaurus" in bright red paint. The Minigun requires minimum 16 STR and 16 SIZ to wield by one person. The crate also contains a special backpack loaded with a 550 round ammo case, which is already hooked up to the minigun, and a spare case which can be placed in the backpack when the first is expended. The backpack also is rigged to hold the power supply for the Minigun, a Car Battery.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing three .45 rounds. The center of the bullets seems to have been drilled out and replaced by tiny (6mm long, 4mm diameter) cylinders of translucent emerald-green jade.</item>
        <item>A 9-inch knife, made from a single piece of highly-polished steel. The entire thing is covered in hierolyphs from the Old Kingdom of Egypt. They\'re just gibberish if anyone tries to translate them; they don\'t mean anything. The knife itself is sharp as sin and very ergonomic.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a leather bullwhip. Someone has carefully fastened pieces of razorblades to the tip. It is moderately stained with dried blood.</item>
        <item>A German executioner\'s sword, c.1760, replete with stylised gothic German Biblical inscriptions. The pommel is made of what appears to be a detachable black, magnetic stone.</item>
        <item>A burlap sack that, when opened, reveals sawed-off 12 gauge shotgun in vacuum-sealed plastic bag. The barrels, in an over/under configuration, have been filed down to within two inches of the handguard, and have become so worn that they have apparently begun to separate. To remedy this, the previous owner wrapped them with chicken wire and yellow electrical tape. The stock has been hacked off completely save for the grip, and the wood has dulled to a dark brown. The receiver, however, appears to be in good working shape, its bright nickel finish still intact. There are two triggers, one for each barrel. A makeshift leather sling runs from the front of the handguard to the butt of the grip.</item>
        <item>Also tied to the butt of the grip is what appears to be an evidence tag that is filled out in Cyrillic letters. If anyone has the appropriate knowledge (Ukrainian language), they find it reads: "Lviv Police Department - Evidence Log #7600034-21 - TOZ-34 shotgun confiscated from residence of A. Onoprienko in Zhitomirskaya by Patrolman V. Kensalo - positively linked to murders in Braktovichi"</item>
        <item>A large laundry bag containing vietnam era US Air Force uniforms and a Colt Commando assault rifle, fully loaded. The weapon has a long shoulder strap with five leather loops for magazines. Three of these loops are occupied with loaded magazines, one contains an empty magazine and the final loop is unoccupied. The Rifle has an inscription crudely scratched onto the side. "And what rough beast, its hour come round at last,</item>
        <item>Slouches towards Bethlehem to be born?"</item>
        <item>A simple six-chamber revolver, still fully loaded. Each bullet is inscribed with the name of someone that the person who finds it once knew.</item>
        <item>A large syringe containing a faintly luminescent and sparkly blue liquid. Written on the side of the syringe with a felt-tip pen are the words "SHOGGOTH POISON." Note to Keeper: it has no actual effect on shoggoths.</item>
        <item>A Uzi msg that is modeled after a human head breathing fire, the gun has an inscription on its grip reading in manderen and in English "Thai spicy" the rounds fired from the gun have a fire quality and the weirder tastes the sweetest burning pain in there mouth that can only be described as Thai spicy. The gun dose 1d10+1d2(Fire damage)</item>
        <item>A sizable pick-like weapon, which a History roll will identify as a Lucerne hammer. It is clearly of modern but capable design, gleams in the light, and when lifted it is far heavier than it has any right to be. From there, an appropriate roll will determine it is apparently made from a platinum alloy (and is therefore worth a fortune in raw metal alone).</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a three-foot long primitive blowgun made from bamboo, and three wooden darts. The tips of the darts are covered in a red-brown paste. [Anyone damaged by a dart must make a CON vs. 16 roll after 1d10 rounds. Success means the victim suffers from slight drowsiness and some disturbing audial and visual hallucination. Lose 0/1d4 SAN. A failure on the CON roll means the victim is unconcious for 1d10 minutes and experience horrifying visions. Lose 1d6/1d20 SAN.]</item>
        <item>A hand-loaded 12 gauge shotgun shell. It is filled with iron-scrapings and rock salt.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a regular radio from the late 80\'s. The inside has been reworked to allow a MAC-10 to fit inside of it. Holes have been cut to allow the shooter to reach the trigger and the bullets to exit the housing.</item>
        <item>A large, funnel-shaped metal device that, upon further inspection, is discovered to be filled with explosives. The wide end of the funnel is magnetized, and examination shows the explosives make a shaped charge.\nThe device is actually a hafthohlladung, a WWII-era German anti-tank weapon intended to be magnetically attached to the hull of a tank. Keeper\'s discretion as to whether this fifty-year-old-plus explosive still works, but it must be attached at point-blank range, and is only viable against metallic targets due to the magnets.</item>
        <item>A mannequin dressed in jeans, a leather jacket and a gasmask leans against the far wall of the green box. Examining it will reveal it\'s stuffed full of semtex and wired to a detonator setup taken from a model rocket kit on a long wire.</item>
        <item>A garish, brightly-colored mass of plastic, which upon closer inspection turns out to be a pipe bomb with dozens of cheap pocket lighters glued to the outside. While this will probably reduce its blasting capability somewhat, it will most certainly start a small fire wherever it is detonated.</item>
        <item>One replica Captain America shield. It is made of high grade aluminum and measures 27" in diameter. It is covered in a red, white and blue lacquer finish and has leather carrying straps attached to the back. It has two dents on the front and several smears of yellow blood along it\'s surface.</item>
        <item>A thick leatherbound book. Only the first 20 pages can be opened, the rest have been meticulously glued together. One third of the glued pages have been cut away and changed for several 1mm thick steel plates, making the book quite heavy and very hard. In capable hands it is probably quite useful for bashing in heads or breaking limbs.</item>
        <item>A cast iron swastika, around a foot across. The ends of each arm have been sharpened into a needle point, and are coated in (dried, possibly ineffective) curare poison.</item>
        <item>A broken katana, and sheath. It\'s of poor quality, and has phosphorescent paint along the entire length of the blade. UV scans indicate a strange ichor along the edge.</item>
        <item>A customized Tippman A-5 paintball gun. Inside the canister are 100 paint balls. Inside the paintballs are a highly acidic solution, that will eat away organic materials such as wood or flesh.</item>
        <item>A slightly worn but lovingly maintained old Colt Python .357 Magnum revolver with two speedloaders and a partial box of ammunition. The ammunition has silver bullets.</item>
        <item>Agents searching the Green Box happen upon a rather large shoulder slung golf bag. However instead of a set of clubs in the bag they find, in a rather curious parody of what is typically in a golf bag, many different sizes and types of swords and knives. The arms range from a genuine Marine K-Bar to a huge German Zwihander (Keepers are free to customize the exact contents as desired). Investigating the arms confirms that all are of excellent quality, made by professional sword and knife makers. No cheap knockoffs here.\nA note attached to the bag states:\n"I thought I would loan my spare bag to those in need. Please treat the blades with respect. Don\'t willfully damage them, don\'t mistreat them, and don\'t sell them. You may keep them as long as needed. However, please return them clean, sharp, and intact to this Green Box at the end of your mission, so the next group of agents my use them. Failure to do so will result in me tracking you down and retrieving my property by any and all means. -R. A. Vandros"</item>
        <item>A handmade wooden box containing a French MAT-49 submachine gun rechambered in 7.62x25mm. The weapon comes with two 32 round magazines one empty, one loaded with 30 rounds. The box also has US capture documentation from Vietnam dated late 1967. Any reference to the serviceman who brought back the weapon has been cut out of the documents with a knife.</item>
        <item>A crude iron trident, about 6\' long, covered with stylized carvings of squids, sea-horses and clams. It is very heavy and unwieldy unless used with a strength of 16 or more. The iron in the weapon has a particularly low amount of sulphur in it, making it very resistant to corrosion.</item>
        <item>An incredibly primitive axe made from knapped flint, reeds, and a stick, quite literally what one would expect to see a cave-man use. However, it is clearly extremely new (although not brand new, since the reed lashings are beginning to rot). Adding to the bizarreness is the fact that the shoebox it rests on contains several plaster casts of footprints that quite obviously look like they would be left by Bigfoot.</item>
        <item>A wooden art supply case with an easel attached to the top.\Further inspection shows a Claymore anti-personnel directional mine within the box, aimed at the back of the box, connected to a proximity sensor. There is a switch near the box handle to arm the device, and instructions that the user has 10 seconds to get out of range before it\'s armed.</item>
        <item>An inch-thick iron rod, three feet long, which has had one end carefully ground into a needle-sharp point. Along the length of the rod twisting arabic script has been etched into it. It is old arabic, but a translation would show it to be the An-Nisa verse 78 from the Quran: "Wheresoever you may be, death will overtake you even if you are in fortresses built up strong and high!".</item>
        <item>A single tranquilizer dart for a veterinarian\'s tranquilizer gun. It is filled with an alcohol-solution of Aconitum Vulparia ("Wolfsbane") and Silver-Nitrate.</item>
        <item>15 feet of Detcord, tied in a perfect noose.</item>
        <item>This is an old, worn, slightly battered-looking M1911A1 "Government Model" .45 ACP pistol with a single magazine. The front sight has been removed and replaced with a small brass crucifix, soldered in place.</item>
        <item>You find a pair of extremely large and old-fashioned revolvers that don\'t appear to be any known model. The metal is very unusual, and a character with any smithing knowledge will see that every part of the guns, from the internal mechanisms to the well-worn sandalwood grips, was entirely hand made. The weapons look to be very old, but extremely well-cared for, no sign of rust is upon them. Strangely for something so finely crafted, there is no makers mark anywhere in evidence, nor any sign of where they may have originated. The guns are loaded with seven rounds between them, which also appear to have been hand made, though without the same level of skill.\nThe bullets that come with the gun appear to be a crude copy of .45 winchester, though when the machine-made bullets are loaded and fired, it just doesn\'t feel as powerful or satisfying.</item>
        <item>An "Ivar\'s Seafood" cardboard carry away food container which holds a single Glock 22 pistol. A shell casing is jammed in the ejection port of the weapon. The casing has the letter "O" scratched onto its exposed side. The magazine is in the weapon and the safety is off. If examined the fifteen round magazine currently contains 10 rounds, each with a letter scratched into its case: B, R, A, N, C, H, I, A, T, and A. A successful Zoology check will bring to mind the term "abranchiate". A result under 20% of the spell (an "impale") brings up the term "zeugobranchiata", which refers to abalone and related species.</item>
        <item>A gun display case like one would find in a private home. An evidence tag on it indicates it was seized by the ATF in the not-to-distance past. Stuck to the the top of the case, with tape, is a yellowing memo that says "For the love of God, don\'t loose these! They have the powdered bones of John Moses Browning in the grips." Inside the case are four elegantly crafted and slightly unique Colt M1911 pistols. There is space for a fifth, but it is clearly missing.</item>
        <item>An antique pocket-watch that conceals a small spring-loaded blade. Pressing an innocent looking button on the side sends the blade flying outwards a considerable distance. The blade can be replaced to fire again, though this process is lengthy and complicated. All the numbers on the watch face read "12"</item>
        <item>One 8mm Nambu pistol with magazine, loaded. It appears brand new in spite of the fact this make and model haven\'t been made since Japan lost WWII. If viewed under a black light, the serial number and other makers marks glow white.</item>
        <item>A WW2 era Thompson sub-machine gun, still in excellent condition. Scrimshawed into the metal is The Lords Prayer, in French.</item>
        <item>This heavy steel ammo can contains one hundred and seventy-five rounds of 12 gauge ammunition loaded in dull olive drab plastic cartridges. Each case has "SCMITR" and "AAI INC" printed on its side in black ink, and the cartridges are headstamped "AAI" and "12 GAUGE" A note inside the can says "Experimental, from the 1970s"\nOpening up a cartridge will reveal that each is loaded with a stack of nasty-looking razor-edged stamped steel darts in a plastic sleeve. For game purposes, a shotgun loaded with this ammo will have armor piercing capabilities vs. modern soft body armor and do double damage in living tissue, as well as having 50% greater effective range--but still won\'t affect Mythos creatures that are immune to mundane weaponry.</item>
        <item>A m1 grand with 3 spare clips and a bayonet. The rifle has the name "Sonya" etched into the barrel it also has 1 in\' long leather strings hanging from the trigger guard, barrel and stock each barring a tooth, horn or other trophy,after closer inspection and a significant mythos roll revivals that the trophies are from the rifles previous kills ranging from deep ones to ghouls to greys. For each new kill a new trophy appears on the rifle, the trophys can\'t be taken or destroyed.</item>
        <item>A worn Sturmgewehr 44 with 3 full 30 round magazines of 7.92x33 ammmunition. Each cartridge has a Celtic cross etched on the case; the stock of the weapon has a Celtic knot engraved on each side. The weapon functions normally unless the firer is of Irish ancestry, in which case his accuracy is increased by 10%, rounded up.</item>
        <item>Concealed within an oil-stained "Crown Royal" bag, a floppy disk sits besides a FN Barracuda revolver. The revolver comes alongside three interchangeable cylinders, allowing the gun to chamber either 9mm, .38, or .357 bullets. However, the firing pin has been shortened ever so slightly, as to prevent the weapon from ever firing properly. Finding a replacement pin is difficult, but possible, if the Keeper is willing. The floppy disk contains a text file, explaining that the weapon was sabotaged for an operation performed by B-cell back in the mid 80\'s, and should not be used for combat.</item>
        <item>An old scratched-to-hell Soviet KS-23 4-Bore shotgun. There is one very large shell in the chamber with "БАРРИКАДА" written on its side.</item>
        <item>An improvised stun-staff, consisting of a long wooden shaft with a stun-gun duct-taped onto it. The leads of the stun-gun have been extended down the length of the staff (excluding the areas gripped by the wielder) by loosely coiled copper wire, and most of the rod\'s surface is therefore electrified when the stun-gun is switched on.\nThis is obviously a horrible idea, and a careless user is more likely to electrocute himself than his or her target.</item>
        <item>A somewhat monstrous version of an H&amp;K MP5, half cobbled together and half built from the ground up by a skilled gunsmith who really, REALLY wanted a sub-machine gun chambered in .50AE. Damage is 1d10+1d6+3, but the recoil is almost comically absurd, the magazine capacity is only 14, and the weapon will fail catastrophically (explosively) on a roll of 94 or above due to the huge pressures involved.</item>
        <item>A box of fifty NATO-spec 9mm cartridges. Close examination reveals that someone has been trying to engrave an Elder Sign into the tip of each bullet\'s jacket with some kind of tool. Closer examination, perhaps with a jeweler\'s loupe and a successful Mythos roll, will reveal that whoever it was didn\'t do it quite right.</item>
        <item>A well-maintained, seemingly new Red Army Pulemyot Maxima PM1910 machine gun on a wheeled Sokolov mount with a modified gunner shield welded with extra steel plates. The gun and its mount mass at 90 kilos. It\'s chambered for 7.62x54mm Soviet rounds ("polar bear killers.") The gunner shield has odd, irregular acid pitting, as well as three 2cm holes burned through cleanly with laser precison.</item>
        <item>A slingshot carved from the bones of a very large animal (an African elephant, if someone figures it out). Its ammunition resembles some sort of homemade paintball, but when cracked open the balls reveal a live poisonous spider. It\'s unclear how the spiders survived inside, since they seem to have been inside the Green Box for weeks, if not months.</item>
        <item>An Indian-made Zittara bullpup assault rifle. It chambers Indian 5.56x30mm INSAS rounds, and only two such half empty magazines are present. There are traces of sandalwood paste, vermillion, and some kind of ash on the stock and the barrel. Forensic examination of the ash reveals it to be cremated human remains.</item>
        <item>A knife-shaped carving of ivory, approximately 8 inches long, with no handle or wrapping. Notes indicate it was recovered during an op, but are very evasive about where or when.</item>
        <item>What appears to initially be a crate of flash-bang grenades. However, when used, any light source within ten meters is extinguished.</item>
        <item>Inside a flimsy plastic bag is an extremely crude zip gun made from two pieces of plumbing pipe, a rusty screw fastened into a metal end cap, and a single 9mm bullet. Dried blood covers end of the thinner pipe. Known as a "Slap Gun", it is fired by slamming the smaller pipe holding the cartridge into the larger pipe with the nail. An aura of despair radiates from the thing, as if it had absorbed the feelings of its many suicidal owners. This particular device was found in the hands of a homeless man, later identified as the missing agent DWYER.</item>
        <item>Twelve M84 "flashbang" grenades stuffed in a US Postal Service satchel with a piece of paper describing their "Faye-Werewolf Repellant" qualities. Each grenade has been professionaly stuffed full of a mixture of silver and iron.</item>
        <item>A wet floor sign, of the folding triangular-pyramid design (rather like a giant d4). When picked up, it is far heavier than it should be, and turning it over reveals a homemade explosive device which appropriate rolls will determine to be a claymore-style directional mine. A cell phone is clearly wired into the setup, with "878-9292 = BOOM" scrawled beside it in Sharpie.</item>
        <item>A pistol that seems to be a standard Colt 1911A1 .45 Pistol. The thing is once used it actually fires a small .32 caliber round at the user from a hidden barrel.</item>
        <item>An ancient LeMat Revolver chambered for .44 caliber lead balls. It is found in a small wooden box lined with velvet. It has clearly been very well cleaned and cared for, with no obvious sign of rust. On one side of the barrel is engraved an image of the Confederate flag.</item>
        <item>No powder or shot is in evidence, and it does not look like this gun has been fired in a very long time.</item>
        <item>None of the chambers are loaded.</item>
        <item>A small ziploc bag containing a 9mm round where the bullet appears to be made from 18ct gold.</item>
        <item>A dilapidated leather briefcase containing a single-shot break action 12-gauge sawed down to a length of ten inches, the stock likewise sawed off. One round of standard 00 Buck is chambered, with no spare rounds in the briefcase. A sealed letter with no outside markings inside. If investigated, the note within reads "Isaac, I couldn\'t go through with it. Please forgive me."</item>
        <item>A single fragmentation grenade. It has been wrapped with chicken wire, into which have been wedged dozens of shark teeth. Every one points outwards, making the grenade extremely awkward to handle.</item>
        <item>A small, undecorated wooden jewelry-box containing what appear to be nine unsharpened yellow-wood No. 2 pencils, manufactured by "D&amp;G Industries". If sharpened down, though, a carbon-steel stabbing blade is revealed immediately below the first layer of wood, making the pencil into an assassin\'s tool similar to an ice-pick. Upon the box has been scrawled "smuggle in blunt, grind down sharp. Nasty surprise inside."</item>
        <item>A cracked glass syringe, with the remains of a rust-coloured liquid solidified in the base of it.</item>
        <item>A flashbang grenade and a fragmentation grenade, lashed together with duct tape for some reason. The two pins have been strung together with dog-tag chain, meaning that if one is pulled then the other will follow.</item>
        <item>An antique single shot Federal Gas Riot Gun loaded with a tear gas round. The wood stock is scratched in a way that suggests it was once used to bludgeon someone\'s head in. When the gun is fired, the faint sound of a crowd screaming can be heard seemingly from nowhere.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing an unopened Mars chocolate bar and a handwritten note: "Warning! Poisoned with cyanide!". A tiny hole, as from a syringe can be found in the packaging. The chocolate bar expired a year ago.</item>
        <item>A wooden box containing five plastic tubes for M720 60mm mortar rounds. These are packed with a mix of high explosive and white phosphorus known as \'shake-n-bake\'. When detonated, the white phosphorus particles will produce a thick,toxic smoke, start fires, and burn through clothing, flesh, and bone until deprived of oxygen. The particles are themselves toxic and will re-ignite if exposed to atmosphere. The pain and suffering caused is almost unimaginable, and use of this type of round against civilians is considered a war crime. Three of the tubes are empty.</item>
        <item>A large, aluminum brief case with a keypad lock on it. There is a small readout to display digits which says ENTER, indicating it wants to set a new key.Inside the case is a complex device which appears to be lead shielded and has a radiation hazard symbol on it, along with two locks built into the device, a second keypad and an actual key lock. Anyone who knows something about physics or explosives can guess this is a tactical "suitcase" nuke. While too small to generate much long-term fallout, it has enough force to level a city block or so.After examining it for a time, the agents will realize that there are still handcuffs attached to the handle. And to a hand. 0/1 SAN. Inside the hand still attached to the cuffs is a key, and a 5-digit password written on the palm. No handcuff key is present, and it will require a Locksmith roll to remove them.</item>
        <item>A baseball bat, studded with human teeth in two rows located 180 degrees from one another. It looks very similar to the Aztec obsidian-studded macuahuitl, albeit...with human teeth.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a polo mallet, its head spattered with blood. Anyone familiar with the sport will note that the head is far heavier than it should be, and the ergonomics of the mallet seem to be more conducive to a golf swing than horseback polo.\nThe mallet is painted jet-black, but somebody has inlaid in gold leaf the word "JAWBREAKER" lengthwise down the handle.</item>
        <item>A STHIL 440 Magnum chain saw with a full tank of fuel mix, a filled oil reserve, and ten bottles of both mix and oil. On the bar of the saw there are 34 tally marks and the words "Papulu protect you".</item>
        <item>Colt Super Match - Factory nickel finish, fixed sights and fitted with factory mother of pearl grips.\nOne (1) box of .45 ammo. One of the rounds has the investigator\'s name carved on it.</item>
        <item>A rather thick metal ruler; handling it may make the investigator think it is hollow. Careful inspection reveals a flexible seam around the 9" mark and a well hidden bullet-sized plug at the 1" side which conceals a gun barrel.\nIn reality it is a single-shot .32 caliber hidden gun, fired by sharply bending the rear part to the left or right. As such its range is pathetic and it is essentially one-use-only.</item>
        <item>A tesla coil hooked up to a set of batteries. It has been setup to be remotely triggered. Why someone would go through this much trouble to make a remote activated one is unclear.</item>
        <item>A Tokarev TT-33 pistol spray-painted dayglo orange. A ballistics trace will reveal that it is the weapon used in two unsolved (non-fatal) shootings in Ohio.</item>
        <item>A Vietnam-era USMC M2A1-7 flamethrower, perfectly maintained. There are three extra sets of fully-charged cylinders. A three-ring binder contains a photocopy of the official instruction manual, quick-use notes, and details for cleaning, maintaining, restocking and long-term storage of the unit. There are eight notches scratched into the side of the firing trigger.</item>
        <item>A 17th century Javanese Kris dagger (1d4+1 damage) with a weird symbol etched into the blade.</item>
        <item>A homemade particle cannon, cobbled together from the magnetron of a microwave, three feet of galvanized steel tubing, and about one hundred yards\' worth of coiled copper wire. It is powered by a twenty-foot extension cord. A Post-It note is attached, reading:</item>
        <item>"Prototype Mk. IV</item>
        <item>note - hopefully we\'ve worked out the kinks this time,</item>
        <item>as my fingernails are beginning to fall off.</item>
        <item>- M.B."</item>
        <item>A battered and somewhat rusty, but very functional 12 gauge double-barrel shotgun with its barrels cut down to 10" or so. There is also a carton containing nine of the original twenty-five old all-brass 12 gauge shotgun shells. Each shell has been loaded with a stack of nine silver dimes instead of lead pellets.</item>
        <item>A rack of six percussion-cap muskets. They areidentifiable with proper rolls as Pattern 1853 Enfield rifled muskets, of the type imported en masse by the Confederacy during the American Civil War. They all have bayonets fixed, and are in remarkable condition. Tags affixed to the trigger guard of each indicate they were (at one point) in the collection of the Smithsonian.\nPowder and shot are included, but closer examination indicate them to be very recent, not from the Civil War as one might expect.</item>
        <item>A standard military issue footlocker with most of the green paint intact. Picking the lock reveals a Mega Man cosplay costume sized for a teenager. The costume was skillfully made - the jumpsuit and boots were hand-sewn and the accessories were carefully sculpted out of rigid foam, plastic sheet, and fibreboard. Upon closer examination, the jumpsuit has a suicide vest built around four kilograms of C4 incorporated into it. The gun-gauntlet has another kilo of C4 and two boxes of roofing nails packed into it. The arming and detonation buttons are attached with hot glue to the inside of the gauntlet, and repurposed IDE ribbon cable connects the detonators to a fist-sized battery pack built into the belt buckle.</item>
        <item>A box of shotgun shells that have been opened and repacked. Closer examination shows that the shot of each shell has been replaced with hand-made iron nails, the sort of kitsch you\'d buy at a rennfaire.</item>
        <item>A metal San Francisco Police Department riot shield. A large elder sign is etched on the front.</item>
        <item>A small mirror with a stand for sitting on a dresser; however, a sticky note on the back indicates that a small but still deadly knife has been concealed between the mirror glass and the frame. It is described as perfect for smuggling a weapon into a hotel or residence, and accessing the knife is as simple as smashing the mirror, though the note does make a weak joke about bad luck at the end.</item>
        <item>A large children\'s teddy bear from Build-A-Bear at the local mall. One of the bear\'s eyes has been loosened and attached with a thin wire to the pin of an antipersonnel fragementation grenade hidden inside the bear along with the stuffing.</item>
        <item>Worn but well-maintained Colt Peacemaker revolver in .44-40 caliber. Serial number has been removed but a successful ARMORER roll will tell the player that it was made between 1878 and 1900, and remains in perfect mechanical condition. Box also contains an equally old leather gunbelt and quick-draw holster, with shell loops for fifty cartridges. About twenty cartridges are present. All are loaded with silver bullets, and each bullet has an Elder Sign on its point.</item>
        <item>17 12-gauge shells - loaded with sea salt, silver, and cold iron.</item>
        <item>A Star Trek Klingon Bat\'Leth replica, in stainless-steel and with a razor-sharp edge.</item>
        <item>A nondescript 12-gauge, double-barreled shotgun, with the stock and barrels amaturely cut-down with a hacksaw. The gun is loaded, one barrel with buckshot, the other with a custom hand-loaded shell containing rocksalt.</item>
        <item>A home-made device consisting of about 25 lbs of ammonium nitrate crystals in a plastic tub, with an epoxy-sealed 1 gallon milk jug (rigged with a small impact detonator) filled with water. (In effect this is a very large "instant cold" pack).</item>
        <item>A set of three glass bottles with standard corrosive warning labels on them. They are identical in use to Molotov cocktails, but with a powerful acid substituted for the incendiary compound.</item>
        <item>An old, battle-worn Dragunov SVD rifle that has definitely seen better days. A close inspection of the weapon reveals many tally marks and writing in several different languages carved into the pockmarked wood furniture. When picked up, the stock and furniture seem to mold to your body almost as if they were made out of putty rather than wood and you feel almos as if you\'ve been using weapon forever.</item>
        <item>A taxidermied baboon, the animal has been dressed up in a tuxedo and posed on its hind legs holding a silver tray in its paws. Sitting on the tray is a loaded colt 1911 with a spare magazine full of hollow points</item>
        <item>A machete (pranga) of African manufacture. A crude representation of a sinuous snake with a single wing has been etched into the blade.</item>
        <item>A throwing hatchet that appears to be crudely home-made.</item>
        <item>An iron mace, probably 18th century, of Indian manufacture. Ornamentation depicts various gods in pitched battle.</item>
        <item>A oddly shaped long sword, the length of a man\'s height, the end is plat as opposed to being pointed, and yet light and easy to weld. However, swinging the sword makes it feel "heavier".\nA attached tag on the hilt: "Terminius Est, Provenience South America (?), unknown date. Metal unidentified, make unknown."\nWhile sharp, the size and luster of the weapon would make it difficult to carry openly, and would no doubt bring unwanted attention, if not attention of the local authorities.</item>
        <item>A Russian ADS amphibious-use rifle, with a powerful waterproof flashlight mounted below the muzzle; there are one hundred eighty rounds of ammunition for it and three magazines. A note in the box reads, "For you-know-whats...try to conserve ammo, though, it\'s hard to find and you don\'t know how many men had to die for us to get this."</item>
        <item>A crate of 7.62X39mm rounds with Chinese markings on the outside. A note on the outside reads in French, "One out of every twenty rounds in this container is booby-trapped with a highly explosive powder load powerful enough to rupture a Kalashnikov type rifle. There is no discernable difference between any cartridges in the quantity."</item>
        <item>An exceedingly bizarre weapon, which more resembles a straight-handled drawknife than a sword. It consists of a double-edged blade, but instead of one hilt and one point, it has a hilt on both ends. They are elaborately engraved in classical Roman style, and each bears one of the two faces of the god Janus looking in opposite directions. Even more strangely, the weapon (although seemingly authentic) doesn\'t display a single day\'s worth of rust or tarnish.</item>
        <item>What appears to be an X-Box. However the internal mechanism has been reworked into what amounts to a claymore anti-personnel mine. To arm it you simply plug it in. It will detonate if the target pushes the power button on the console or uses a controller to start it. Made for a mission that never came off.</item>
        <item>It appears Delta Green somehow came into possession of one of the few XM8 prototype rifles made for the Army; it lies in an opened shipping crate cradled by packing peanuts, as well as twelve magazines fitting it (since it doesn\'t accept normal STANAG magazines).\nA note rests on top of the weapon:\n"Remember, there are NO SPARE PARTS for this thing. At all. So don\'t break it, ok?"</item>
        <item>A battery-powered electric flyswatter, built into a pink plastic frame resembling a 1/2 scale tennis racket. The device inexplicably delivers a single jolt equivalent to that of a police taser before the batteries melt. Afterward, it never functions again.</item>
        <item>Two dozen strange-looking hand-loaded twelve gauge shells. Upon inspection, it appears the first dozen are heavily modified Taser X-REP shells tweaked to deliver a highly lethal shock, and the second dozen are filled with homemade thermite, functioning like a more lethal version of the Dragon\'s Breath novelty round.\nTaped to the box is a note reading "FOR WHEN BULLETS DON\'T WORK". Below, a series of notes left by previous visitors form a debate on whether or not to include silver bullets.</item>
        <item>What appears on exterior to be a Yugoslavian-made Zastava M70 assault rifle, a high quality copy of the AKM; however, its interior is stripped and packed with plastic explosives, wired to a detonator activated by pulling the trigger. It has been reasonably well hidden, it will take actually disassembly to discover its secret, though anyone experienced with Kalashnikovs will note the rifle is somewhat oddly weighted compared to a normal rifle.</item>
        <item>A worn hickory golf club, of the style used in the 1890s. The clubhead is cracked and stained with dried blood; no amount of bleaching, cleaning, varnishing, painting, etc. is able to remove the stains. Despite appearances it is an effective melee weapon, and never breaks, nor can the user be disarmed of it while conscious.</item>
        <item>A flintlock rifle in excellent condition. This impressive rifle of the Revolutionary War era measures 72 inches in overall length, with the wood stock measuring 55 inches of the total. The rifle is stamped St. Etienne on the lock plate. along the smoothbore rifle\'s barrel is the following inscription, in facny French longhand,"beni dans l\'Avignon, dans le palais des papes" (translation: blessed in Avignon, the palace of the popes.) The front half of the rifle is entirely covered with dried blood. It is not loaded, though there is a pouch with 20 balls of shot, an equal number of cloth patches for the shot, and a very large horn of dry, usable powder. Both the horn and pouch lay on the ground near the rifle.</item>
        <item>You see what appears to be a one meter section of an ordinary concrete curb, such as can be found on the side of any nearby street. Turning it around, you notice that it is an IED; several sections have been hollowed out and replaced with high explosives, a detonator, and a circuit board attached to a cheap mobile phone. A yellow note attached to the phone reads "For a good time, call 555-BOOM (555-2662)! Should splatter anything within 10 meters. Have fun".</item>
        <item>A medieval-style longsword which appears shiny and brand new. It turns out the metal of the blade is composed of pure Rubidium, which explodes on contact with water.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>