<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_weird_artifacts">
        <item>A home exorcism kit (King James Bible, holy water in a bottle, candle, bell, silver-plated knife, duct-tape) in a satchel.</item>
        <item>Three dozen flat-packed Amazon.com boxes, all addressed to a fishing supplies store in Branford, Connecticut. Each box contains a receipt for the purchase of a rare occult or Mythos tome. The buyer of the books, easily tracked down by her name or credit card details, is meant to be under Delta Green surveillance but is, due to a bizarre set of unfortunate and surprisingly violent circumstances, currently under the radar. A-Cell will want the agents to make sure this doesn\'t happen again...</item>
        <item>A small locked safe. Contains a small piece of foul-smelling black paper, if anyone manages to get it open.</item>
        <item>Sixteen party balloons neatly entwined into a large Elder Sign. It bobs eerily by the ceiling in the corner of the Green Box, but is otherwise entirely harmless.</item>
        <item>An antique full-length mirror dating from the 1850s. It\'s hardwood frame - turned black from the grime of many decades - is carved with scenes from the stories of Edgar Allan Poe. The tomb broken open in "Berenice" to reveal the corpse of a woman with all of her teeth pulled out; "The House of Usher" with it\'s eye-like windows and the crack running down one wall; "The Pit and the Pendulum"; "The Tell-tale Heart" and others. The silver-backed mirror itself is somewhat murky with veins of black threaded through it where the coating has peeled away but it is still quite reflective.</item>
        <item>Seven 55-gallon drums are on a wooden pallet in the back of the Green Box. Two are empty, the remaining five have been crudely sealed with duct tape and roofing tar and a sheet of plywood has been laid on top of them. "Human Waste Disposal! Don\'t Open!" has been spray-painted across the sheet.</item>
        <item>An uninflated sex doll that if inflated is revealed to resemble one of the Agents.</item>
        <item>A large glass jar containing the severed head, spinal cord and nervous system of a middle-aged balding man. Examination indicates very little tissue decay, although the head and nervous system are covered in a film of thin grey slime. Evident on the man\'s face is a withered but still thickly luxurious moustache. Closer inspection suggests signs of frostbite on his face.\nAttached to the outside of the jar is a small piece of paper, bearing the words "We miss you, Starkie". On the other side is written "Antarctica, 1933".</item>
        <item>A small wooden box containing a german WWII Iron Cross 1st Class.</item>
        <item>A United Nations peacekeeper helmet, bearing the initials and the distinctive light-blue color scheme. About a quarter of it is missing, and the helmet has a bizarrely porous feel to it, as though it were pumice. Parts of it come off at the touch and it leaves a layer of dust wherever it is placed.</item>
        <item>One-hundred dried-out human scalps wrapped in a Union Jack flag.</item>
        <item>A collection of cardboard boxes stuck together and drawn on with thick, black marker pen to create a dozen "desktop computers". They\'ve been networked with lengths of twine.</item>
        <item>A mummified human hand held upright by a brass tripod. Each finger is tipped by a small candle.</item>
        <item>A painted portrait in an elaborate wooden frame. It must be at least a few centuries old. Unsigned, probably the work of a clever amateur. The subject is a man, sitting. His face is thin, with narrow eyes and an unusually red mouth who looks to be near 40 when the portrait was painted. He wears rich clothes of red velvet and silk and the gold chain and square medal of an insigna hang aound his neck. An hourglass held horizontally so as the prevent the flow of sand from one end to the other is held in his right hand, and his left rests upon an open book, on one page of which some writing is discernable. On closer inspection of the painting, the insigna on the medal around the man\'s neck is a clock face without hands. And the writing in the book is a single line in French: "J\'eviterai plaisir et damnation." ("I shall avoid pleasure and damnation.")</item>
        <item>A donkey\'s jawbone.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag filled with twenty-two yellow and black casino markers, all with a Yellow Sign in the centre. [SAN-loss as usual if the Agents haven\'t been exposed to the Sign before.]</item>
        <item>An unnervingly detailed statue of a human being, complete with facial features, fingers, etc. It is made from tens of thousands of spent bullet casings, and seems to be cringing in terror.</item>
        <item>An unlabeled twist-lid wine bottle full of a smokey black-green liquid and a grainy deposit. The liquid is a 35% strength Pisco - a Chilean grape brandy - mixed with gunpowder. Popularly known as "Chupilca del Diablo", the mixture is a popular pre-battle intoxicant used to increase aggression, numb the senses, and dull physical pain.</item>
        <item>A prepaid cell-phone. There is only one number programmed into it, no name is given. If the number is dialed, Adolph Lepus answers.</item>
        <item>A fish tank, filled water that is green and murky with algae. Suspened in the center is unusual scally severed limb that rotates and occasionally twitches on it\'s own</item>
        <item>A table globe, in a semi-meridian mount with a half-ring attached to either pole of the globe.</item>
        <item>However, the world depicted is not Earth; long, jagged bas-relief mountain ranges cross red oceans, large portions of the surface have had black oil paint applied with a palette knife, in a scale-like effect, and in each hemisphere are three or four strangely depicted Zephyrs, thin instead of plump, sexless, long, ashen hair and cruel looking teardrop eyes. Their cheeks puffed out in their gaunt faces, bursts of crimson feathers being blown from their pinched lips, their fists ending long, curled black talons.</item>
        <item>At first glance, the subjects of this collection of photographs appears completely ordinary; a man riding a motorcycle down a busy street, a twisting garden path leading to an elegant house, two children in an empty street in autumn. Strangely the photos are in color, but the era seems to be the early twentieth century. A closer examination reveals that the flora, fauna, clothing, architecture, writing, and technology depicted are unlike anything you have ever seen in any past or present culture. Successful history, natural history, mechanical repair and/or anthropology checks will confirm this. The motorcycle seems to be powered by a small pneumatic engine. Large dirigibles with underslung cargo can be seen in some of the backgrounds. The dominant architectural style mixes graceful Art Nouveau metalwork with round roofs and walls decorated with geometric repeating patterns. The writing consists of a series of small, vertically arranged circles emitting short lines and curves. Most of the people in the pictures have a somewhat Eurasian appearance, but subtle differences in their features suggests otherwise. Their clothing is composed of thin multiple layers with repeating patterns in drab colors. You gradually start to feel something about the photos is off, almost as if you shouldn\'t be looking at them - and that you are being watched. Thankfully, the feelings wear off 24 hours after viewing the photos. (These are photos from an alternate Earth, whose timeline diverged sometime within the past 8 million years, thus having a different technological, social, natural and even geological history. This information simply should not exist in this world. Every day an agent views the photos, there is a five percent chance that a Hound of Tindalos will catch their scent...)</item>
        <item>A one quart mason jar one third full of dead, red ants. It appears that the jar has been through the canning process because it\'s tightly sealed.</item>
        <item>A USB Flash drive containing an executable file that, when launched, will wipe the computer\'s hard drive and install a program that plays the music video for Rick Astley\'s hit "Never Gonna Give You Up" on infinite repeat when the computer boots up.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a plastic toy magic wand for little girls. It is in fact a plastic toy magic wand for little girls, and doesn\'t actually do anything.</item>
        <item>A deck of cards with non-standard suits (hearts, knives, robes and altars) and goat-like figures in place of the standard face cards.</item>
        <item>A large collection of antique surgical equipment, the box shows it to be french in origin.</item>
        <item>A greasy drawstring pouch containing human infant teeth, black hairs (from a black bear) and half a dozen feathers (blue jay and barn swallow).</item>
        <item>A portrait of Hitler with grievous wounds, including at least two bombings.</item>
        <item>A brown cardboard box labeled with the name of a high school in the local area. The box is filled with confiscated cellphones, CD players and other items. Closer examination will reveal the Yellow Sign has been painted on two of the CD players with white out.</item>
        <item>A glass eye that swivels to look at the closest person by itself.</item>
        <item>A small brass cage containing the decomposed remains of some sort of small yellow bird.</item>
        <item>A WWII metal canteen with the Elder Sign etched into both sides.</item>
        <item>An antique silver St. Christopher\'s medal. Careful inspection notes that the saint\'s head with a dog\'s head (as is it sometimes can be) but that he is standing atop of a pile of corpses. The whole thing is lightly caked in foul-smelling dirt.</item>
        <item>A key chain with a human ear on it. 0/1d4 SAN</item>
        <item>After closing the door of the Green Box, you turn and discover that someone has spraypainted a very large Yellow Sign on the inside of the rolling steel door. Keeper\'s choice as to whether or not this actually has any effect other than frightening the characters.</item>
        <item>A fetish doll of a man in a dark suit with pins stuck in it\'s groin.</item>
        <item>A home video in old-fashioned tape reel format, labelled "1600 Penn."\nViewing it in the nearby projector shows it to be a day in the life of President Jimmy Carter, showing him walking around the White House apparently giving the cameraman/woman a tour. The tape ends suddenly as someone (seemingly a White House chef) rushes Carter, attempting to stab him with a kitchen knife. He is subdued by Secret Service agents before he can reach the President, and another Secret Service agent blocks the camera until the tape cuts out.</item>
        <item>Unopened 50ml bottle of whisky. Suntory Yamazaki single malt, aged 12 years. Slight moisture damage to label and minor tears on the wrapper around the cork The only unusual markings on the bottle are five bloody fingerprints, too smudged to be matched with any certainty.</item>
        <item>Upon entering the greenbox, the characters discover that someone\'s decorated it for Christmas. A large Christmas tree stands in the middle of the room and all of the room\'s contents have been neatly (obsessively?) gift-wrapped and stacked beneath the tree.</item>
        <item>A collection of toy soldiers, circa the Crimean War. All the faces have been mutilated or modified. Some appear dog-like in appearance.</item>
        <item>An extensively modified lineman\'s handset:\n- 16-button DTMF keypad (0-9, #, *, A-D);\n- programmable speed-dial with ten memory banks capable of holding 256 digits total, plus pauses and adjustable dialing speed (what numbers are already in memory?);\n- removable alligator clips with several other tap attachements (including heat coil and magnetic induction);\n- redial;\n- hookflash;\n- a speakerphone mode;\n- line in and out jacks;\n- a standard talk/monitor/mute switch;\n- standard tone/pulse dial selection.\nThe handset is black and there\'s a grinning skull sticker on the back of the earpiece. "2600" is scratched into the handle.\nA small box next to the handset is a 20-digit DTMF decoder with a LED screen and a 1024 digit memory. There are line in/out jacks on the box. The oldest numbers rotate out as new numbers are recorded, so there may be over a hundred interesting phone numbers, access codes, etc. still in memory. The box runs off line-in power from the handset, and uses a common 10-year LI watch battery to maintain the numbers in memory.\nInstructions for use &amp; parts/wiring diagrams are in a three-ring binder found with the devices. Agents will need a 1/8" m/m audio patch cord to hook the devices together &amp; decode touchtones picked up via the handset.</item>
        <item>Several lengths of steel rebar, all bent into triangles of various sizes and types. They are arranged in an indecipherable but seemingly deliberate pattern.</item>
        <item>A large glass aquarium, the interior so tangled with lengthy clumps of cobwebbing that it is nearly impossible to see inside...</item>
        <item>A plastic bag full of offal. A lot of the blood and juices have leaked through and it all smells horrible. Strangely, no insects will go near it. DNA testing proves inconclusive.</item>
        <item>A small ziploc bag containing an old silver dollar. One side of the coin is skillfully carved to show a monstrous octopus-like face. Drops of salt-water can be seen on the inside of the bag.</item>
        <item>A wooden dagger and some sort of ceremonial black cloak.</item>
        <item>A box full of plaster death-masques, many cracked beyond repair. The intensity of pain and fear on their cold, dead features is particularly disturbing.</item>
        <item>An onyx signet ring. At first glance, the seal is a rampant lion, but when you look again, it\'s a pentacle.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a small origami flower folded from pale yellow paper. There are several folds and angles on the flower which seems like they should be impossible to create. Trying to unfold the flower produces only a torn up mess of paper.</item>
        <item>A stack of crude earthen jugs, with strange, leering faces carved into the sides.</item>
        <item>An oil painting. It is a family portrait, dating from the late 19th century. While the artistry is poor, of greater concern are the weird deformities of the subjects. The family, posed in a formal setting in a rather posh home, all share some sort of congenital defect causing enlarged eyes and a hunched-back (to varying degrees, the deformity increases with age), as well as an eczema-like skin condition and distorted limbs. One woman is so deformed as to hide her face behind an opaque veil. Furnishings and other signs suggest the portrait was created in New England some time after 1860. (see p. 83 of "Return to Innsmouth" for more information)</item>
        <item>Inside this Green Box is a low table, which has several paper and styrofoam containers on top of it, of the sort normally associated with take-out Chinese food. They contain fried rice, a very spicy chicken dish, fortune cookies, disposable chopsticks, and so on. All are still steaming hot and apparently fresh, in spite of the fact that the PCs are (supposedly) the first to enter this Green Box since 1998. The chicken dish is excellent, the fried rice just so-so.</item>
        <item>The hand of a Grey alien, dissected with parts of the skin and organs pinned back for study.</item>
        <item>A headless and limbless male Caucasian torso bound in saran-wrap. Its DNA is an exact match for sixteen different people, all currently incarcerated in Federal penitentiaries.</item>
        <item>A very old, slightly rusted military "dog tag" chain with a pair of rusty old military ID "dog tags" on it, with the name of one of the PCs--who has never served in the military. Also on the chain are two dozen or so small flat wrinkled objects threaded onto it; closer examination will reveal them to be mummified human ears. 1/1d4 SAN, double for the PC whose name is on the tags.</item>
        <item>A big jar full of pickled cow eyes.</item>
        <item>A Tibetan prayer wheel without a spindle. If translated the prayers are all to the \'Emerald Lama\' and pray for the oblivion of the world.</item>
        <item>A box of expensive Cuban cigars, with a sticky note:\n"KGB SELECT- laced with polonium-based radioactive toxin. Be MILES away from the second-hand smoke, if you know what\'s good for you. Cheers, M"</item>
        <item>A supposedly cursed tiki mask.</item>
        <item>Human-leather wallet.</item>
        <item>A small refrigerator, shut tight with a sturdy padlock. Inside are carefully dated and segregated glass jars full of blood, semen, expectorant, urine and pickled faces - a veritable collection of human byproducts. Comparing them to DNA databases ties them to Cpt. Douglas Booth Ripley, USAMRIID. He died "during training" in 2009.</item>
        <item>A makeshift idol, constructed of old cans and plastic scraps. It appears to be some sort of squat humanoid with wings and an octopoid head. The junk it was assembled from suggests it was made in Brazil.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box containing a large piece (15" by 20" by 4") of anthracite coal, split down the middle. There is a perfectly triangular cavity within the rock, 6" on a side and 1/2" deep. The box bears a stamp and is postmarked to the Carnegie Museum of Natural History in Pittsburgh, PA. The return address has been removed.</item>
        <item>A briefcase containing a strange assemblage of leather straps and a steel framework. Nasty-looking steel screws jut out of the framework at certain positions. A closer inspection reveals that the equipment is probably intended to be strapped onto some small animal or human, like a medium-sized dog och child. Tightening the screws will then slowly and agonizingly kill the restrained creature. The briefcase also contains a pair of surgical gloves and a small tape-recorder. No tape is present.</item>
        <item>A set of one dozen two foot tall plastic pink flamingo lawn ornaments. If set into any lawn at each dawn they will be in a different configuration; any record of that configuration always shows the current configuration, no matter how or when it was recorded.</item>
        <item>Two black steel 55 gallon drums with steel lids clamped on, each about one third full of a mixture of prilled potassium hydroxide and prilled quicklime. The second one contains the same mixture plus many gallons of foul-smelling sludge and a crumbling, partially dissolved skeleton, 1/1d3 SAN. Noticing that the skeleton is only vaguely humanoid (Keeper may feel free to add details like grotesque fangs, arms longer than legs, clawed hands terminating in talons, top of skull secured with brightly polished silver machine screws), 1d3/1d8 SAN. Noticing all the scratches and gouges on the inside of the drum, 2d4/3d6 SAN.</item>
        <item>A cheap, battered blue cooler half-filled with dark colored wood chips and sawdust.\nA note scrawled on the lid in Sharpie says, "It may look like trash, but it\'s REALLY important. DO NOT DISPOSE OF.\n-R Cell"\nEven if the current investigators are R cell.</item>
        <item>A cheap notebook with the familiar black-and-white-blobs cover common to those used in high school. The first page reads "Aklo For Dummies" in curiously neat and stylized calligraphy. The remaining pages constitute an introductory self-taught course in Aklo. 6 weeks (2 to skim), 2/1D6 SAN after reading and practicing the lessons therein.</item>
        <item>Pair of incredibley, elaborately detailed fake binoculars made from wood and laquered black so as to make them look like the real thing. When someone adjusts the focus spring-loaded four-inch spikes will spring out of the "lenses". Fortunately for any unwary person looking through the Green Box, someone has already sprung the spikes so they can be seen.</item>
        <item>A Shining Trapezohedron keychain, made in Taiwan.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a normal, if slightly outdated, wired computer mouse. However, if plugged in, a small and well-concealed explosive charge inside will detonate when the right mouse button is clicked. The explosion isn\'t strong enough to kill, but it will certainly take off a forearm, and perhaps put some shrapnel in the user\'s chest.</item>
        <item>What first seems to be a human eye, is on closer inspection a very good replica of one. The "optical nerve" is actually a bundle of thin, coppery wires. If the "eye" is split, one will find all manner of electronics in it. An agent may replace a lost eye with this, simply by putting it in the missing eye\'s socket. It will sting, and the agent will lose 1/1d4 SAN, but it\'ll work perfectly.</item>
        <item>A backboard of the sort you\'d find in an ambulance\'s usual allotment of equipment which has been retrofitted with a very large C-clamp that has a piece of 2x4 crudely affixed to both the stationary bottom and mobile upper screw-piece. Several loose coils of sturdy nylon towing strap with quick-close ratcheting dogs and a battery powered power drill with a 1/4" bit are nearby. There are traces of blood on the C-clamp and cervical collar mount of the backboard.\nYes, this is a field trepanation kit.</item>
        <item>A Jack-in-the-Box, except that instead of music when the crank is turned the Agents hear the last conversation they had with each other.</item>
        <item>A Glock 17 9mm pistol. A closer inspection shows that all the inner workings, including the half-full magazine, has been subtly deformed in some unknown way and has partially merged together, making the gun useless.</item>
        <item>A tear gas canister, as used by riot police. However, this one is apparently modified, as well as being painted with the Elder Sign on one side. Upon use, it disperses a large quantity of the Powder of Ibn-Ghazi, which makes invisible creatures visible and causes harm to Mythos creatures.</item>
        <item>Piece of roughly torn thin white cardboard about 5" x 4". There is a faint dried stain about 3/4" in diameter on the card; the stain has been roughly circled with a blue-black fountain pen, and a question mark is written next to the circle. In fact the stain was caused by water from a rain barrel.</item>
        <item>A jade elephant, about seven inches long. The crystal appears to have darkened for unknown reasons. Those that stare at it for over five minutes, can start to see the dark blotches moving.</item>
        <item>A battered and unlabelled VHS tape, the label has been torn off and the cardboard sleeve simply reads "day 101" in sharpie. If watched it\'s a silent black&amp;white recording of a crow perched on the picked over remains of a coyote, the crow picks at the carcass occasionally, and finally looks at the camera before the tape ends.</item>
        <item>A calvarium - the top and rear portion of a skull - which looks humanoid, but is unusually large and unusually shaped.</item>
        <item>Human skull with elongated canines - Red marker on the side says "Van Helsing was here" with a smiley face next to it.</item>
        <item>Beautifully made signet ring of whitish gold, the face depicts the jaws of a predatory fish.</item>
        <item>A six-foot tall slab of half-inch steel plate welded to a wheeled frame at an approximate 75 degree angle from the ground. A vision slit has been crudely cut into it with a blowtorch, and the entire front of the assembly bears sporadic pitting as if spattered with strong acid.</item>
        <item>A medicine cabinet fitted to the Green Box\'s wall contains a dozen formaldehyde-filled glass jars, each containing a piece of male human anatomy.</item>
        <item>A shrunken head</item>
        <item>A series of tapes of a dirty, and wild-eyed man making a long rambling rant. Occasionally he will address the watcher as if he knew that they were there and perehaps even provide some insights. After any part of the tape is watched it is erased for ever.</item>
        <item>A sealed 55 gallon drum bearing a large label, "JANITOR IN A DRUM." Opening the drum reveals the janitor. He has been dead quite some time. 1/1d4 SAN.</item>
        <item>Someone went to a considerable amount of trouble to chisel a room-sized Yellow Sign into the floor of the greenbox. A number of chisels worn blunt by the effort were tossed carelessly into a corner of the box. The hammer is embedded an inch deep in one of the walls. Keeper\'s decision as to whether or not anything actually supernatural is associated with this.</item>
        <item>A small refrigeration unit, containing a frozen human tongue in a plastic bag. The bag is labeled "Sverdlovsk, 1959".</item>
        <item>A small handheld device that flashes a repeating series of lights (green, green, green, red) despite no apparent source of power. If a person focuses on the lights for too long, they go into a trance where they are unaware of anything that happens until some wakes them up or removes the device from view.</item>
        <item>A Magic Eye picture that forms ten different occult symbols at different angles of viewing. One will deal 1d4 points of san damage; the rest are mere curiosities and not actively harmful.</item>
        <item>A hermetically sealed glass bio-sphere - algae, oxygen, water, and a pink octopus that appears to be resting contentedly at the bottom of the softball-sized globe.</item>
        <item>An oil painting, with an ornate wooden frame. It depicts a heavily-bearded madman, clad only in a filthy, tattered loincloth, his emaciated body covered with dirt and sores, dancing wildly on a precipice between two massive, metal pillars. His long, gray hair whips about his face in an unseen wind; behind him, beyond the precipice violet clouds seethe and roil. He seems to be playing some strange sort of wind instrument, like a flute. The painting is rendered in a realistic, highly detailed style.</item>
        <item>A glass container with yellowish preservative liquid in it as well as a human head. It has long hair and a scraggly beard, and the cut around its neck is ragged. On the side of the container is a label with the text "HOBO HEAD" neatly written.</item>
        <item>An oxy-acetylene welding torch and a contraption that appears to be for holding a limb in place.</item>
        <item>A manila file listed "Wilmarth Foundation". Inside is paperwork, but provides no useful information: just invoices and reports. From a small note within, it seems that a previous agent had acquired the documents, and wanted to use it as a red herring.</item>
        <item>Eight human skulls in a duffel bag. Their bone crumbles like plaster if handled roughly, as if drained of their density.</item>
        <item>Surveillance video-tapes from various government installations in Washington D.C. (including the Library of Congress, Hoover Building and White House). All are dated 11 FEB 2011. About fifteen minutes into each tape the cameras shut down for four minutes before restarting - to show the interior of the wrong building...\nIt\'s almost as if the cameras and tapes were physically switched between each other while filming.</item>
        <item>Ten 36″ x 48″ acrylic-painted canvases that have been removed from their stretcher bars and loosely rolled up. The paintings depict blurry, fevered scenes and in bright colors, detailed map overlays of Kadath, Leng, and Carcosa.</item>
        <item>Rusted and pitted cavalry saber with a tag marked "1970 Angkor Wat Incident".</item>
        <item>A dry erase board, upon which a complicated Algebraic Topology theorem has been completed in sloppy handwriting. A different hand has written "DO NOT ERASE" and for those who can\'t read, a full plate of clear plexiglass has been attached, covering the front of the board.</item>
        <item>A small cardboard box of items that seem straight out of a Bond film. It includes a Zippo grenade whose 5- second fuse is armed by the lighter wheel, a (very garish) tie with a carbon-fiber garrote wire stitched inside, a pack of AA batteries designed to ruin any electronic they are placed in with extremely rapid pulses of high-voltage electricity, and other examples of prop-department spy gear. At the bottom is a yellowed business card for a local amateur inventor, now deceased.</item>
        <item>A small wooden statuette of Pazuzu, Babylonian king of the Wind Demons, wrapped in many layers of duct tape. If unwrapped the statuette seems to be of modern manufacture, probably in India or Vietnam.</item>
        <item>A set of scalpels, the edges of blades are made of an obsidian-like material. The blades are incredibly sharp but the edges are fragile and prone to splintering if used roughly. The scalpels are held in a faded leather wrap.</item>
        <item>A lampshade made of human skin. It has the Yellow Sign tattooed on it. It has been mounted on a blacklight desktop lamp.</item>
        <item>A bezoar in an ornate golden box studded with precious stones</item>
        <item>Approximately 30 feet of 7/8" steel rebar, such as the type used to reinforce concrete. This length has been bent into an elaborate bear shape, not unlike a balloon animal, by someone or something with immense strength.</item>
        <item>An ornate .357 revolver with a snub-barrel inside an expensive looking case with velvet interior. The grip is engraved with patterns of a vulture gnawing upon a bone. One round is chambered.</item>
        <item>In the corner of the room is a large, reclinable dentist\'s chair with wipe-down plastic covers. There are metal braces welded to the arm-rests, as well as a strong strap on the fold-up foot-rest, allowing anyone seated to be securely restrained...</item>
        <item>A small, well-kept terrarium containing a chameleon. It has an unnerving habit of constant, unblinking eye contact whenever looked at, and if the investigators take their eyes off of it they will occasionally hear indistinct (though definitely human) muttering coming from its direction.</item>
        <item>Several aluminum crossbow bolts lined up end to end on the floor. Their heads are badly melted, as if fired into something impossibly hot.</item>
        <item>A hacksaw coated in a woolly greyish mold, of a species currently unknown to science. It is contained in several layers of vacuum-sealed plastic placed in a taped-shut clear plastic tub. If opened, everyone who inhales the airborne spores must make a POT 17 poison check or lose 1d4 points of CON permanently, as well as develop acute symptoms of pneumonia. Those who save against it only suffer from sporadic coughing fits.</item>
        <item>The jawbone of a ghoul (though not recongizable as such unless the viewer is familiar with ghouls; others will be perplexed). It has been lacquered and silver has been inlayed on the surface; two holes (black wax residue suggests for candles) have been bored into the masseter.</item>
        <item>A 1954 Sparton color television, packed carefully in a cardboard box filled with packing peanuts. If examined the television is inoperable- significant modification has been made to the internal wiring. A number of Regency TR-1 transistor radios have been soldered into the basic wiring. If carefully examined, a number of strange pencil markings in a curvilinear script can be spotted on the back of the television. They are untranslatable.</item>
        <item>Bizarre art-deco monkey statuettes embodying "See No Evil", "Hear No Evil" and "Speak No Evil" - as well as a fourth: "Smell No Evil"</item>
        <item>A small green paper box containing a single "Suzie B." 1 dollar coin. The Apollo 11 mission insignia on the reverse side has been defaced with some sharp instrument.</item>
        <item>A human skull wearing a Sikh turban. The skull\'s front incisors are gold capped and there is a neat bullet-hole above the right earhole.</item>
        <item>A two feet tall concrete replica an Easter Island "head". The replica weighs approximately 80 lbs and if broken apart a polished human skull can be found at its centre.</item>
        <item>Inflatable mattress with odd stains; some stains appear to be shaped like ancient runes.</item>
        <item>A genuine lava lamp, straight from the 1960\'s. The only difference is that it seems to function only when there are no other lights in the room.</item>
        <item>A complete suit of plate mail made of thin, white glass wafers. It includes gloves and a coif that covers most of the face. Physical analysis shows the material sandwiched in the wafers to be Thallium doped Caesium Iodide. Resting atop the suit is a DVD labeled "Tin Foil Hat (BUT IT WORKS!)" The DVD is a collection of IR videos showing soldiers in this mail in a desert at night. They maneuver around and take shots at lights in the sky, which then move erratically or blink out. At one point a soldier comments "In-fucking-visible. Amazing."</item>
        <item>Rows of jars containing various organs and body parts perserved in formaldehyde. Each jar has detailed notes recording a variety of measurements and tests, written in a scientific manor. Each has the word REJECTED at the bottom for unstated reasons.\nThe only exception is the last jar, which is taller then an investigator and is empty except for a few dregs of fluid and a few hairs. The accompanying notes are blank except for HE APPROVES.</item>
        <item>A picture of Hulk Hogan, autographed with a few words in Cyrillic nearby.\nThe picture shows a second smaller face beneath Hogan\'s classic mustache, and repeats endlessly even on a microscopic scale.</item>
        <item>A brightly-colored Super Soaker lies on a table; it has been labelled "L.R.I.D." in red Sharpie. Upon closer examination, a subtitle indicates this to mean "Long Range Intoxication Device".\nThe tank is filled with a particularly dry blend of vodka martini.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag filled with used 9mm bullets. Some flattened, some fairly intact, but all are covered in dried blood. There is also a note in the bag saying "Where the hell do we dispose of these!?".</item>
        <item>A smallish human skull with a serif \'V\' etched into its forehead. It is missing its jaw. When you hold it, you begin to question every act of charity you\'ve performed.</item>
        <item>A child\'s dollhouse, no more than two feet high. Everything inside it is in perfect working order; the taps on the sink run hot and cold water, and the cupboards are filled with miniature cans of real food. There are no dolls in the dollhouse, but close examination will reveal several half-eaten meals on the dining room table, as well as a cigarette butt in a tiny ashtray, still smoking.</item>
        <item>A heavy but small cage covered with long dried fecal matter and blood with a plate "Specimen Phi Iota Catskill" with 2 notes pinned to it, one in unintelligible glyphs, another says "do not release". The cage is open.</item>
        <item>A brown glass bottle in a paper bag. On the bag, written in marker pen, are the words \'Hobo Jack\'s Private Reserve\'. The bottle is a crude and dangerous mixture of antifreeze, motor oil, cola and milk which has been lying around for far too long. The consequences of actually drinking this mix are quite obvious.</item>
        <item>A fetal pig floating in a full bottle of Luksusowa vodka. The bottle is sealed - and in any case, the pig is too large to fit through the neck of the bottle.</item>
        <item>A bizarre set of dentures made entirely out of stainless steel; it appears to be an attempt to create a real-world equivalent of the Bond villain Jaws\' teeth.</item>
        <item>A pair of old fashioned wrought iron manacles of the type in use in New England in the 1860\'s. They are well maintaned and in working order but lack a key; upon investigation the key is found to be on a key ring on the investigator\'s person.</item>
        <item>One foam-lined aluminium box containing a single speaker from a compact stereo set. Taped to the back is a complex circuit-board, along with a note saying: "Operation Dry-Wipe: Evidence" and "Warning: Do not disconnect!". If the circuit-board is disconnected from the sockets the speaker will immediately begin hissing and sputtering a very loud, hideous and high-pitched noise, occasionally interrupted by, apparently human, screams. It will make unbearable noise continuously, without a power-source, until the circuit is re-connected, or the speaker is damaged beyond repair (three or four rounds of 9mm HP ammo should do it).</item>
        <item>A leather flying helmet, of the type often used by World War I aviators. It has a small hole just above the left ear area, a larger hole on the right side, and most of the sheepskin liner is stained dark brown. The leather is soft, supple and in good condition.</item>
        <item>One Stevens Model 67 pump-action shotgun. unloaded and wrapped in brittle plastic tarp. The barrel of the weapon is severely pitted and corroded as if it had been subjected to extremely powerful acid.</item>
        <item>A strange, grasshopper-shaped miniature drone sits on a shebox-sized metal box. Behind both is a water-damaged dot-matrix printout of a user manual, which identifies this as a DARPA experiment in autonomous contraband-detection drones. Simple controls such as on/off, recall, print report, etc. are on the side of the box, which serves as both a carrier and a recharging station.\nShould it be turned on, its faults will be fairly obvious. Not only does it have abysmal pathfinding systems (easily trapped by furniture, curbs, stairs, etc), but it is also rather overenthusiastic about what it decries as dangerous: the rat poison left in the corner will register as a chemical weapon, any type of signal sending/receiving device will register as a possible detonator (including it\'s own home base), and a pack of emergency road flares nearby will be registered as incendiary grenades.</item>
        <item>The box contains the right rear paw of a black house cat. Attached to it a note that reads: "Look out for Tripod, he\'s the only one you\'ll be able to see."</item>
        <item>A small pepper-spray bottle, the label of which has been removed and replaced by a taped-on printed Jack Daniels\' label. Predictably, when used it sprays a fine mist of whiskey, useful for instantly discrediting a witness.</item>
        <item>A Marshall Island stick chart. The charts represented major ocean swell patterns and the ways the islands disrupted those patterns. It just appears to be sticks and shells. However, someone who knows how to read it will recognize that one island is marked as off limits.</item>
        <item>An empty bottle of Crown Royal. Any attempts to destroy the bottle will be met with failure, and any liquid stored within the bottle will disappear as soon as the bottle is placed out of sight.</item>
        <item>A shoebox with a collection of photographs from the 60s. They appear to be some kind of lab photographs, or portraits of individuals in 40s-era finery. Most of the photos are hard to make out, because they have red marker over large sections of them. An Idea check will allow the PCs to arrange the photographs so the lines match up, forming the words "Would You Kindly?" over the photographs.</item>
        <item>A shoebox with post-it note stuck to the lid reading: "Miniature Black Hole Inside - Do Not Open!"</item>
        <item>A set of false teeth replicating the layout of shark\'s teeth, but with human incisors.</item>
        <item>A large Crookes tube, modified with strange attachments - batteries to power it, and an arrangement of screens and reflectors.</item>
        <item>An Erlenmeyer flask with a black rubber stopper, sealed with what appears to be Super Glue. The flask is half full, containing a blue liquid which seems to swirl around.</item>
        <item>A set of unlabelled futuristic plastic cassettes with connectors unknown to regular technology. These are Majestic-12 memory blocks containing the digitised memories and personalities of dead scientists and agents, courtesy of MJ-12s alien "friends".\nUnless agents have the corresponding room-sized equipment to transfer these cassettes to a fresh brain (cloned or overwritten), they are useless. Nevertheless, NRO agents are still looking for them ever since they were stolen from a lab six months back and will use all force to regain them...</item>
        <item>A human skull that has been fashioned into a chalice. The base of the chalice is brass with sections of gold inlay. Semi precious stones circle the "brim".</item>
        <item>A piece of funhouse mirror, burnt around it\'s broken edges. Its reflections are warped in different way every time you look at it.</item>
        <item>A 15-foot long propeller blade from a C-130 "Hercules". There are deep gouges along its length, as if from a trio of claws.</item>
        <item>A large plastic Elvis coin bank containing 3 kilos of heroin in small glassine packets.</item>
        <item>What at first glance appears to be a power-drill with a fishing reel soldered on, this crude delivery system is in essence a tiny elevator. The line is tied off to something sturdy on the top side of its track, and the power-drill\'s trigger is locked down using a moving metal bar. The drill\'s spinning motion unreels the line, lowering it down to the ground; it can be sent back up by simply reversing the drill\'s direction.\nThis is obviously not strong enough to carry a human being; its maximum weight capacity is probably around 20 lbs. Its cargo is carried in a small burlap sack tied off to the drill\'s pistol grip.</item>
        <item>Three carefully made tin-foil helmets.</item>
        <item>A menu for a local Chinese take-out restaurant. A few of the items on the menu are circled, with numbers written beside them clearly indicating the quantity desired. On the back of the menu, someone has written "feeds one cell, great for stakeouts and stuff. You won\'t regret it :)"\nShould the investigators order it, however, the person on the phone will audibly panic, inform them that every time that specific order has been made in the past, the delivery boy who brought it never came back, and hang up. The restaurant them stops answering the phone for the rest of the day.</item>
        <item>A bootleg music CD. Every track is a different cover version of "Monster Mash," starting with the 1997 punk rock version by The Misfits.</item>
        <item>A city utilities safety vest. A sizable chunk is missing from the left side...a Spot Hidden check will note caked-on blood, and that the hole is actually a bite mark nearly as big as that of a great white shark. 0/1d3 SAN loss from thinking about that too hard.</item>
        <item>A fully functional black powder cannon, complete with 1d6 cannon balls. Powder, cleaning tools, and all other necessary supplies for operation can be found in a footlocker nearby. A note atop the footlocker reads: "WARNING: DO NOT ATTEMPT TO USE. Not joking! - V, 2014".</item>
        <item>A carved wooden box containing a mummified squirrel.</item>
        <item>A framed photograph of President Ronald Reagan smiling and shaking hands with Stephen Alzis, apparently on the White House\'s South Lawn. If anyone who might have been around when this photograph was taken (retired Secret Service agents, Nancy Reagan, White House staffers, etc.) happens to be asked about this picture, none of them remember Alzis ever being around the White House.</item>
        <item>A piece of sheet metal scarcely recognizable as the horrendously deformed car fender, punctured multiple times with strange, star-shaped implements and severely warped, as if from heat. An appropriate roll would note that the metal in question would require temperatures in excess of a thousand degrees Fahrenheit in order to bend the way it has.</item>
        <item>A large plastic evidence-bag containing a branding iron with a tip formed as a strange squiggly symbol. Judging by the blackened tip it has been used.</item>
        <item>A heavy, impact resistant case filled with $1000 dollars in quarters. A plain blue birthday card within reads "A little something for the arcade fund, Love Stewie."</item>
        <item>A jack-in-the-box (closed), with a hand-lettered sign taped to it that reads, "DO NOT TURN CRANK."</item>
        <item>Tins of soup. Hundreds of tins. Every type, every make, every flavor. So many tins. Who needs this much soup?!</item>
        <item>A flashlight with an odd symbol acid-etched onto the glass. Bloodstains fluoresce under its light as if it was a forensics blacklight.</item>
        <item>A small ziploc bag containing a Russian "Saint George the Victorious" 3 rubles silver coin. The obverse side indicates it was printed in 2008, which is strange as the production of the silver version only started 2009. The image of Saint George and the Dragon on the reverse side is also subtly different; the Dragon seems thicker, it\'s wings larger and it\'s face sprouts flailing tentacles.</item>
        <item>4 wooden cups containing 5 six sided die in each. The dice seem to be hollow and have something inside them that rattles when the dice are agitated.</item>
        <item>A wooden crate bearing a custom stamp from the 1930s. Inside is a rock and barnacle encrusted mass with streaks of greenish-blue metal visible beneath. If x-rayed, the mass proves to be a short sword of unusual manufacture; the potassium -argon dating says that the metal is over 10,000 years old; the sea-life covering the weapon can be indentified as native to the Atlantic Ocean off the northern coast of Brazil; lastly the style of blade matches no ancient human artistic tradition.</item>
        <item>A small, hovering black-hole about the size of a golf-ball in a glass bell-jar. The lid of the jar can be removed and objects fed into the black hole where they will be trapped forever. So long as an individual doesn\'t touch the event-horizon (which extends about 1/3" beyond the sphere\'s boundary) he is safe. Touch the boundary, however, and unless you amputate that body part, you will be sucked inexorably in - and pulped into infinitesimally small parts. Forever.</item>
        <item>A small packing crate style wooden box on which was taped a piece of paper and a scrawled message \'Warning, do not under any circumstances open this!\'</item>
        <item>A device similar in shape and design to a rubix cube, except in appearance it looks to be made of obsidian or some such material. In place of colors, each tile has a single gilded number, and the device twists and turns of its own volition. It may be used 1d6 amount of times to decipher a lock combination/computer code/etc, which the box will then whisper to the user in a child\'s voice.</item>
        <item>A tentacle made of an unknown crystalline substance. The tentacle absorbs any silver it comes in contact with and then grows longer.</item>
        <item>A severed index finger wrapped in Saran-wrap, covered in blood. Above it, someone scrawled (apparently using the blood from the finger) "IT DIDN\'T WORK ON THE SCANNER, M!"\nBelow it, in Sharpie, a much more steady hand has written "Of course not, dumbass, it has to be ATTACHED. Also, that\'s totally unsanitary. Why is it even still here?"</item>
        <item>19th century gravestone taken from London\'s Highgate Cemetery</item>
        <item>A variety of wooden geometric blocks: cubes, octahedrons, dodecahedrons, cylinders, prisms etc. An eye has been carved into one face of each of them. There are no pyramidal blocks.</item>
        <item>A wicker picnic hamper containing a raw, half-eaten civet cat and a lot of maggots. Toothmarks on the animal\'s corpse are undeniably human. Tests also conclude the animal was suffering from severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS).</item>
        <item>6 1 meter lengths of oxygen-free copper rod 10mm in diameter.</item>
        <item>5 are still sealed in their protective packing - the last seems to have been chewed on, with 23 cm gnawed away.</item>
        <item>A child\'s tea-set in an ornate but worm eaten wooden chest. Residue in the little tea-cups appears to be blood. Amongst the little spoons, forks, cake and sandwich plates are a collection of well cleaned, tiny bones. Some appear to be chicken bones. A Medicine skill roll reveals others to be from the hands of new-born infants. Lose 1/1d3 SAN.</item>
        <item>A cassette tape, the faded label is illegible except for "...ars are dow..." Upon playing the cassette you will hear what sounds like early grunge rock for a few seconds followed by static for the rest of the tape\'s duration.</item>
        <item>Two one gallon glass bottles with ground glass stoppers. One contains sulfuric acid ( 95% purity ), the other contains hydrogen peroxide ( 30% purity ). Mixed in a three to one ratio, the resulting liquid dissolves all known organic matter.</item>
        <item>A 50 gallon poly drum with "MDR 360-39-2112" written on the lid in Sharpee. A little bit of research will reveal that the initials and number, a social security number, belong to Martin Dhruve Rezard, a former agent with the National Biological Survey. Evidently,</item>
        <item>Martin went missing two years prior while on assignment near Flagstaff, Arizona.</item>
        <item>A bleached and varnished skull of some unfamiliar creature.</item>
        <item>A dried monkey\'s paw; three fingers are curled up, the other still extended.</item>
        <item>A home-made piece of equipment that emits sound at 14,000 to 100,000 Hz (adjustable). A piece of tape with an arrow scribbled on it marks frequencies between 42 and 45,000 Hz. It needs a new battery.</item>
        <item>A finger bone from a T. rex. Fossilized, of course.</item>
        <item>A small aquarium containing a tiny red fish, a few rocks and some sand. A large note is pasted to the glass with the text "Beware! Spawn of Scylla!"</item>
        <item>A small coffin. It is shabbily made; a ramshackle mess built from cheap pine now half-rotten with age, barely held together with rusted nails. Someone has pried open the lid. On the lid is a corroded nameplate that reads "William Deane b. June 4, 1955 d. September 19, 1959". A look inside reveals that instead of a child\'s remains the coffin contains the worm-eaten bones of an animal, most likely a dog.</item>
        <item>A collection of listening-tubes and coffin-alarms of the sort most often used during the mid 19th century when fears of being interred alive were rampant. All of these alarms appear to have been compromised from underground.</item>
        <item>A well-worn Zippo lighter. The front side shows the Rolling Stones mouth logo, but with an Elder Sign etched into the tongue. Works like any other lighter..</item>
        <item>A tote-bag with everything needed to go vampire hunting: crucifix, spray-bottle of lightly chlorinated water, bag of tent-pegs and wooden stakes, a mallet, a cheap Bowie knife, coffee tin full of dry rice, and the lingering smell of garlic.</item>
        <item>A leather pouch containing hair, teeth, and feathers.</item>
        <item>A folded up full-size flag. Though similar to the American flag the fifty stars have been replaced by swastikas. It is quite sun-bleached and worn, as if by heavy use.</item>
        <item>A plastic trashcan containing the broken up remains of an ancient egyptian mummy. A note fastened to the lid says "Waste of time.".</item>
        <item>An engraved leather box containing a set of acupuncture needles. The needles are made of a strange whitish material. If samples of the needle?s material is examined the investigators will discover they are made from dinosaur bone.</item>
        <item>A plastic box full to the brim with thousands of different types of keys. What they\'re for, nobody knows.</item>
        <item>A glass blob containing several human teeth, including one with a gold filling.</item>
        <item>Dog skull on a stick. Obviously some sort of witchcraft fetish.</item>
        <item>A partially burned, black-and white harlequin doll, about 18 inches tall. In sections, the cloth and stuffing has burned away, revealing a glossy black skeleton of perfect human proportions.</item>
        <item>Covered up under a canvas sheet is a tall chair, rather archaic in appearance, made from a dark, oily-looking world. It has a box bottom, solid sides and no armrests. Carved on the oval-topped head is a hand grasping some sort of trident. Closer inspection reveals the carved hand is scaled and clawed.</item>
        <item>An ashtray stolen from the Belle Vue Hotel in Syracuse, NY, containing five blood-stained gold teeth. They\'re the remnant of a hip-hop "grill" - since each has a letter embossed. Put in order, they spell "FUK-YO"</item>
        <item>A series of photographs of the interior of an apartment, apparently captured over the course of several hours (the sun seems to sink lower in the sky). Photographs show at least three individuals progressively prying apart the floorboards until they are able to retrieve an enormous glass jar of some murky black liquid.</item>
        <item>A tattered and yellowed envelope containing four tickets for a concert held in 1989, if the date is accurate. The name of the band is The Ulthar Cats.</item>
        <item>A fabric travel-suitcase, its handle bound with a baggage-tag showing arrival at Detroit Metopolitan Airport from London Heathrow in late-1994. Inside the bag is an extraordinarily large and moth-eaten pelt, it\'s shaggy gray fur warm to the touch. Unfolding the pelt reveals the animal to have had six legs. Its head has been removed, which may be a blessing.\n(Cthulhu Mythos roll recognises the pelt\'s original wearer as one of the Gnoph-keh.)</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a crumbled up lump of crushed plastic and metal which can be identified as the remains of a Glock 17 9mm pistol. A closer examination find what appears to crush-marks from human-sized fingers. Fingerprints can be lifted but give no hits in the databases.</item>
        <item>A small but heavy lead-lined box containing four small metal pellets. They are spent uranium dioxide pellets from a nuclear facility and highly radioactive.</item>
        <item>A particularly ugly Russian doll (or matryoshka) about the size of a bowling pin and painted like a sad and bloated old woman. With some effort it can be opened, revealing successively smaller dolls nestled within each other. It becomes slowly apparent - usually when the opener reaches a doll the size of his fingernail - that the dolls seem able to continue to open no matter how far one goes, revealing duplicates presumably ad infinitum (1/1D4 to realise this may be the case)</item>
        <item>A solid gold toilet in 1:19 scale.</item>
        <item>The remains of an ancient piece of machinery; a History or Archaeology roll will identify it as a Roman-era ballista, however all wooden pieces are petrified to the point of appearing to be jade. A Geology roll will indicate that is not, in fact, supposed to happen.</item>
        <item>Model of a male human left foot hewn from luminous blue Play-Doh. Scarily life-like, it even includes calluses and toe-prints. Checking the prints find they match a female John Doe washed up on a beach in Oregon in March 2003.</item>
        <item>A cheap black velvet drawstring pouch that jingles when moved. It contains five gold coins a little bigger than an American quarter, each of which bears an unfamiliar seal and inscription. A little research will show that they are one numismatist\'s or goldsmith\'s idea of what an Amero (the proposed pan-North American dollar and equivalent to the Euro) would look like if it actually came to be as a currency.</item>
        <item>An iron railroad spike. The Hebrew letter \'mem\' has been etched into the head.</item>
        <item>A human finger in a wedding-ring box. Fingerprint and DNA are both untraceable.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing broken light-blue shards of some crystalline material and a note saying: "Think it\'s inert now, but keep isolated just in case.".</item>
        <item>A plain wooden box, about 12" x 12" x 6". When opened it there is a very exotic smell. The box contains bags of dried spices, including: cambodge rinds, cardamon seeds, cinnamon sticks, whole cloves, coriander, cumin, kokam rind, whole nutmegs, saffron (in a glass jar), turmeric and vanilla pods. A faded stamp inside the lid names Gopal and Sons, Export &amp; Import, Calcutta.</item>
        <item>A Kalashnikov rifle with markings that identify it as from the Egyptian Army of Nasser\'s day; its receiver has somehow been pierced through and through by an iron-tipped spear, whose head is still lodged in the side of the weapon. An attached note reads "All that was left, Outpost 114, 1968-07-31."</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing a thin silver chain bearing a number of small silver symbols: a Christian cross, a Star of David, a Hand of Fatima, a seated Buddha and a Pentagram. They are all spattered with dried blood.</item>
        <item>A battered, but serviceable, Parker Bros. Ouija board, ca. 1930s. Its surface is readable, but marred by curious rust colored stains.</item>
        <item>An unlabelled medicine bottle containing about six dozen dried rhinocerous\' horn pills.</item>
        <item>A "Multicam" camouflage pattern bathrobe and bunny slippers. The bathrobe has a subdued "Payback Enterprises" patch on the left shoulder.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing a single Rider-Waite Tarot card (The Devil) with several bullet holes in it.</item>
        <item>Ontop of a small table in the back of the room stand Eight red LEGO spacemen. They are arrayed in a square on the edge of a 16x16 green LEGO baseplate. They are facing in. At the center of the plate is a single solid gold 2x2 Brick. It is extremely difficult to remove the brick from the baseplate.</item>
        <item>A large gray vinyl suitcase. Inside are the yellowing skeletal remains of a large labrador dog. Cursory examination finds the teeth were removed, probably pre-mortem, and the ribs were broken and allowed to heal sometime in the past.</item>
        <item>A nine-and-a-half inch and terribly rusty iron nail in a cheap plastic display case. A newspaper article is tucked into the back of the case reporting the theft of a reputed "Holy Nail" relic from a basilica in Mexico.</item>
        <item>A statue of Martin Luther King made out of plastic in full color with individual fibers for hair and clothing.</item>
        <item>A ventriloquist\'s puppet with an uncanny resemblance to someone you knew.</item>
        <item>A set of unlocked black titanium handcuffs; there is no keyhole or any sort of release at all - once the handcuffs locked, there\'s no opening them.</item>
        <item>A tombstone, fresh dirt still clinging to its base. The name carved into it is vaguely familiar...</item>
        <item>A Hand of Glory.</item>
        <item>A Browning Hi-Power pistol without a magazine bearing many years of coral growth on and within it (at least 300 years if tested)</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a blood-stained titanium pipe, 1/4" in diameter and 1 foot long. One end has been sharpened into a vicious point, on the other a wooden handle ending in a mouthpiece has been fastened.</item>
        <item>A graffiti artist broke into the green box, but rather than take anything they painted a huge mural combining the most visually appealing aspects of a Mandelbrot fractal and cephalopod tentacles. If any of the agents can read wildstyle spraybomb, the graffiti reads "DELTA GREEN," otherwise it\'s a beautiful but incomprehensible design.</item>
        <item>An obviously antique and empty armoire, taller than an average man and almost as wide. It is made from a very dark lusterless wood of a distinctly peculiar grain that feels almost like stone to the touch; the wood is colored a mottled near-black and deep, bilious green. The borders and lintel are covered with bas-relief carvings, extremely detailed depictions of graceful, human-like nereids moving among tritons, seashells and driftwood and various flora and fauna of the ocean floor. However, the bottom and short legs are covered in carvings of strange, humanoid creatures that look as if they\'re part fish, part toad. Their heads are upraised, toothy mouths open, their clawed hands reaching upwards.</item>
        <item>A small (15" long) Chac Mool statue made from greenish stone. This Pre-Columbian Mesoamerican statue shows a reclining human male with the head up and turned to one side, while holding a sacrificial tray over his stomach. An oddity is that the tray contains an inch-wide dark-stained hole leading down into its stomach. Breaking apart the statue, or X-raying it, will reveal a strange metallic "seed" embedded in its centre and connected to the hole. This 2" long oblong "seed" is totally impervious to physical damage.</item>
        <item>A Flash Drive containing images - many of strange and grotesque forms. Those seeing the images feel a sense of ancient dread.\nEach of the file names follow the same format (Title followed by Username)- a common format for a popular art website. Searching the usernames, one will not find accounts, but will find comments containing those names. Most comments are references to artists who had deleted their accounts without warning.</item>
        <item>The Green Box contains a red-and-black stripe 1970 Plymouth GTX 440 "muscle car" with the keys in the sun visor. Considering the only way to get it in here would be to take it apart and rebuild it inside the Box piece by piece, the team of agents who did it must have been sophomoric, if patient, comedians...</item>
        <item>A horse skull with Norse runes painted over it in a brownish substance.</item>
        <item>A pitchfork with a propane blowtorch attached below its tines. a note attached to its handle reads, "J- why use torches and pitchforks? This is the 21st century, be a little more inventive! -K"\nIt appears to be the result of an inside joke, though incomprehensible without knowledge of the event that initiated it.</item>
        <item>A rusty metal tool box. Empty when opened, but feels and sounds as though something metal is contained within when carried.</item>
        <item>A Milestone Motorola filled with a blow by blow establishment of the green-box.\nFrom demolition to start that is.</item>
        <item>A jade dragon, about eight inches long. The crystal appears to have darkened for unknown reasons. Those that stare at it for over five minutes, can start to see the dark blotches moving.</item>
        <item>A museum display case, 4\'x2\'x1\', with a broken pane of glass in front. Inside are four dream-catchers, each with multi-colored feathers. Each dream-catcher has a plaque in the case listing the origins (Bayou country, Louisiana) and the dates of creation (1926-39). A fifth dream-catcher is clearly missing.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing a small plier and a handkerchief covered in dried blood. The handkerchief has been folded around four human molars, one of which have a small crystalline cube embedded in it. Closer inspection reveals that the cube is cracked and has an intricate web of filaments shooting through it.</item>
        <item>A glass goldfish bowl full of replacement heart valves.</item>
        <item>Underneath a dusty tarpaulin ticks a plain wooden grandfather clock. The face\'s numbers are in no known language and the dozen or so hands spiral in intricate and unfamiliar patterns. It chimes irregularly.</item>
        <item>3 sets of cast iron manacles (ankle, wrist, and neck) - these are quite old and rusty. There are layers upon layers of blood and old skin on the inside of all of them.</item>
        <item>Ringing cell-phone that can be heard ringing from outside the Green Box. As soon as Agents opens the box, the cell phone within quiets down. When inspected, there is no phone number displayed on the screen, just a name. The name is of one on the Agents\' close relatives, but, upon closer inspection, it is marked as "agent". The phone can\'t be used to make any calls or send any type of messages, an emotionless male voice will reply "Invalid Code". The cell phone will occasionally receive calls. If one of the Agents answer, they will just hear heavy breathing.</item>
        <item>A food storage container containing a red/yellow gell. Suspended in the gell is a human eyeball with attached nervous system tissue.</item>
        <item>A steel surgical tray containing a few bloodied troodontid teeth. Some broken, others ripped out entirely. Upon examination the teeth appear relatively fresh and can provide tissue-samples of both human and unknown type. The unknown tissue can be shown to match that of the teeth.</item>
        <item>A large evidence bag containing a full set of clothes (a blue suit, tie, shirt, underwear and black shoes). The clothes are blackened on the inside as if something has burned in them.</item>
        <item>A statuette of a Christian knight placed in a hole in the floor. The symbol on his shield is a 5-pointed star with a blazing eye in the center, and a faded Post-it note is stuck to the front of the knight\'s torso that reads "Don\'t fucking remove this!".</item>
        <item>A wax-paper packet of small candles. (They have been made from human fat.) If burned they produce nightmarish visions.</item>
        <item>An ornate, gem-encrusted jade statuette in the likeness of Nicolas Cage. It menaces with spikes of gold.</item>
        <item>A generic-looking glue bottle. The glue within is an absurdly strong adhesive. Aside from super-glue polymers, the glue is infused with enzymes that can molecularly bond similar materials. It dries within a minute of application.</item>
        <item>Thirty-two well-scrubbed human femur bones in a mottled laundry-bag. All the bones been drained of marrow and are curiously flaky.</item>
        <item>A pillowcase stuffed with about six pounds of human hair.</item>
        <item>Seventy-one silk ties, various colours and styles, knotted into a large ball.</item>
        <item>A diaphanous, insectoid wing not unlike what one would expect to find on a wasp or similar creature, carefully preserved in formaldehyde,. However, this particular sample is so large that is preserved in a clear, sealed 5-gallon bucket, and is comparable in size to a tennis racquet. 0/1d2 SAN loss for considering what could possibly yield a wing of this size.</item>
        <item>A one foot tall free form metal sculpture made from shredded aluminum beer cans. The investigator has the uncomfortable feeling that the sculpture is alive in some way, and time lapse photographs show that it does in fact change shape over time, but no mechanism or organism can be found to account for this. Attempts to communicate with it uniformly fail. If it is disassembled it fades away over the next few hours.</item>
        <item>An abstract 15" high sculpture made from razor-blades spot-welded together. It looks sort of like a fat mushroom made of gleaming sharp steel edges. It is hard to move it without wearing gloves.</item>
        <item>A VHS copy of one of the agents\' sixth birthday party. 1/1d3 SAN for viewing it, because until now the individual believed there was only one copy of that tape in existence, and that it was tucked away in their parents\' attic; how (or why) it ended up in a Green Box is beyond anyone\'s knowledge, except A-Cell; they simply respond "not cleared".</item>
        <item>A complete length of tongue, ripped out at the root and wrapped in cellophane. You can tell it\'s human due to the barbell piercing near the tip. Sanity loss is 1/1D3.</item>
        <item>Several massive maggots, each easily the size of a human thumb, preserved in a jar of formaldehyde.\nUnderneath the jar are four unlabeled folders. The first contains an FDA official statement attributing the gigantic maggots to experimental bovine steroids; the second is an apparently unsolicited study from an entomologist (whose name has been redacted) which pokes several holes in the FDA\'s claims; the third is an unopened (possibly undelivered) letter to a colleague in which the entomologist claims he fears for his life after his home was firebombed; finally, the fourth is a Cincinnati PD missing persons report for the still nameless entomologist which seems to have been left unsubmitted to police records.</item>
        <item>A manila envelope simply labeled "HOUND" in red pen on the front. Inside, there are 1d100 aged pieces of paper, some more aged than others, all containing erratic, almost impressionist drawings of a canine-like creature. An agent trained in Craft (Art) may recognize that all the drawings appear to have different artists.</item>
        <item>A BDSM ballgag painted as a human eye.</item>
        <item>A sturdy flashlight with no batteries (it takes two AAs). If loaded and turned on, it proves to contain a blacklight bulb.</item>
        <item>A cheap-looking imitation rabbit\'s foot, dyed a toxic shade of green. If a character picks up the rabbit\'s foot, the next words he or she utters that could reasonably be construed as a command, wish, or desire come true in the most accurate and literal sense possible. The rabbit\'s foot then vanishes and reappears in a random location somewhere on Earth where it is likely to be found. The character who used the rabbit\'s foot loses 1/1d4 SAN upon discovering his or her wish came true, and 0/1 SAN for every time during the next 30 days that he or she hears about a particularly unusual stroke of fortune someone has experienced since the time the wish was made.</item>
        <item>A 107-sheet (unfinished) house of cards. Whoever made it has meticulously glued the edges together so that it can be picked up and moved around.</item>
        <item>A digital camera that, when photgraphing a shadowy area, sometimes causes subtle but definite ghostly figures to appear in the image. While this may seem Mythos-related, an inspection by someone proficient in programming will uncover a very complex and advanced, but otherwise mundane, program designed to embed these images. Commented into the bottom of the code is a line reading "Gotcha ;) -F"</item>
        <item>Two pocket-watches. Both of their fascia are cracked and they have stopped at 10.46. If tested, they are radioactive well above healthy levels.</item>
        <item>A series of numismatist\'s collector\'s cases, containing dozens of low denomination coins. Examination by someone with relevant historical skills determines that some are hundreds or thousands of years old, and every one is from a nation destroyed in war.\nA note on the backing of one case reads "SDA will be back for these, but he can\'t have them. They\'re ours now, dammit." signed \'M-cell, 06/06/1987\'. Prying the relevant information from A-cell will reveal that that incarnation of M-cell was wiped out to the last man while on downtime, their acquaintances slaughtered, and their family trees scoured, root and branch - all murders unsolved, and deemed unrelated.</item>
        <item>A vhs tape showing about twenty minutes of a performance by a street musician (apparently in Chicago, circa 1998). The musician is an African-American in his late thirties, possibly mentally ill. He is playing (badly) a Casio keyboard, singing a mix of gibberish and requests (at $1 a pop). During a particularly awful take on "The Man Who Sold the World", he pauses and begins a brief rant in an unknown language; the video taper zooms in on his face, showing his eyes rolling back in his head. The crowd is visibly shaken</item>
        <item>A soft bag made out of pale skin, containing ten finger bones and two smooth, oblong black stones.</item>
        <item>A large South Korean national flag ("Taegeukgi") starched and folded into a stellated icosahedron.</item>
        <item>A bridal veil. It is stained with a fine mist of some faded violet liquid, and smells vaguely of raspberries.</item>
        <item>A box of cooking matches. There are no matches inside, but there is a recently-removed pinky finger, from the left hand of a woman. It appears to have been chewed off its hand.</item>
        <item>A pack of cheap playing cards in a small, worn cardboard box. Opening the pack and riffling through them reveals that the images on the face cards are all slightly stylized representations of the characters.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>