<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_supernatural_tome">
        <item>Wrapped in butcher paper and bound with twine is a manuscript for a book entitled "BEYOND THE VEILS OF SCIENCE" by "Dr. Harlo Y. Patten", dated 1971. It is actually a tattered photocopy of a low-quality dot-matrix printout. The author\'s name is an obvious pseudonym (and an anagram of "Nyarlathotep"), and little or nothing can be found out about the book\'s true origins.\n"Dr. Patten" presents a philosophical reflection on the meaning of modern physics, much like \'The Tao of Physics\' or \'The Dancing Wu Li Masters\', but informed with a sinister and oppressive Mythos sensibility. The book discusses the implications of relativity, quantum mechanics and non-Euclidean geometry as a way of thinking about the world, and demonstrates that human notions of morality and ethics are meaningless in the face of an empty universe ruled by random chance.\nCharacters becoming temporarily or indefinitely insane as a result of reading this book will usually manifest their disturbance either as a chokingly deep and pervasive depression, or as a variant of Quixotism: "referential mania", the belief that everything that happens, no matter how small -- the blowing of a dead leaf across the street, someone slamming a door, the shapes of clouds -- has a darker, hidden meaning.\n(SAN Loss: 1D6/2D6; Cthulhu Mythos +11%; spell multiplier x1, study time: 7 weeks, recommended spells: Create Gate, Call/Dismiss Azathoth)</item>
        <item>A handful of laminated pages in a cheap loose-leaf binder. Each page describes a minor ritual:\n1. Makes the caster more attractive to crows; they will follow him around, and may potentially pick up and return dropped items or harass attackers. Does not grant direct control; requires seven feathers from sever different species of carrion birds, a cup of the caster\'s blood, and a simple circle of wax.\n2. Dispels a recurring mundane nightmare. Has no effect on magical nightmares. Requires a largish vial of human cerebrospinal fluid (no more than a single body\'s worth), some objects relevant to the nightmare (underwear for showing up at school naked, empty bullet casings for war flashbacks, etc.) and a simple salt circle.\n3. A ritual for looking impressive. Requires five colors of chalk, four colors of candle, magnesium powder, and a large flat space to draw the circle. When performed correctly, everyone present at the ritual will come to regard the caster as an immensely powerful and puissant wizard, including the caster himself. Wears off after a few days.\n4. This page has been rendered illegible.\n5. A short phrase that, when spoken, lights the speaker\'s hair on fire. Labeled as causing small changes in the ambient temperature.</item>
        <item>"Cognitive Science and the Writings of Abd al-Azrad" - An obscure book that was one of the few titles published by a small press named Human Horizons Press, which closed when its offices burned down in the early morning of May 1, 1983. Research will disclose that the book\'s author, Jonathan Stellare, was arrested in connection with the fire, but committed suicide while in police custody. This book never actually went to the printers before the fire, but bound galleys were sent to several reviewers.\nStellare appears to have had access to a mostly-complete copy of Dr. John Dee\'s English translation of the "Necronomicon" in the preparation of this work. He draws parallels between the rituals that Abd al-Azrad describes and algorithmic descriptions of computer programs. Pseudocode and fragments of source code are included from one of Stellare\'s attempts to electronically re-create a worship service of the Outer Gods; a competent computer programmer who learned the spells from this book might be able to construct a program to aid in their casting (Keeper\'s option).\nUnfortunately, Stellare does not appear to have truly understood the significance of the "Kitab Al-Azif" and his explanations and descriptions are fragmentary, confused and heavily adulterated with New Age mysticism.\nBook stats: English, SAN Loss: 1D3/1D6, +5 Cthulhu Mythos, spell multiplier x2, recommended spells: Contact Nyarlothotep, Summon/Bind Hunting Horror, Summon/Bind Servitor of the Outer Gods, Study Time: 8 weeks)</item>
        <item>A first edition copy of the novel "Blindsight" by Peter Watts and a Baretta 9mm pistol in a thickly bloodstained plastic bag. It seems that the book has been read only a small number of times judging by the wear and tear done to the spine and pages of the book (bloodstains excluded). If the magazine of the pistol is extracted it is found to contain bullets but is short four or five rounds.\nThe flyleaf of the book bears the following inscription: "Whenever I find my will to live becoming too strong, I read Peter Watts." --James Nicoll\nThe corruption surrounding this copy of the book is subtle but inexorable: the story, while well written and researched, is also incredibly depressing as it makes an excellent case for the nonexistence of free will as we know it. The last several people who read this particular copy of the book shot and killed themselves with the same pistol in the same way. With each suicide the curse grew slightly stronger until the pair of book and pistol became a threat to life, limb, and sanity. If the Keeper is feeling merciful, 1/1D6 SAN.</item>
        <item>"Sideshow Freaks" - a 1984 picturebook of black and white photos from sideshows stretching back a hundred years. Disturbing in the conventional sense, investigators with sufficient Mythos knowledge may also recognise a ghoul, a Tcho-Tcho, and a Deep One (all in carnival dress) amongst the human freaks.</item>
        <item>A wooden box containing a 1\' long Tibetan prayer wheel made from rusted black iron. The wheel has not the traditional Om Mani Padme Hum prayer written on its outside but instead a strange swirling script unknown to mankind. [Anyone mounting the wheel on an appropriate spindle and spinning it in the clockwise direction will get visions of the darkness between the stars, and the ancient beings living there. Lose 1d4/1d10 SAN and gain 1d4 Mythos. Spinning the wheel in the counter-clockwise direct the attention of these beings to the one spinning the wheel and Summons either a Dimensional Shambler, a Byakhee or a Nightgaunt who drags him or her off to meet the beings in person.]</item>
        <item>One large capacity memory chip for a digital camera; the contents are a hastily taken set of photos of Gantley\'s "Hydrophinnae". The photos are of marginal quality having been taken with a flash and in some haste. Careful examination reveals a flashlight and a gloved hand in one shot. A time stamp indicates that these images were recorded a few months previous. The text is in Latin and is otherwise as per the Keeper\'s handbook.</item>
        <item>A Kentucky State Police evidence box containing: a paperback copy of Carol Mason\'s "Killing for Life: The Apocalyptic Narrative of Pro-Life Politics", thirteen 7.62 FMJ bullets in polythene wrap, a wooden-handled kitchen knife, a list of pro-life organisations and spokespeople in the Indiana-Kentucky-Ohio tri-state area, and a well-thumbed copy of Joachim Ferry\'s Notes on the Cthaat Aquadingen (Sanity Loss 1D4/1D8; Cthulhu Mythos +6%).\nThe previous owner of the items is currently serving a 56-year sentence in Kentucky Correctional Institute for Women for the attempted mass-murder of a Michigan family visiting Louisville last year. Claims the family was of "tainted blood" didn\'t go too well with the trial judge.</item>
        <item>A cheap paper folder with the Johns Hopkins University seal containing 1980s era computer print out (dox-matrix) of a lengthy text in English purporting to be "an invocation to Saddogowah", with phonetically spelled portions supposedly from Ojibwe. The text is obviously incomplete. (It is a partial copy of the spell "Contact Tsathoggua".)</item>
        <item>A series of photographs of the walls of a room. The once white walls have had words either scribbled on them in blood or etched in them with a sharp instrument. The rambling text is filled with obtuse, deranged, and often downright vague references to the Magnum Tenebrosum, Cynothoglys, Byatis, and, most disturbingly, Y\'golonac in a rather disturbing form.\n(SAN Loss: 1D10/2D10; +8 Mythos; Spells: Call Y\'golonac, Call Cynothoglys, Call Magnum Tenebrosum, Contact Byatis; 14 weeks study time)</item>
        <item>A copy of Robert Chambers\' "The King in Yellow." When first opened, every page will bear the text "IT IS A FEARFUL THING TO FALL INTO THE HANDS OF THE LIVING GOD" above a stylized Yellow Sign. SAN loss 1/1d6, or 0/1 if the agents have seen the Yellow Sign before. If opened again, all the pages are heavily water-stained and illegible.</item>
        <item>A college textbook, which seems at first glance to be a typical pre-owned Geology 101 book.\nThe geologic timeline in the front of the book has been annotated with the truth of the Mythos. Notes such as "3.8 bil yrs ago (early Archean): Settlement of Tsathoggua into caverns of N\'kai" and "350 mil yrs (early Mississippian): Cataclysmic surfacing of R\'lyeh, arrival of Cthulhu from Xoth".\nOther points are outlined in the margins of the book, but no spells or practical information other than pre-human history. 1/1d6 SAN, +3% Cthulhu Mythos (if believed; it is, after all, scribbles in a college textbook, the investigators could easily dismiss it as an obscure fantasy setting)</item>
        <item>A handwritten 1927 autobiographical text by Albert N. Wilmarth, folklorist and assistant professor of English at Miskatonic University. It tells of his investigation into the strange events following that year\'s historic Vermont floods...\n[Keeper\'s should give investigators Lovecraft\'s story Whisperer In Darkness. Cthulhu Mythos +4%, Sanity Loss: 1/1D4+1; Includes spells: Contact Mi-Go)</item>
        <item>A blood-spattered plastic binder holding a photocopy of the Revelations of Glaaki, Volume III. The copy seems to have been made in haste and is of poor quality.</item>
        <item>A wooden shipping crate containing an Cape Buffalo skull and tanned hide, there\'s a note on the hide reading "if you\'re reading this we managed to get it out of the country, keep it hidden." The hide has Dusseldorf\'s "Unaussprechliche Kulten" inked on the underside. The shipping manifest says it was shipped from Tanganyika in 1947.</item>
        <item>A rewritable CD with a single 15 minute .AVI video file ripped from a live broadcast by the Saudi-owned "Al Arabiya" news channel. The on-the-ground footage shows violent crowds during the Egyptian uprising of 2011. A group of two or three dozen young men appear to be praying and chanting in a manner completely separate to the other protesters, however; and their words seem to cause consternation among the crowd, which around the ten minute mark turns on them. A miniature riot breaks out within the broader violence before the video suddenly ends.\nViewers fluent in Arabic will be able to hear the group of young men chant not to Allah or freedom, but to the flaming god on Fomalhaut, Cthugha...</item>
        <item>A Marshall Island stick chart. The charts represented major ocean swell patterns and the ways the islands disrupted those patterns. It just appears to be sticks and shells. However, someone who knows how to read it will recognize that it carries a message. Deciphering it will teach the player a tribal version of Contact Cthulhu.</item>
        <item>Seventeen sheets of tracing-paper, each page containing strange curvilinear script rubbings. No other information is provided, but a successful Occult roll recognises the symbols as similar to those on the infamous Eltdown Shards. (A suitably versed investigator with a very high Cthulhu Mythos skill might also realise it is written Yithian).\nThe pages are rubbings of a "metal-plate" version of the Eltdown Shards proper, and if translated offers everything the original Shards did - spells and all.</item>
        <item>A roughly two hundred year old carved oak box containing an unbound fifty page illuminated manuscript in 13th century French, written in mirror writing. Reading it (assuming the investigator can do so) costs 2/1d6 SAN and gives 1d2 Mythos; it describes a process by which the reader may summon a creature "from beyond time and space" to attack his enemies.\nIf the investigator should be so unwise as to hold the manuscript up to a mirror a Hound of Tindalos emerges from the mirror and drags him into it.</item>
        <item>"The Vikings, Greenland and the Cult of Taranis" - a badly edited paperback, with pencil underlining of any occult portions of the text. Describes a Viking settlement in Greenland that was destroyed by what seemed to be a hours long lightning storm. Contains diagrams of complex runes that if correctly researched and reproduced, can attract lightning to the object they are carved into during storms.</item>
        <item>Type-written notes with instructions for the spell "The Black Binding"</item>
        <item>A three-ring binder labelled "Surveillance Photos". The contents of the binder actually change every time they are viewed; they always depict the exact location the binder was opened at, exactly six hours prior. The photographs are always accurate, and change even by merely opening and closing the binder.\n1/1d4 SAN loss upon realizing that the binder\'s contents have changed without rational explanation.</item>
        <item>A folder filled with crime-scene photographs, apparently a murder quite literally in the locker room of a Dallas police station. Around the body, crime-scene tape has been carefully and expertly arranged into the Yellow Sign, so that anyone viewing the photos will suffer its effects.\nAlong with the photos, the only other thing in the folder is a simple sticky note: "Investigation halted for now; do not let this happen again. -A"</item>
        <item>A modern reprint of Francis Barrett\'s "The Magus". Penciled on the inside of the front cover are instructions on how to cast "Bind Nightgaunt".</item>
        <item>A badly scorched and torn photograph of a humanoid figure seated in an armchair in a studio setting. Close examination reveals the figure to be other than human.\nAny viewer who correctly recognizes the figure as a ghoul loses 1d4/1d8 SAN; each night thereafter that person sees shadowy figures following him. No others can see these figures; if he attempts to confront them they disappear into the shadows. He loses 0/1 SAN every night; when his SAN reaches 0 he disappears, never to be seen again.</item>
        <item>Several coroner\'s reports on a series of deaths in Trenton, New Jersey, between 1989 and 1992. All of them list the cause of death as prolonged lead poisoning, although the coroner is unable to provide a good explanation as to how it occurred between these individuals.There are no recurring factors between the individuals, as they all come from different neighborhoods, ages, socioeconomic backgrounds, ethnicities, etc.\nPenned into the margins of several are what appears to be a somewhat deranged attempt to connect all the deaths in a singularly Mythos-aware fashion; however, even with the extent of the author\'s knowledge, no good explanation can be reached. A last page has been affixed to the packet, upon which is written only "...coincidence?"\nWhile no information can be gleaned on the cases themselves, the disjointed theories of the editor can be read for +1 Cthulhu Mythos.</item>
        <item>A beautiful and ornate hardback book entitled "The Ocean War: America\'s Seizure of the Samoas, 1903."\nA History roll will indicate none of the events (covered in extensive detail) in the book actually occurred; furthermore, there is no record of an Admiral Francis Buffby, the listed author. In fact, no record of this book can be found.\nIf the reader happens to flip to the last page, they discover a horrifying image: a coat of arms bearing the dreaded Yellow Sign has been painstakingly inscribed on the inside of the back cover in pen and ink; above it, in the same hand, has been written "PROPERTY OF HIS LORDSHIP HILDRED CASTAIGNE, IMPERIAL DYNASTY OF AMERICA".\nSAN loss for seeing this as appropriate; further sanity loss if a good part of the book has been read, as the investigator realizes he or she just read a piece of history as it exists in the tangled timeline of Carcosa.</item>
        <item>A paperback copy of the Young Adult book "City of Night" by Katherine Chance (as per The Unspeakable Oath, issue #16/17). Inside the front cover is a library card from Nathan Hale High School in Seattle, Washington. It has been checked out numerous times, most recently three years ago. (Book stats: English, +1% Cthulhu Mythos, 0/1d2 Sanity, x2 spell multiplier, Spells: Receive the King\'s Dreams. Created by James Holloway and Phoebe Kitanidis)</item>
        <item>A map of the local area. Comparison with another map of the same place reveals this map isn\'t correct; however, if one attempts to follow this map they will arrive at the destination this map says, even though all other maps disagree with it and say they should be somewhere else.\nAt some point along the way, the investigators have slipped into Carcosa, and cannot find their way around without the map. 1/1d8 SAN for realizing this, and 1/1d6 if the map is lost after that.</item>
        <item>A smoke-damaged but otherwise legible first-edition copy of John Horace Tobin\'s seminal 1920 publication on the supernatural: "J.H. Tobin\'s Spirit Guide - Being A Compendium of Gods, Ghosts, Spirits and Manifestations from Outside the Normal Realms of Existence" (1D2/1D6, Occult +5%, Cthulhu Mythos +4%, Spells: Contact Ghost)</item>
        <item>Three photocopied versions of the John Dee Necronomicon. The copies are of very low quality - perhaps not the first generation of copies made. Only about 10% of the original text is in the material, and much of it is illegible. 0/1d5 Sanity loss, +5 Mythos. 3 weeks to study.</item>
        <item>An old-style floppy diskette. On it is a .txt file containing a binary read-out of the Mythos tome Ocultus Deus in English translation. (Sanity Loss 1/1d6+1; Cthulhu Mythos +4 percent. No spells.)</item>
        <item>A file folder containing black and white contact sheets of a series of photos of frost on the inside of windows appearing to be in the same house. A magnifying glass will reveal writing scratched into the windows. The writing is mostly the ravings of person apparently held captive and tortured for a very long time, but it ends with "My soul takes its leave now, snatched up in the gelid talons of heaven," then relates the spell Summon/Bind Nightgaunt.</item>
        <item>A VHS tape labelled (in Russian) \'Men from Beneath\'.\nIf played, it shows a large group of soldiers with Kalashnikovs (their uniforms indicate they are Tajik Border Troops, but it\'s unlikely the investigators would recognize those). They advance slowly and cautiously across flat, sandy ground, weapons at the ready and pointing in every direction. At first, nothing can be heard or seen to justify this apparent paranoia, but suddenly the camera turns, and a large plume of sand (looking as though someone or something is digging frantically) is seen a few dozen yards away. The soldiers start shouting in Russian and fire wildly at the sand column. Instantly, several humanoid forms charge towards the group, and as they get closer they can be heard shrieking at an impossibly high pitch. An investigator well-versed in the Mythos will recognize them as Sand Dwellers.\nLanguage: Russian. Sanity: 1/1d6. CM: +2%.</item>
        <item>A blocky, ill-defined mimeograph scroll of the "Seven Cryptical Books of Hsan" printed along the back of a roll of wallpaper. Written in Classical Chinese and effectively complete (Sanity loss -1d4/1d10, Cthulhu Mythos +11%) the spells are unreadable.</item>
        <item>Fragments of papyrus in a plastic envelope. Written on the papyrus, which dates from about 500 BCE, is a prayer to "The Dweller at the Gate" in period Egyptian hieroglyphics. The prayer is a fragmentary version of the spell "Contact Yog-Sothoth".</item>
        <item>Seven full rolls of rather rough looking toilet paper. Someone has unwound them, filled both sides of every sheet with extracts from the book "The Revelations of Glaaki" in tiny, spidery handwriting, then rewound them onto the cardboard tube. (Average 28 weeks to study and comprehend; Cthulhu Mythos +8%; Sanity Loss 1D4/2D6)\nAn empty cardboard tube is nearby. Written on it in black ballpoint: "Sorry. Didn\'t know what it was til after I went. ~ F"\nWrapped in heavy green paper and tied with butcher drawstring are 270 unbound, typewritten pages.</item>
        <item>The document is labeled "Drums and Shadows; Georgia Writer\'s Project, Work Projects Administration; Mary Granger, District Supervisor; Savannah, Georgia; October 13, 1940; DRAFT."</item>
        <item>In addition to copy edits in red pencil, someone has penned in three spells: Snare Dreamer, Bind Soul, and Compel Flesh. The text itself provides +1% Mythos, +1% Occult.</item>
        <item>An 8mm film containing incontrovertible evidence of an otherspace.San dmg and Mythos skill are up to the GM.</item>
        <item>Surveillance video from a \'Kum &amp; Go\' gas station in Iowa. The grainy video, with a P.O.V. of the main entrance, is a series of still images with one picture being taken every two seconds. The footage is initially normal, showing the arrival and departure of perhaps a dozen late night customers. Suddenly a minivan swerves into view, colliding with a car parked at a nearby pump. Two men dressed in suits can be seen running from the minivan and towards the store entrance. As one man reaches the door the other turns and begins firing a pistol at an unknown target. General havoc ensues. In the final few images something violently shoves the van out of frame and causes the canopy over the pumps to collapse. If paused the thing can be seen only partially and then in only two frames. It is well over man-sized, and is a bipedal creature with a long trunk of ropey cables terminating in two or three tenticular limbs. Those who believe the tape is genuine (Idea roll to disbelieve) lose 1d2/1d6 points of Sanity. The date stamp on the tape is June 20, 2001. No unusual events or deaths can be uncovered in Iowa on that date.</item>
        <item>A collection of badly printed dual-language Bibles with faded leather covers, their alternate pages in terrible English. The first person to read one cover to cover - taking 1D6 weeks -, and succeeding at a POWx2 roll will be able to permanently understand that language fluently, though not speak or write it (realising this for the first time costs 1D3+1/1D6+2 Sanity loss).\nCopies in the set includes: Traditional Chinese, Dutch, German, Latin, Swedish, Korean, and a language that may be written Deep One...</item>
        <item>A large cardboard box full of mould-stained books, half-completed ledgers, and crumpled loose pages. It takes 1D3+1 hours to sift through the collection, but there is a 10% chance of finding a single Cthulhu Mythos tome (Keeper\'s choice) at the bottom.</item>
        <item>A copy of "Howard P. Lovecraft\'s Guide to New England Architecture," published by Miskatonic Press in 1950. The text covers architectural peculiarities of a number of New England towns. The author bio indicates that "Howard P. Lovecraft" is an architectural critic of some note, and was apparently alive when the book was published. Searching the Library of Congress or other database will find no record such a book was ever published.</item>
        <item>A copy of the transcript of a lengthy debriefing of \'Rosemary S.\', a student at a California music school, dated March 3, 2003. Her interrogator, apparently an FBI agent, focused questioning on the activities and whereabouts of Dr. Curtis Korman, a professor of Music and the interviewee\'s academic adviser. Great interest in taken in Korman\'s creation of an elaborate "musical performance piece" for a show consisting of hundreds of electronically controlled tuning forks and other tone producing devices in a 3 dimensional space. Korman called this "the Device" and, while forcing the interviewee to assist in its construction, he refused to explain his increasingly odd and paranoid demands. He was following notes written by someone named "Quantrill" though Ms. S. is unsure of who this is. She claims not to know of Dr. Korman\'s location, the location of his family, or of two other students and states that she was visiting a sick family member the night of Korman\'s show (at which there was an unspecified "accident".) Review of her discussion of "the device" can allow an attempt to assemble one, if an electrical repair, a mechanical repair, and a music skill roll are made. 0/1 point of Sanity, teaches spell "Summon Angel of Music".</item>
        <item>A worn copy of Computers for Dummies, 1989 edition. On the inside front cover it is stamped "Property ot T. Danforth". Written neatly into the margins and blank spaces throughout the book in red ink are instructions for building and operating a complex electronic communication device. Should these instructions be followed the resulting device will contact the nearest group of Mi-Go, with unfortunate results for the operator(s) and anyone else nearby. Should the book be destroyed or damaged it vanishes, reappearing intact 2d4 days later in a randomly chosen library.</item>
        <item>A 5" diameter transparent glass sphere. On the inside of the glass swirling text in an unknown language has been etched. Anyone attempting to read the text must succeed with a POW vs 16 roll to break away from the sphere or be trapped in a trance-state until passing out from dehydration a day or two later (or until someone removes the sphere from sight). Entering the trance-state also increases Cthulhu Mythos with 1% as some information about Yog-Sothototh is imparted.</item>
        <item>An unlabelled audio cassette tape. The A-side contains a bootleg twenty-one minute taping of the Dead Kennedy\'s live gig at the Deaf Club in 1979; the opposite side contains fifteen minutes sung from the Dhol Chants in a long dead language that seems to seep right into the listener\'s brain (Sanity Loss to listen 1D2/1D4+2, Cthulhu Mythos +3)</item>
        <item>A nearly new paperback copy of Cole Morton\'s "Is God Still an Englishman?: How We Lost Our Faith (But Found New Soul)". Careful annotations are penned-in, many of them long and rambling. Tangential to the text, most are about personal experiences with god, miracles, Anglican doctrine and the immortal soul, as well as ways of opening oneself to direct communion with the divine and angels.\nA successful Occult roll and 1D6+1 days of reading learns the spells Bless Blade, Candle Communication and Contact Great Race of Yith</item>
        <item>A VHS videocassette; something in cramped, illegible letters is written on the lable in green ink. If played, the grainy tape begins with a group of young people (late teens through twenties) gathered in a poorly lit room. A middle-aged man is talking to a frightened young woman, attempting to convince her that the body is not real and that no actual harm can come to her. She timidly repeats his assurances as she lays down on a mattress in the center of the room. The others in the room are chanting softly in some strange, guttural tongue. The older man places a revolver in the woman\'s hand, and she continues to mumble to herself as she works up her courage. Then she fires a round into her head. The chanting stops.\nAfter a few moments, the man grabs the woman\'s limp form and begins kissing her. On closer inspection, it appears he is actually breathing into her with great physical effort. Finally he backs away, exhausted. Within moments, the woman opens her eyes and rises from the bed, grateful and astonished to be unharmed. However, it is obvious that she still bears the grisly wounds of her ordeal, and the look in her eyes is disturbingly glassy and remote. Abruptly, the tape ends.\n(-0/1D3 sanity; +1 Mythos; Spells: none; one afternoon to study and comprehend)</item>
        <item>A pair of extremely thick manila folders, which, upon examination, appear to be semi-scientific experiments into devising a form of body armor useful against heat and electricity based weaponry, ostensibly used by the authors\' "enemies". The original conductors of the study are unnamed (though it seems to be someone other than Delta Green, apparently more a survivalist-style militia), and any reference to their identity has been blacked out as much as possible without making the dialogue transcripts confusing (i.e. "J------, M.L., Dr. F-----, etc.). Most of the tests in the first folder focus on modifying already existing items, like firemen\'s bunker gear, electrical lineworkers\' safety equipment, radiation suits, etc. The second folder seems to be a compilation of attempts to create a proprietary personal protective suit from scratch, and some of them show signs of being designed by individuals with genuine scientific talent, but all of them appear to have lacked the funding to ever make a functional prototype. Scrawled on the inside of the rear flap is a note in red marker: "J-----: this ain\'t X-COM. -Lt. N-------".</item>
        <item>A leather document case full of notes concerning the translation of a treatise on metaphysics written by Marquis De Sade, a copy of the original text is included. Starting as a scholarly examination but degenerates into chicken scratch notes about gates, possible other dimensions, and contact between the real and the realer still. The last few pages are composed of neatly handwritten instructions for a complex origami pattern. (1d4/1d8 San points if read entirely, +5 mythos points) the pattern is actually a set of instructions for a spell that calls a small group of outer being dwelling a maze-like other dimension.</item>
        <item>A collection of police reports attempting to interpret a series of bizarre deaths among insane asylum patients as the workings of a serial killer. In all cases the killer somehow entered the victim\'s cell without any breaches of security, brutally mauled the victim like a predatory animal, and fled without being seen. In some cases, DNA was found not belonging to the victim, but a strange blue-gray resin seemed to have been applied to intentionally contaminate any samples.\nShould an investigator familiar with the Hounds of Tindalos read the documents, they will undoubtedly recognize their handiwork, and lose 1/1d4 SAN. Otherwise, an ignorant reader will only lose 0/1 SAN due to the mind-boggling nature of the cases.</item>
        <item>A second-hand copy of "Wine For Dummies" where, on the inside front cover, someone has doodled a complex "crop-circle". If made to a suitable size (90 feet or larger) and set alight during a cloudless full-moon, the procedure automatically casts Contact Greys</item>
        <item>Xeroxed copies of extensive notes in English, detailed instructions about the chemical preparation of what appears to be some sort of spirit (and a potent one at that); and a coniderably larger sheaf of paper written in what is discovered to be an obscure form of cuneiform.\nAnybody taking the time to transcribe the cuneiform sheaf will discover a lengthy alchemical treatise on the preparation of the self for travel between the celestial and ethereal spheres, the strange dangers involved in such travel, and on such denizens as may help or hinder the dedicated planeswalker.\nSan loss: 1/1d4\nCthulhu Mythos : +3%\nStudy time: 20 weeks to translate and comprehend\nSpells : Brew Space Mead, Summon/Bind Dimensional Shambler\n(The original papers were found by Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives agents who raided what they thought was a large, illegal moonshine operation. Instead they found a building empty of everything except a sophisticated distillation set-up assembled from expensive laboratory glassware. The absence of anybody to arrest was particularly annoying and troublesome to the agents, since the building had been staked out for days, and nobody could have left the building without being seen. But all evidence pointed to the raiders having missed them by minutes. The only other evidence were the original papers found on a desk and a single remaining flask containing a small amount of a potent, golden spirit.)</item>
        <item>A series of 8 X 10 color photos taped together on a wall, showing a large Native American petroglyphs of unknown origin. Numerous post-it notes identify figures and symbols, sometimes uncertainly (such as "3 prayer sticks" or "Aldebaran?"). A large figure of a bent or broken-boned humanoid is simply identified as "Him". Careful study might allow this image to teach the spell \'Summon Hastur\'.</item>
        <item>A typed copy of chapters 5-8, 12 and 15 from von Junzt\'s "Unaussprechlichen Kulten." A post-it note is affixed on the front that reads "J, I HIGHLIGHTED THE GOOD PARTS FOR YOU, JUST LIKE YOU ASKED. -M." Anyone opening it will find that the "good parts" are all of the descriptions of the depicted cults most horrific rites and practices. However, reading everything but the highlighted portion can prove informative without being quite as psychologically damaging as normal. Sanity loss 1d6/1d10 (1d2/1d6 if ignoring highlighted portions), Cthulhu Mythos +11 percentiles (+6 if ignoring highlighted portions), average 16 weeks to study and comprehend (10 if ignoring highlighted portions). GM\'s discretion as to spells.</item>
        <item>A VHS video tape. "The Fire Dancer" is written in blue ink on the cover. A printed A4 sheet folded into the case details the specifics of where and when the tape was located and how it came to be in The Green Box. (The exact details are up to the Keeper)\nIf played the tape shows an outdoors scene shot at night. A naked woman is standing by a large campfire, she is apparently Caucasion and appears to be in her late twenties and is slightly plump. She exchanges some words with the person operating the camera, these are not distinguishable. A drum track, probably taped, starts up and she begins to dance. The dance lasts approximately five minutes the womans movements becoming wilder as the dance goes on. As the dance goes on the fires burns brighter and brighter. Suddenly the woman stops, looks towards the camera, then she turns and sprints away into the night. The camera turns around quickly, and a dark mass fills the screen - the recording stops aburptly. (+1 mythos point, 0/1d3 SAN to watch through.) If a more detailed analysis is carried out, probably using specialist equipment it will be possible to identify the language spoken on the tape, possibly regional accents as well, and identify the drum music being played. Enhancing the final images is also possible. (+3 mythos. 1/1d6 SAN if so done.)</item>
        <item>A worn, dusty scrapbook. The red-orange faux-leather cover is cracked, and the corners have peeled showing the cardboard backing. The 25 translucent pages contain large well preserved sections of human skin covered in tattoos. Many of the tattoos are variations on the same theme, a red and white snake wrapped around a skull. The preservation is perfect, the tattoos are colorful and vibrant, and the flesh looks almost alive. Touching the skin causes SAN loss 1/1D6 as the edges of the cold flesh squirm and ripple. A successful library use or history roll to trace the skull and snake theme will lead investigators to a series of newspaper articles regarding the \'Corpse Corps\' motorcycle gang that terrorized the area in the early 1970s. Elderly locals are extremely hesitant to speak of it, but on a successful fast talk roll they will whisper the story about the night long ago when old man Harvey ran screaming into the local bar, foaming at the mouth and gibbering about worms crawling under the biker\'s skins, and how he shot them over and over again but they wouldn\'t die...</item>
        <item>Blurry, second-generation pages photocopied from an unknown book and stapled together. The opener is headed "Chapter VI: Occult Crime in Western Europe, 1850-1945" (0/1 Sanity to read. +1 Cthulhu Mythos. No spells).</item>
        <item>A copy of Roger Ainsley\'s rare "Dreams and Fancies"; see the scenario of the same title from Kingsport for more information.</item>
        <item>Wrapped in black silk, a beautiful gemstone-inlaid cover binds a 16th century heretical interpretation of the Islamic Quran. The text is in Classical Arabic and equates Allah with Tulzscha. (SAN 1/1D3+1 - double for fundamentalist Muslims; +3 Occult; +3 Cthulhu Mythos; +1 Arabic; Spells: Contact Tulzscha)</item>
        <item>An un abridged version of the necronomicon discussed as a teenage girls diary with rainbows unicorn stickers. Braking the seal of the book summons a demon keepers choice.</item>
        <item>A copy of the film "Dirty Harry," with a video rental listed for Port-Au-Prince. At the 56 minute mark, someone has replaced the footage with a shaky mobile phone video of strange dark creatures shooting across the sky in a woodland scene. There are several people running around trying to shoot the creatures. The accents of the people are Caribbean, and a knowledgable investigator will recognise the language as Creole. The video ends when a claw appears and grabs the filmers head with a sickening crunch.</item>
        <item>A leather-bound book with the title: "Per Viam et Clavis". While it seems to have been printed in the 19th century no author or printing company can be found. The text is in badly written Latin and anyone reading it will get the general idea it is some sort of religious text about wheel-shaped angels being gates to other spheres. [After a few pages the reader must make a POW vs 16 roll. Success means the reader can continue to read the rather rambling text unhindered. After two weeks of study the reader gain Mythos skill +2%, and lose 0/1d3 SAN. A failed roll means the mesmerized reader starts to read the text aloud, and then shout it. If not stopped within 4 rounds the reader suddenly fades away and is replaced by a random previous reader who failed the POW roll. This new arrival disappeared 1d100 years ago, and has lost (1d6+ number of years lost) SAN. Anyone returning from such a disappearance can only describe his experience as "freezing cold and grey clouds".]</item>
        <item>"Ils Papyri d\'Ylarnec", 1822 French translation of the Ilarnek Papyri (-1d2/-1d3; +3 CM)</item>
        <item>A series of twelve home-made pornographic film reels shot in 1932 by a wealthy land developer named Donald Cardiss, featuring his friends, a nephew and his daughter. The films were made in Cardiss\' home for distribution among a close-knit circle of \'cinema enthusiasts\' in semi-open defiance of the authorities while he was awaiting trial on an obscenity charge.\nThe contents wouldn\'t be considered particularly racy by today\'s standards, being spliced together from scenes of unattractive naked people staring at the camera in drink- or opium-befuddled complacency, or having unenthusiastic sex in twos and threes. The most interesting moment is when one girl who\'s sampled too much of Cardiss\' inducements over-balances and slides right off her partner, knocking herself unconscious on a coffee table.\nThe bumping and grinding in the foreground is just a distraction, though. Set up behind the participants and carefully framed in every shot are a series of canvas dropcloths crudely painted with erotic symbols. The symbols are texts, disguised by a simple substitution code which protects them from casual viewing but wouldn\'t pose a challenge to anyone familiar with the basic concepts of cryptography.\nThe texts are spells, more than a dozen of them, in haphazard order. Many of them mention Y\'Golonac. Most simply don\'t work, but a few are genuine.\nCardiss himself appears only once in the entire work, at the start of the first reel. He is fully clothed and looks directly at the camera, mouthing what could possibly be a long poem. None of the reels have sound or subtitles but a lip reader could, with difficulty, make out a chant calling on the viewer to \'make a weapon of the flesh\'.\nIt isn\'t clear who Cardiss was trying to pass his knowledge on to, but the making of the films contributed to his conviction on the obscenity charge, and during a three year prison sentence he appears to have had a change of heart. He spent his remaining years before dying of a heart attack in 1938 trying to re-acquire and destroy all the reels.. There were too many copies made, though. Some still existed though, like these dozen found who-knows where before being stored in the Box,\nSan loss: 1/1D6\nMythos knowledge: +1%\nStudy time: 4 weeks\nSpells include: Shrivelling, Hands of Colubra, Wither Limb, Wrack, plus six incomplete and three that don\'t appear to have any purpose.</item>
        <item>An 8mm film entitled "Lost Spaces". There is a typed note inside a small manila envelope taped to the outside of the film canister. The note explains that the film was produced in 1954 in Santa Barbara by a film student named Charles Duransky. The black and white film depicts a young woman (credited as Wilma Thomas) being followed by a figure in a white cloak. The cloaked figure is always shown behind the young woman as she travels across various landscapes. In one scene the figure reaches for the girl, the girl turns to face it and stretches out her arm to rebuke the cloaked figure. A close up of the girl\'s hand shows that her palms have been painted with stylized eyes. Once shown the "eyes" the figure turns from the girl and leaves. The film ends with the girl staring into the camera. There are no film credits . If the investigators research the director his records show that he was committed to a mental institution in 1965. Duransky died while committed in 1972. Wilma Thomas, the actress in the film, is now a retired grandmother living in Florida. If contacted about the film she will laugh and recall Duransky as a paranoid art school boy who drank and smoked too much marijuana. She will explain that Duransky felt the film would become the first in a series of "messages" to the world. She has not spoken to him since completing the film and is unaware of his mental breakdown and death. If the investigators make a successful occult roll they will discover that the "eyes" are simple warding devices. A week after viewing the film, the PC\'s will be haunted by dreams of being followed by a cloaked white figure.</item>
        <item>A dusty book entitled Things To Do In The Dark: A Fun and Sinister Book For Enjoyment. The book\'s pages are entirely blank until the lights turn off upon which reveal instructions for a summons, a seance, and constructions of portals. The name of the author of the book is no where on the cover.</item>
        <item>A scroll with instructions for casting the spell Summon Star Vampire.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>