<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_supernatural_misc">
        <item>A pair of shock paddles that have "Boo Doo People Murder People" engraved on the handles that when used cause a random corpse in a 100 feet radius to be revived but in doing so makes the user sleep for 2 days</item>
        <item>Everything in the Green Box has been neatly arranged on long wooden tables and labelled...in Aklo.\nIf the investigators recognize it as such, 0/1 SAN loss.</item>
        <item>Fluttering about the top of the Greenbox are several small iridescent blue butterflies measuring from 7/8 - 1 1/4 inches. Any natural history or biology related skills can be used to ID these as Xerces Blues. The species went extinct in 1941; a positive ID will cause the investigator 1/1D4 san loss. If attacked the butterflies will be killed easily as they are quite delicate. If left alone they will continue to flutter at the corners of the ceiling silently.</item>
        <item>An ancient locked steamer trunk, opening it will show it contains a heavy wrought iron cage with a mummified human hand in it. The hand will scuttle around in the cage and snap at anyone who places their fingers near it. If provided with paper and a pen it will write out portents of the future.</item>
        <item>A crudely made and heavy set of metal plate armor with an accompanying literal bucket helm. It would take a strong person to wear it, and it limits vision.\nThose who do put it on find it renders the wearer completely immune to any physical attack or hazard that hits somewhere above the belt. Between the old bloodstains and numerous divots on its surface, the scratched letters "KELLY" can be made out.</item>
        <item>An iron cage, 2\' high. Inside a ratlike creature squats and watches whoever opens the Green Box with malignant intelligence shining from the eyes in its shockingly human-like face. It will not speak. The cage and the area around it is quite dusty, pointing to it having been there for months, if not years.</item>
        <item>A rolled piece of linoleum. If examined, there are two concentric circles with a diameter of 3 and 4 feet respectively in the middle, of some dark substance. Between the two circles are a number of Arabic words and letters and a number of wax blotches. The whole thing stinks of sulfur and looks to have been peeled roughly from a wooden floor.</item>
        <item>A clay vial, which is market "Dragon Blood" in German. Undoing the wax seal and examining the contents reveals a substance which looks like blood, only is bright red, does not coagulate under normal circumstances, and is several degrees higher than human body temperature.\nThere is enough in the vial to soak one body part such as an arm, or the chest, or the back, in the blood. If done so, the area covered by the blood will experience a stinging, burning sensation, and be permanently stained with a reddish color, and become immune to all damage from mundane weapons. However, should the blood be drunk, or otherwise enter the body, the person will rapidly heat up and burst into flame from the inside. But, if poured on the tongue of a person, they will gain the ability to speak to Birds, as if speaking their Native Language. Realizing you can speak to birds is 1/1d4 SAN. Actually talking to one for the first time costs 0/1 SAN.</item>
        <item>A black body bag containing a set of burned skeletal remains. A Medicine or Forensics check identifies it as near-human, but not human. Mythos check will identify it as Ghoul remains. 1/1d4 SAN</item>
        <item>A poorly-preserved paw from a monkey of some kind. When an Agent sleeps while holding the paw, one or more of their wishes will be granted, but in a dark and twisted way to the Keeper\'s discretion.</item>
        <item>A small metal strongbox, of the type sold in hardware stores in the 1980s, for storing valuables. The box is unlocked; whoever opens it first finds its key inside. As long as he is alive and retains the key the box behaves normally for him, but anyone else opening the box finds it empty. Any items they place in the box vanish the moment it is closed; where they go is left to the imagination of the Keeper.</item>
        <item>This apartment\'s kitchen has a deep freezer, and in the deep freezer, underneath a pile of microwavable TV dinners whose freshness dates expired some time ago (safe to eat, but stale-tasting), is a very heavy glass jar with a heavy stainless steel lid screwed down tightly. Within the jar is a pinkish object covered with frost; whenever observed in a frozen state, it appears to be have the shape of one of the Platonic regular solids--a tetrahedron, cube, octahedron, dodecahedron, or icosahedron, different shapes on different occasions, though it never changes when viewed directly. A note taped to the lid says "DO NOT OPEN! DO NOT ALLOW TO THAW! NOT KIDDING!" It\'s up to the Keeper to decide what it actually is. It can\'t be a small shoggoth because those don\'t freeze, but beyond that, well, one supposes that if it were to thaw and escape it would be mobile, hostile, and very, very hungry--and possibly immune to mundane weapons.</item>
        <item>One full aerosol spray can of SPF 20 sunscreen. Any attempts to apply the sunscreen to naked human flesh results in 1d3 acid damage. Anyone who has been sprayed with the sun screen hears the voice of the Can, begging people to spray it, and must make a 0/1 SAN check upon first hearing the Can speak. The Can never runs out of spray....</item>
        <item>As someone opens the Green Box a vaguely greenish cloud of noxious gasses drift out. [Anyone caught in the gas (Dodge roll to avoid) takes 1d4 HP damage and loses 1d4/1d6 SAN as horrifying visions of being dragged down to the ocean floor and devoured alive by tentacled monstrosities flash through their brains.] A small roman amphora can be found broken inside the Green Box, images of octopuses covering the ancient clay.</item>
        <item>A heavy oak coffin, chained shut with 3/8" steel chains and secured with multiple padlocks. Occasional thumping sounds can be heard from the inside.</item>
        <item>A large Tibetan mandala is drawn out in the middle of the Green Box\'s floor in multi-colored sand. In front of it someone has spelled out in the same sand: "NO BREAK CERCLE"\nSo long as no one enters it, or alters the circle\'s integrity, the mandala manages to contain the very angry Flying Polyp swirling within...</item>
        <item>A single, and uncharacteristically large, Russian Matryoshka doll, which has been glued shut. Any investigators who successfully open the doll will discover a finely ground powder. Analysis of the powder will determine that the substance is, in fact, the processed remains of the body of one of the PC\'s. Carbon dating proves ineffective in determining the age of the doll, suggesting it has been made in the future....</item>
        <item>3 Class II Tactical Armor Vests (2 Medium, 1 Large) in Black - shot to hell, the large is scored by huge claw marks and blood stains.</item>
        <item>A human head, perfectly preserved in a jar of some clear, viscous liquid. The liquid does not stick to flesh, and if the head is removed, none will cling to it. However, if removed, the head will open its eyes and begin shrieking at the top of its lungs. It can only be silenced by putting it back into the liquid or by high amounts of damage. SAN 0/1 to see the head, 1/1d6 if pulled out.</item>
        <item>A small canvas bank-bag filled with some number of soft and flat things that appear to be scraps of fabric. In the crate next to it is skinning knife/gut hook that has traces of blood on it. Scrawled in marker on the bag is "Don\'t Look!" (Inside are 39 scraps of human skin, each tattooed with the Yellow Sign - there is evidence that attempts have been made to burn them with no success. They are indestructible, and this fact will net an additional 1/1-2 San loss in addition to seeing any of the various Yellow Signs)</item>
        <item>The complete print of the original cut of Fritz Lang\'s Metropolis, including the "lost for ever" scenes. Including an unreleased scene where a ghostly figure in tattered robes overlooks the fall of the city. The figure is coloured in yellow on the film itself and will appear on the screen in yellow. Despite the film being black and white.</item>
        <item>A blister pack of 12 glow sticks. When cracked, they do not seem to emit light, so much as absorb the dark. Tendrils of shadow seem to peel off of the surroundings and snake towards the glow stick before disappearing into it. Each stick lasts 30 minutes. According to the package, they are of Malaysian make.</item>
        <item>On a neatly desk located in the middle of the room is a square box wrapped in tin foil measuring roughly 8 in" long 8in" wide and 4 in" high, placed on a bundle of newspapers. On the box is a yellow sticky note with a hastily etched warning "do not open for any reason". If the box is opened there is a lone 3 by 3 photograph placed face down. If flipped over and looked at by any living creature there soul is ripped out of there body, leaving behind a paper thin husk of what the creature previously was, additional any creature living or non living loses 50d100 sanity( this includes elder gods and great old ones alike, at keepers discretion)\nThe stack or news papers report the photos property\'s and 3 husks in varying stages of decay( non of which are human keepers discretion) players lose 5 sanity per husk.</item>
        <item>A freshly cut rabbit\'s foot. Upon further inspection you will find out that it is the back left foot.</item>
        <item>A small round metal disc, about 3 cm across and 1 cm thick, engraved with an intricate pattern. The metal appears to be silver, but is harder than steel. If inserted into a sealed container it appears to temporarily stop all decay processes in the container. However, if it is removed the contents of the container rapidly decay (at ten times the normal rate) into useless debris and/or slime. Anyone who sees these effects loses 0/1d2 SAN.</item>
        <item>Strange squiggly signs cover the walls, floor and roof of the Green Box. They seem to have been drawn with some milky white substance which is more resistant to liquids and physical harm than it first appears. If the Green Box is of the walk-in type anyone entering it is unable to leave (when moving to the exit it appears to be farther and farther away (Lose 1/1d6 SAN). If the Green Box is of the storage box cellType items in it (including the signs) are always out of reach for those outside it (Lose 0/1d4 SAN). The only way to break the effect is by destroying at least one-third of the signs (this may have to be done by destroying the walls itself if you\'re on the outside of the Box). Of course, there may be some good reason for the signs to have been put there for the first time ...</item>
        <item>A heavily modified 8mm video camera. It has a variety of lenses, filters and supplemental lights for the aperture. The films shot bear almost no resemblance to what the investigators would see, showing odd geometric patterns with stars moving before them, and occasional tentacled things swirling about, instead of (for instance) the safehouse.</item>
        <item>The Green Box contains a hungry Ghast.</item>
        <item>A small glass jar with a plastic lid containing a clear jelly-like substance. If the jelly is rubbed on an object it becomes impervious to attack by Mythos creatures; if it is rubbed on a living being it renders them impervious to attack by Mythos creatures, but does 1d4 damage to the creature until it is removed (it can simply be wiped off with a cloth).</item>
        <item>A weird white spider-like creature, about 1" across, in a jar of formaldehyde. No information is provided about the creature (a brood of Eihort) but the jar (for Matthew\'s Lemon Curd) can be identified to be of British manufacture, probably from the early 1960s.</item>
        <item>A human hand and portion of a forearm (wearing a broken handcuff), re-animated with Dr. West\'s formula. It will attack anyone who opens the Green Box. The thing is slightly stained with a bluish color and looks to have been ripped from the original corpse. The thing has crawled about the interior of the Green Box, leaving a sticky trail behind. The other half of the handcuff can be found attached to a pipe or other fixed point.</item>
        <item>A tightly-sealed jar containing two liters of fine blueish-grey dust. If sifted through, it will be found that the dust is nearly frictionless and none of it remains on the fingers. If anyone thinks to cast Resurrection on the dust, it reform into a famous figure from history (GM\'s discretion as to whom). There is a 10% chance that some of the dust has already been taken and that an attempt at Resurrection will instead summon up "onlie the liveliest awfullness."</item>
        <item>A small dropper bottle of black liquid that moves like mercury. Certain mythos creatures [up to GM discretion which ones] will attack living beings tainted by the liquid.\nComes with bundles of notes on the dark methods used to create more</item>
        <item>A Cambodian-style fetish necklace, made of dried human fetuses. Known as "smoke children," they protect the wearer from any physical harm. One has to doubt the sanity of anyone who chooses to wear it, though.</item>
        <item>A Polaroid camera. Regardless of what the camera is actually aimed at, all pictures show the same view: A landcape of blackish rocks covered with some sort of blue-green mold or grass, under a purple sky with two suns.</item>
        <item>A small glass cylinder, with a cork placed in it tight. A note next to it says "Caution: Contains Screams".\nAny Agent inexperienced or dumb enough to try the vial by opening it is treated to the most blood-curdling and ear-splitting scream they\'ve ever heard or will hear in their life. The scream continues as long as it is open. All within earshot lose 1/1d4 SAN. The person holding the vial also needs to make a POW x5 roll, or drop the container. Should the container be dropped, and the vial shatter, the scream reaches a mind-shattering crescendo before dying out, inflicting 1d3 damage on anyone who can hear it. Double this damage in confined spaces or areas with good acoustics. Characters exposed should also suffer penalties to listen checks. If the vial is recorked, and opened again, to see if it works twice, they agent is once again met with terrifying scream. They expect it this time, so only 0/1 SAN loss on all future openings, and not dropping the vial becomes POW x7.</item>
        <item>A trapdoor set into the Green Box floor leads to the Dreamlands.</item>
        <item>A card board cut out of chuck Norris.</item>
        <item>The inside of the Green Box is frozen solid, as if the temperature has dipped well below the freezing point for an extended period. This may well have destroyed some items in it (especially things containing liquids). As the Box is opened the inside of it will slowly thaw.</item>
        <item>A small drawstring Nike bag, containing a portable black hole. Anything placed within the bag cannot be retrieved. Realizing the existence of such a contained phenomenon is a 0/1d4 SAN check. If informed, A-cell will request that the bag be mailed to Dr. Pappu, A DG friendly at the University of Texas in Austin.</item>
        <item>The body of a large gray earth worm measuring 27 feet long and 4 feet wide. It is labeled Mongolian pet worm, there is also a conch shell that when blown the worm looks up and begins to act like a normal worm would.</item>
        <item>A large plastic evidence bag containing another, slightly smaller, evidence bag. There is also a post-it note on the larger bag: "Yes, it\'s the fucking evidence bag!". [Anything, including living flesh, touching the inside of the smaller evidence bag start to rot/rust/corrode at a rate of 1d4 HP each minute (even if removed from the bag) until destroyed or the d4 rolls a 1.]</item>
        <item>As the Green Box is opened sea water rush out of it, as if it has been filled to the brim (for large Green Boxes this may well be a painful experience for whomever opens the Box). The water is filled with (dead) deep-water fish and rotting crustaceans. Somewhere in the mess left behind can also be found the thoroughly dissolved tome responsible for the manifestation.</item>
        <item>A compass whose needle appears to change randomly throughout the day and night. If studied, it will be found that it is always pointed in the direction of the star Aldebaran.</item>
        <item>A plastic storage bin sits in the back of the Green Box. Inside there is a warning on top to not open it. If the players open the box it will reveal a standard car battery. If removed from bin the battery will disappear and reappear at random, at the agents\' place or work and at home. And in the oddest locations, it will continue to haunt the agents until it is returned to the bin or used in a vehicle.</item>
        <item>A wooden sundial, about six inches in diameter, with time marked out in an unknown language. Anyone attempting to use it for its intended purpose will quickly discover than the sundial\'s gnomon casts no shadow. 0/1 SAN.</item>
        <item>A mannequin whose face resembles one of the agents. Which one is up to the GM. If the agents leave the mannequin in the green box and later come back, the mannequin will be wearing identical clothes to the agent it resembles. San loss at the GM discretion.</item>
        <item>The bleached and varnished skull of a Deep One.</item>
        <item>The Green Box and everything in it, except for a small empty area, is covered in a thin layer of translucent slime. The slime smells vaguely of chlorine and is slightly radioactive (which may lead to some trouble for Agents touching it and then entering areas monitored for radiation). It will evaporate if exposed to sunlight only leaving a low-level radioactive patch behind. The empty area in the Box indicates something approximately skull-sized has been removed from it.</item>
        <item>Against a wall lies a old mattress. When moved aside it reveals an opening to anouther room. Problem is that room can\'t exist( the wall\'s other side is a hallway). How was the opening created &amp; what is inside can be an adventure in itself.</item>
        <item>A package wrapped in stained brown paper and string. As someone opens the Green Box a decayed human arm wriggles free from the package and attacks the nearest target. [The Arm has 4 HP and its horribly strong fingers squeeze for 1d3 HP, Impaling Hits apply as the fingers find something painful to grab onto. It has 25% chance to hit, but cannot move faster than walking speed except for short (2m) bursts once every three turns.]</item>
        <item>The Green Box is haunted by a ghost. Whether it\'s attached specifically to the Box or to something in it is up to the Keeper.</item>
        <item>An eleven-foot long, oak pole. It\'s charred and chipped, but remains strong. If an agent holds the pole, he gains an innate sense for detecting ambushes and traps: if one is forthcoming, he will smell burnt wood and have a headache. The pole itself is indestructible; no mortal being could ever break it, and immortals would have an extremely hard time as well. At the base of the pole, in small, neat lettering, is the following: "The only memory I have of the Old Times. Treat it well, traveller, for it has treated me well. Signed, G."</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>