<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_weird_tome">
        <item>A once-white pamphlet, now faded and tinged with yellow, devoid of any other colors or pictures. On the front is a single word in verdana font: "Skin". Opening the pamphlet reveals nothing inside but the following paragraphs, again in verdana font:\n"Skin Donation: You have been selected!\nWe of the Love Corporation, LLC., have been in the process of abducting lone travelers on America\'s interstate system for the past eighty years. We are the main cause of missing persons in this country, and have held the championship title for nearly fifty years (save, of course, for a brief period in the 70\'s when that bothersome Satanic cult stalked the lovely denizens of Vallejo, CA., and nabbed nearly two-hundred souls. What a summer!).\nIf you have responded correctly to the fear catalyst that we\'ve infiltrated into your vechicle through the air conditioning system, then you are sitting in a little patch of sand on a service route, just off of I-85. Please stay right where you are, as a highly trained Love Corporation representative is approaching your location as you read this very pamphlet, to collect all of your skin. Thank you very much for the donation and have a wonderful day!\nSincerely,\nJ. G. Waldenfont"</item>
        <item>A tome of the DM\'s choice is in a box at the back of the room. The book has been booby-trapped by a M84 stun grenade. Failure to check the box while cause the stun grenade to fall out and go off. This was left as a safety measure by the last cell. Whether or not they realize the trap is there is up to the GM.</item>
        <item>A partial photocopy of the dissertation "William Canning Webb, 1831-1919". The copied section concerns Webb\'s visit to western Greenland in 1863 and his study of a peculiar Inuit group who practiced human sacrifice and worshiped an otherwise unknown deity known as Cout Oul\'u.</item>
        <item>A 100-page typed script, stapled together. The title is "A Night At the Opera" and it is supposedly by "D-Cell". It appears to be a Play or TV show, but notes in the margins and corrections with red pen in multiple handwriting makes it a bit hard to follow. It seems to be an attempt at Black Humor, surrounding the slightly fictionalized antics of the aforementioned D-Cell as they investigate a cult linked to an opera house. They win, but not after one of them is eaten "humorously" off-screen by a Shoggoth and another goes insane and decides to marry a slightly friendlier than normal Deep One. 0/1 SAN Loss. Agents who still have a sense of humor left may appreciate it. On the last page is a sticky note that says "You realize you can\'t publish this, right? -D."</item>
        <item>A small black address book. There are several entries on the first few pages; all of them are womens\' names and all addresses are within 30 miles of the Green Box. Nearly half of the names have a red check mark next to them. Research uncovers that every name checked off is that of a missing person.</item>
        <item>A stack of Penthouse magazines, with every female face pasted over with cut-out photographs of fish-heads. Their cold, ichthys eyes stare with eerie lust.</item>
        <item>Several pages of loose-leaf notes evidently written by a clinically insane man, chronicling his attempts to figure out if goldfish can live in fishtanks filled with human blood. He describes in graphic detail how he abducted, murdered, and drained the blood of two prostitutes, but seems to express far more guilt over the fact that his experiment\'s subjects did not survive in the blood.</item>
        <item>A large book bound in eland hide, with no identifying markings on the cover. The title page proclaims it to be "An overview of religion among West African natives". The emphasis is on the more outre cults, including some which worship entities resembling Shudde M\'Ell and Nyogtha. Recognizing the resemblance costs the reader 1/1d4 SAN and imparts +1 Mythos.</item>
        <item>A large scrapbook with "Where The Bodies are Buried" in red Sharpie on the cover. Inside are annotated maps, scraps of newspaper articles, and ambiguous jottings on the disappearance (and impromptu burial) of seven people in the local district over the last four years. Whether this was part of a Delta Green op is left unsaid, but it\'s obvious A-Cell likes agents to keep a regular watch on the burial sites for reasons unspecified...</item>
        <item>A stack of 20 loose notebook pages, bound in butcher twine. The paper itself is very old, heavily smoke- and water-damaged, and charred around the edges. A small note on top of the stack reads:\n"Kolya,\nI found these in an alley next to your apartment, after the fire. I hope they are still of use.\n- RJ"\nThe pages are covered in writing - in both English and Serbian - and mathematical formulas. The majority of the work is either smudged beyond recognition or outright indecipherable, but it appears to be a completed work on a unified field theory. The final page does not seem to be related to the others, but appears to be the schematics for a hovercraft of some sort.</item>
        <item>An old, extremely yellowed newspaper clipping that appears to be from a Nova Scotian publication. The article covers a strange incident at an unnamed office building in which every single person inside inexplicably climbed to the roof and jumped to their deaths, in the middle of the business day. Eyewitnesses report the office workers simply stepped off the edge of the roof totally calmly, almost casually, one by one in the order they reached the rooftop. No explanation is offered by the paper as to what could have been behind this mass suicide.</item>
        <item>A simple leather bound book. Embossed on the cover iais the image of a double headed eagle and the words "Imperial Guardsman\'s Uplifting Primer" The book contains various tactical information for an unknown military</item>
        <item>A collection of reel-to-reel tapes, dated 8/15/62 to 9/29/62; twenty-one hours total. Audio is of the congregants of an unknown church (know or English to identify Appalachian accents) engaged in a pseudo-Christian service using snake-handling. Frequent mentions are made of "Saint Yig", "the Scaled Redeemer", and "the Blessed Serpent". 0/1d2 points of Sanity to listen.</item>
        <item>A softcover book, THE SPACE PEOPLE-TOP SECRET TRUTHS by Prof. Vance Cragun, published in 1990 by "Truth and Light Books, Inc." 230 pages, with a creased spine and tattered cover. The author claims to have insider knowledge connecting the Philidelphia incident, Roswell, Shag Harbor, various UFO sightings, Area 51 and stories of underground alien/gov\'t bases in the US Southwest together. In the final chapters dealing with said bases, sentences and whole paragraphs have been highlighted, underlined, circled and various notations have been scribbled in the margins in pen and highlighter.</item>
        <item>\'A walking guide to the Fens of England\' Written in 1904 by U.I. Penwith.</item>
        <item>Further investigation reveals that neither the auther or any of the places mentioned can be found in any database.</item>
        <item>A yellowed laboratory notebook dated 1962. Will Brandley,the previous owner, was conducting studies on a material from a mine shaft in West Virginia. The substance is noted as being, "viscous, acidic and yellowish in color".</item>
        <item>A copy of the King James version of the Bible, but with a text that diverges radically from the standard version. Everything continues as normal until the Binding of Isaac, which ends with Abraham sacrificing Isaac as a human sacrifice and God awarding Abraham with "favor beyond that of thy fellows." Cannibalism features prominently--David ritually devours Saul\'s heart to become the new king, and the Last Supper is depicted as a cannibalistic feast. The Book of Revelation is also different, depicting the awakening of long-slumbering ancient gods or demons who then scour the Earth clean of human life in a horrific bloodbath. The book does not contain any mention of printing date or year or a dedication; the first page is the beginning of Genesis. 1/1d6 SAN if read in its entirety, 10 weeks to study and comprehend.</item>
        <item>An album of 60 black and white photographs. The photographs, taken in what appears to be an arid location, possibily in the southwestern United States, are of the tracks of an unknown bipedal creature, larger than a human. A pickaxe placed next to one of the tracks suggests the creature\'s foot was over 16" in length. In one photo an Arizona highway sign is partially visible that places the source location for the photograph to be somewhere between Ganado and Keams Canyon.</item>
        <item>A hardback of Sarah Palin\'s biography "Going Rogue" - but the woman on the front cover is not Sarah Palin. It might be excused as a mix-up at the printers, if it weren\'t for the fact every photograph in the book - from childhood to adulthood - is of the woman who\'s not Sarah Palin. The text is otherwise exactly the same.</item>
        <item>The City Life/culture section of the local newspaper dated 1d6+1 days in the future from when it is found.</item>
        <item>A run of imported pornographic "manga" comic-books. All fifty-seven trade-paperbacks appear to tell of plucky schoolkids trying to save the world from a stark and unrelenting tentacle-laden eldritch horror, but the language definitely isn\'t Japanese and the last issue is missing.</item>
        <item>A children\'s coloring book pertaining to astronauts and the Moon; the second half of the book\'s pages are covered in hastily-copied technical diagrams depicting both American and French ICBMs, which are almost certainly classified information.</item>
        <item>A piece of pink construction paper, on which is drawn, in crayon, a child\'s rendering of Cthulhu. It is signed with the child\'s name, aged 5.</item>
        <item>A VHS copy of a 1998 horror film titled "Shadowmancer". It is a low-budget direct-to-video piece of schlock, about 90 minutes long, centered around an evil modern-day sorceror who uses his powers (portrayed with laughably cheap F/X) to kidnap victims (usually women in revealing clothing). He takes him to his secret underground lair to offer as sacrifices to the nameless "demon god" he worships and draws his power from. Only a hardboiled cop (played by a has-been soap opera star) and an occult expert (played by a woman who wears low-cut blouses and mini-skirts) can stop him. If an experienced and knowledgeable agent watches the film, they\'ll note that while many of the "mystic" symbols that decorate the walls of the sorceror\'s lair are obviously made up, some of them are Elder Signs. Also, during an incantation at the climax of the film the sorceror mentions Yig, Yog-Sothoth, Hastur and Ithaqua. Furthermore, tucked into the VHS jacket is a note from "R" addressed to "J" suggesting that "J" should check into the film\'s production company, Red Lightning Films Ltd. "R" writes that of most of the films Red Lightning had produced during the 90s were low-budget action movies, that Shadowmancer was the company\'s first and only horror film, as well as the last movie they ever produced before going bankrupt. "R" seems to think some investigation of Red Lightning might be worthwhile.</item>
        <item>A dog-eared old paperback copy of J. R. R. Tolkien\'s "The Silmarillion" with various words and passages in the text marked in red highlighter. Reading through the text and trying to find a pattern to the selected portions causes a whanging headache and 0/1 SAN loss.</item>
        <item>A manga called "My Maid is an Alien Blob", staring a cute looking maid.\nReading the manga, the maid turns out to be a Shoggoth. Anyone who finishes the book with Mythos Knowledge loses SAN.</item>
        <item>A small, slim English edition guidebook entitled \'A Guide to the Palace des Tuileries\' produced by a French publisher in 1982 as part of a series called Paris Historique. The book contains many attractive contemporary color photographs and a relatively small amount of explanatory text.\nThe text has accumulated very few mistakes in the translation into English. It describes the rooms of the Palace and their contents, and the history of the building until about 1978. After some time one of the investigators remembers / reads in another book or on the internet / is told that the Tuileries Palace was destroyed in 1871, during the suppression of the Paris Commune.</item>
        <item>Half a dozen VHS tapes labeled "Property of Springfield Police Department" and each sealed with evidence tape. The tape on all six has been cut. If watched the videos contain six hours of uneditted footage from two different camera men on a film team from the "COPS" television show. Five hours and thirty minutes into the tapes the team, following a pair of officers, enters an alley after getting reports of a possible crazed drug addict from locals and finds a man in filthy ragged clothes bent over another man laying on the ground, When commanded to put up his hands by the offices it becomes clear that the filthy man has been eating the stomach of the man on the ground. Both officers open fire and one of the camera men flees. The filthy man staggers but does not fall and hisses something difficult to hear and which causes the tracking on the VHS to shift. Both officers then turn and being shooting the camera crew, causing both cameras to be dropped and face, respectively, a wooden fence and a brick wall. Both camera tapes play out for twenty-five minutes and while the view never changes the sound of dragging can be heard mixed in with city background noise. 2% Cthulhu Mythos and 1/1d6 SAN for watching the tapes in their entirety.</item>
        <item>A safe deposit box containing a series of letters (dated from 1947 to 1962) written to one Elmer Stephens, the editor of the Waterloo-Cedar Falls Courier from a Conrad Henried, of Glasgow, Iowa. Henried reports a series of vague but apparently prophetic dreams to Stephens; most events are local in nature but a few are more globally significant, such as the Inchon landings. It is unclear if Stephens replied to these letter, but each has a few newspaper clipping attached to them, indicating when these visions came true.</item>
        <item>A stack of music magazines dating from 1993 onwards, including NME, KERANG!, Music Monthly, various college rags and numerous home-made fanzines. The only thing in common is that all feature articles or reviews on a cult New York band called "Charnel Dreams".\nA Spot Hidden roll notices that in every magazine, in the background of a picture completely unrelated to Charnel Dreams, lurks Stephen Alzis. Here he is in the crowd at the Kerang! Awards; over there smiling in the press-pit at the Brit Awards; right in the corner, impeccable at Burning Man; altogether worth a 0/1D3 Sanity loss...</item>
        <item>An Oxford box filled with typewritten pages that seem to reports of surveillance on the routes of various pedestrians through the city streets, how long to the second they stayed in this or that store or restaurant, and so forth.</item>
        <item>A red folder covered with Department of Energy classification notices, FBI confiscation records, and even a DoD Top Secret clearance. Its contents are incongruous for such a flurry of government activity: crude sketches of a bizarre, spherical animal which (according to an apparent middle-schooler\'s description of biology and nuclear physics) would be able to sustain cold-fusion reactions within its digestive system by simply eating uranium.\nEven a glance should be enough to tell an educated individual that everything about this is incorrect, making the federal panic seem even more surreal.</item>
        <item>A piece of notebook paper, crumpled up and tossed in a corner, on which someone has quickly sketched out a rough family tree. Although the male lines are shown, only the females names are written out, from \'Bertrade\' at the top, to \'Gerberge\' at the bottom. A successful History roll will reveal that this is the family tree of the Carolingian dynasty, circa 752 - 987 CE. The name "Hildegard of Vintschgau, 758-783" is highlighted, circled and double underlined.</item>
        <item>A crumpled piece of notebook paper, reading "The CIA...DEA...EPA...FDA...FAA...all ending in \'A\'. Not coincidence. Never trust the bastards ending with \'A\', they run the world behind the scenes..."\nThe paper is wrapped around an unlabelled VHS tape, which, if played, shows a confused-looking man stumbling around a public restroom. He seems to be completely oblivious to the cameraman. Judging by his facial expressions and walking pattern, he seems be heading towards a bathroom stall, suddenly forgets what he was doing, paces around somewhat drunkenly for a few seconds, remembers, walks towards the stall, then forgets again in a seemingly unending loop. This continues for fifteen minutes, and then a door can be heard opening, and a deep voice from behind the camera says, \'Turn it off.\'</item>
        <item>A crudely hardbound copy of the Varo-Jessup papers. Upon cursory inspection this will appear to be a copy of the actual Varo-Jessup text as described in the Delta Green corebook, but multiple people have added their own annotations to the text, effectively expurgating any useful information by adding what appears to be well-meaning but incorrect misinformation.</item>
        <item>An entire giraffe skin inside a plastic box. Appearing to have been cut across the middle, it has the entire text of one tome (Keeper\'s choice) written on it. A yellow Post-It note stuck on top of the box reads: "You don\'t even want to know. Trust me."</item>
        <item>A recent model Panasonic Toughbook 31 ruggedized notebook sits atop a cheap beige folding table connected to a frayed network cable. A successful computer use check will show it is part of a secure DG subnet hosted by a hacked cell phone tower. The cable connects to a transceiver and directional antennae concealed in a plastic crate on the facility\'s roof. The username and absurdly long password have been texted to one of the cell members by Cell-A. Numerous YouTube shortcuts on the desktop link to a series of truly bizarre videos titled "Unarius: The Arrival", produced by a Southern California religious group called the "Unarian Academy of Science".</item>
        <item>A copy of the Book of the SubGenius - ISBN 0070622299 - Normal in every respect (well, as normal as the Church can get), except that it\'s mirror-reversed. All of it - covers, text and pictures. So are the Ye Olde English handwritten annotations...</item>
        <item>An untitled book containing no writing, instead each page is illustrated with images of people with unseen faces, engaged in an unknown and wild dance. As the book continues the figures start to blend and at the climax, they combine into a hideous morass.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a thin leaflet showing the notes for a short piece of flute music named "In His House". Some of the notes are not of the regular type.</item>
        <item>A audio casette tape. On the label someone has written "THE THING ON THE SLAB" in bold black letters. If played it starts off with a man\'s voice identifying himself as a county medical examiner performing an autopsy on a hit-and-run victim. The speaker then goes on to give the time and location of the autopsy. The victim is descibed as female of indeterminate ethnic background. The examiner notes that the victim was found naked at the side of a road and that her eyes are of different colours. As the autopsy proceeds the examiner notes peculiarities in the corpse and anomalies which are hard to explain in conventional pathology. These are noticed at first with surprise, and then alarm, and then it seems as if what the examiner is seeing is beyond his ability to comprehend. The last heard of the examiner\'s voice is his alternately calling upon God to protect him and arguing that "the thing on the slab" is proof that God cannot exsist. The examiner\'s voice cuts off aburptly and nothing else is heard on the tape until it runs out. (+1d3 mythos points. -0/1d4 San.)</item>
        <item>A file folder bearing the label "Anomaly 6, California". The contents are two publicly available satellite photos (one from 1992, the other 2004) of a hilly area of Southern Monterey Country, CA, northeast of Samson. Both maps show roughly the same patch of rolling hills, small farms, and the occasional larger building with one critical difference. The second map shows one of the small valleys, about 1/2 across, has been the subject to some sort of significant event. The soil has an ashen appearance while the surrounding trees have been burned (careful inspection notes a radial falling of trees away from the center of the area) and toppled. A short report summarizes a few investigatory telephone calls to local authorities who indicate that the area suffered a small fire during a particularly violent thunderstorm. Whoever complied the notes indicates they did not believe this story to be true.</item>
        <item>A Mead composition book that was used as a journal. The contents detail the slow descent into insanity of the author (no name is given) a young woman living in Boston in 1998 (according to the few entries that were dated). The author, clearly somewhat unstable to begin with, took up residence in a decrepit house, renting one of the squalid rooms there. Aside from complaining about the filth, the vermin, and the unresponsive landlord, she soon begins to claim that voices, particularly an old man\'s voice, keep telling her to harm herself. A pair of burning eyes also appeared to her in visions. Her writing grows erratic and nonsensical, interspersed with brief lucid passages. The final one of these is her will, dated August 20, 1998; she bequeaths her few possesions to her brother Andrew. The last line reads "Must go, knife waiting".</item>
        <item>A paperback book: "Genetic Revival: Your Way To A New Body", by Marvandas Yul. The book contains a 30-day program claiming to raise the body of its adherent to the "pinnacle of human evolution". The program involves ingesting specific combinations of over-the-counter medicines together with the reciting of advanced "Yogic Mantras", which looks suspiciously like incantations to a suspicious eye.</item>
        <item>A slim, black book, written in English, cheaply bound and very tattered, with brown pages crumbling at the edges. On the title page, it is dated London, 1904, and authorship is attributed to someone calling himself "rother A. Poole, Opener of the Gate". The title of the book is "The New Revelation Revealed to the Elect".</item>
        <item>The actual text is quite strange, but boring, lots of borrowing from the book of Revelations and certain nastier parts of the Old Testament, with other sections apparently based on the works of people ranging from Charles Darwin to the philospher Jeremy Bentham to spiritualists and occultists like Madame Blavatsky; the result is a strange and turgid hodgepodge. The final summing up of the hundred or pages is a caution, or rather summons, to the "Faithful Brothers and Sisters of the Elect" to withdraw from the world and settle together in a "Secluded Spot" at the first oppurtunity.</item>
        <item>A decade-old hentai comic book titled "Flush Twice" in a stylized tentacle font. The cover art depicts a bright white cake with a red candle for every year on the agent\'s next birthday. The protagonist in the comic is obviously the agent, who engages in one debauhced sex act after another with all kinds of aliens, mythos creatures, sculpted scat, food, and anime-cute waitresses/waiters. The comic concludes with the agent diving down a toilet (see the 1996 movie "Trainspotting") into a fairy-tale underwater city populated by friendly sea monkeys. The final frame reads, "Life after the flush?"</item>
        <item>A December 1996 issue of Playboy Magazine. All of the eyes have been cut out of the models and various words have been underlined or circled.</item>
        <item>A pirated DVD of "Snoop Dogg\'s Hustlaz: Diary of a Pimp." The case has a poor quality .jpg copy of the cover and the DVD itself is a generic region 2 disc. The back of the cover has a Google Earth map of San Fernando Valley with red x\'s corresponding to various porn producers. On the disc: there\'s no menu, the sound is unaltered throughout the production, but 25 minutes into the feature the video switches to 16 minutes of low-production quality and highly criminal snuff porn. While it\'s difficult to discern, there appears to be something vaguely human (albeit with six arms) in the background urging on the infernal rapes, which is all the more disturbing with Snoop Dogg\'s continued, stoned rambling. Then, the regular feature resumes: it\'s a mix of hardcore pornography and music video featuring rapper Snoop Dogg. The unadulterated video was originally released in 2002, a year after Snoop Dogg set the trend of mixing his signature Doggytstyle hip hop with porn.</item>
        <item>This is an old, yellowed, somewhat ragged-looking spiral-bound notebook, and on the cover is written "P-CELL WAR JOURNAL, 1989." Within are many pages dated from January to August of that year, in which an agent PETRONIUS has made many entries, sometimes including little doodles and caricatures of other P-Cell members. Reading it, you notice that PETRONIUS is sarcastic and snarky, with a bitter sense of humor, describing the day-in, day-out interactions between the members of P-Cell as they worked out of this safehouse in 1989. There are terse descriptions of Nights at the Opera--one that February was an operation against a "New Age" group calling itself "The Noble and Benevolent Order of Our Lady of the Rainbow," which turned out to be a Shub-Niggurath cult. There are notes about stakeouts and investigations of other local New Age groups that turned out to be just New Age groups, and investigations of bizarre local violent deaths that resulted in the apprehension of a mundane, but still SAN-drainingly bizarre, serial killer, and the investigation of a group of "Satanists" who, as it turned out, were sacrificing neighborhood pets and possibly homeless people to something that may or may not have been a shoggoth in a cave in a wooded area outside of town (killed the cultists, dynamited the cave, don\'t know if they killed what was in it, but a backpack nuke wasn\'t available). There are also hilarious, if uncomfortable stories about doing little mundane favors for local Friendlies (two words: prom date). Then there appears to be a long dry spell for most of the summer, in which most of the investigations did not pan out directly, though the cell leader seemed to think there was something to be gained by what PETRONIUS calls "snipe hunts in the sewers." Last entry, though, is undated--it looks like the same handwriting, but rather unsteady, and just says, over and over, "they see all and wait betewen the walls, no, OUTSIDE, and they watch us and wait and they\'re going to come for us"</item>
        <item>A book from the from the apparently benign religious group that is handed out by its members on every street corner. What makes this copy different is the number of footnotes scribbled in by an unknown writer.\nThe notes talk about the deeper meanings and dark secrets of religion\'s practices and beliefs detailed in the book With each page the secrets becomes more disturbing and writing becomes more unhinged. The notes sometimes belittle the religion\'s members as stupid dupes that deserve their eventual fates and at other times make frantic pleas for the reader to help those in the group.</item>
        <item>A pocket monograph "Heterodox Polynesian Religion, with particular reference to aquatic fertility rites" (University of California, Los Angeles; 1985 by Shin Joo-Yoong). 0/1d2 Sanity to read. +1 point Cthulhu Mythos</item>
        <item>Collection of confidential reports submitted between January 1963 and December 1990 to various Avation Safety Boards in the US, Canada, UK and Denmark. A handwritten note reads: "recommend pull files March 2000, DBR" The reports are of unusual observations made by pliots of transatlantic flights while crossing the ice over northern Canada and Greenland. Most of the reports describe patterns of lights seen on the ground. (These are the four countries which control the most northerly transatlantic crossings, Greenland falling under Danish control for much of the period.)</item>
        <item>"An original copy of Lewis Carrol\'s \'Alice\'s Adventures Underground.\' Inside the manuscript, every instance of the word \'cat\' is underlined in red sharpie."</item>
        <item>A dog-eared book containing excruciatingly detailed anatomical drawings of unknown flora and fauna. Forensic analysis reveals that the ink used is a substance like human blood.</item>
        <item>A small binder filled with pictures of the Russian mystic Grigori Rasputin. A few pictures at the back show a dilapidated house in the Russian steppes. The final picture shows five men holding machine guns and assault rifles, and a handwritten caption reads: "Lets see if the bastard can survive this!"</item>
        <item>A sheaf of typewritten pages being held together by a paperclip. The pages look and read like they\'re from early drafts from Hunter S. Thompson\'s "Fear and Loathing on the Campaign Trail \'72". Skimming through the pages reveals among the material that defintiely didn\'t make it into the final book, a brief passage that has been circled in red ink, an almost absentmindedly scribbled question mark next to it:</item>
        <item>"We were waiting in the hallway outside the rally when I got The Fear. I thought it might be the speed coming on top of the ether but my teeth weren\'t grinding like they usually do. This was something different.</item>
        <item>I saw one of Nixon\'s flunkies standing nearby, giving me the eye, just another young guy. I\'ll rack any lawyer with a shot to the nuts if I think it\'s needed but this one was different. Just another kid in a cheap suit, but with that Hitlerian air of certainty and righteousness so many of these Nixon Youth carry. It could have been the drugs, but I swear the bad mojo rose off of this guy like vapors. I turned away to wipe the sweat out of my eyes and when I looked back, he was gone. Maybe he\'d never been there.\nJesus, I needed some whiskey. I went to find the bar."</item>
        <item>A rolodex filled with numbers, which include local cleaning services (Normal and Crime Scene), Veternarians, Occult or New Age bookstores, Fortune Tellers or other psychic hotlines, gunsmiths, a small computer repair company, a hardware store, a locksmith, and an army surplus store. Also listed are several private numbers, with names or notes under them, which indicate these people to be discreet doctors, money launderers, bookies, arms dealers, or other useful criminals.</item>
        <item>A dog-eared and coffee stained paperback copy of "Dark Mission: The Secret History of NASA" by Richard C. Hoagland. In addition to the usual highlighted passages and underlined phrases that one would expect of a book owned and abused by a fairly serious conspiratologist or UFOlogist, some pages are also littered with sticky notes and index cards scribbled with ascension/declination/timing triats of satellites in orbit and radio frequencies that a little research will confirm as being used by NASA and the NRO for satellite telemetry.</item>
        <item>A small film canister, containing what proves to be a Warner Bros. Road Runner cartoon. The colors are extremely faded, and noticeably pyramid-shaped rock formations can be seen in some of the backgrounds. Two and a half minutes into the cartoon, as Wile E. Coyote is chasing the Road Runner along a desert highway, he abruptly catches the bird by the neck. He comes to a stop and turns toward the viewer. The film stops at that point.</item>
        <item>A dog-eared stack of photocopies, containing a portion of Wassermann\'s "The Occult Foundation" (+2 points Cthulhu Mythos,-1d2/-1d4 points of Sanity to read, 10 weeks of study). Highlighted portions discuss a theory that the "fabric" of reality is weaker at specific "nexus" points.</item>
        <item>A thin and badly glued paperback: "Illuminati vs. The Crown: The Army of the Third Eye", published by a small neo-Nazi and millennialist press in St Petersburg, Florida.\nThe text is a synopsis of American Lee Coleman\'s founding of the Army of the Third Eye terrorist organisation in Britain, its attacks on British interests, and the eventual arrest and destruction of the group in 1997, all tied into a racist screed of Anglo-American Jewry, a secret war between Washington\'s Illuminati and the "Aryan" Merovingian bloodline, and such. Nonetheless, the facts relating to Coleman and his group are accurate and pay particular attention to contemporary reports of trepanation and "infestation", though in this case explaining it in terms of brain-washing...</item>
        <item>A stack of greenbar printout (18 inches wide, patterned with alternating pale green and off white bars, of the sort that would be run through a very old-style dot matrix printer) containing an autopsy report for one William Milton Cooper of Apache County, Arizona, pronounced dead 6 November 2001. The autopsy report is about what one would expect of a 58 year old man being gunned down by police officers (the medical examiner documented three gunshot wounds consistent with the sort of weapons and shot placement training characteristic of Arizona police officers at the time). The noted cause of death, however, states that massive cervical trauma (rupture of the spinal cord running through the C1, C2, and C3 vertebrae) was the actual cause of death.</item>
        <item>A ring-binder labelled "DOUBT #23A" containing long-distance surveillance photos of various couples in sexually compromising positions. Obviously blackmail material, each has the location the photograph was taken, along with a time-stamp and date.\nThe first investigator going through the collection stumbles upon a picture of someone looking remarkably like their significant other performing a graphic sex act on an unknown individual (Sanity loss 1/D2+1).</item>
        <item>A small faux-leather notepad containing the real name, address, telephone number, social security number, family members etc. of eleven Delta Green agents and seventeen friendlies. This includes the reader\'s own information...</item>
        <item>A large binder containing a complete blue-print of the Winchester House. On a post-it note on the first page is witten: "Took 6 months! Not a fucking trace of anything supernatural.".</item>
        <item>200-page file last updated in 1967 . Entitled " "Where Is He Now?" dedicated to Rudolf Hess - which contains hitherto unseen reports from both Axis and Allied sources on his life, medical history, psychological profiles, etc . It also contains a series of " aged " photographs purporting to show how Hess would look in 1970, 1975, and 1980 . The pictures bear zero resemblence to the prisoner who resided in Spandau Prison</item>
        <item>Ten vintage, obviously aged issues of the pulp fiction magazine \'Weird Tales\', dating from the late 1920s and very early 1930s.</item>
        <item>The \'weird\' thing is that none of the contents of these copies match up with the listed contents of these particular issues. None of the authors or stories in the table of contents are known \'Weird Tales\' authors and research will show they were never published in \'Weird Tales\' or anywhere else. None of them seem to have existed.</item>
        <item>The common trait for these copies is that each contains a story by a "Jason Kalavich" who like the other authors appears to never have existed.</item>
        <item>Kalavich\'s stories and their themes seem strangely familiar to some readers, with their themes of cosmic horror and ancient entities.</item>
        <item>These stories feature titles like "The Sleeper in the Tomb", "The Hour of Cthulhu", "The Shadow from Outside", "Fragments of a Forbidden Book", "The Parchment of Doom", "The Goat of Mendes", "Beneath the Black Sun", "The Sorceror and the Nymph", "The Curse of the Mound" and ""Dawn of the Shoggoth".</item>
        <item>A ripped and stained paper grocery bag containing a large stack of swinger\'s magazines catering to the local community. The sections of personal ads in the back of each issue are dog eared and densely scribbled on. About a third of the advertisements in each issue are circled with red feltpen. Some of the circled ads are thickly crossed out as well. If the agents decide to investigate the crossed out names, they will be known to some agents of other cells as having been involved in Mythos-related activities (usually procuring meals for ghouls).</item>
        <item>A thoroughly blood-stained photocopy of Yukio Mishima\'s short story "Patriotism". In the margins, someone has written excepts of dialog from the movie "Men Behind the Sun"</item>
        <item>A softbound English language copy of the Chinese "I-Ching", an ancient text on astrology and divination. Bound to the book with rubber bands are fifty yarrow stalks, three Chinese coins, and a five-dollar bill.</item>
        <item>A Roughly worn 13x21 cm red moleskine journal. The pages are filled with check lists, Poetry fragments, poorly drawn doodles, sketches of floor plans for various buildings of obviously fictitious origin. The hand writing is blocky, all caps, and hard to read. The contact details in the front of the book are covered with broad strokes of permanent marker. The \'return reward\' line is visible with \'$25\' scribbled in.\nCloser scrutiny will reveal that the owner is most likely named \'Tony\' and he was a third year student at Iowa University in 2004.\nThis Journal was gifted to him on his birthday, August 24th, and the last date recorded is June 5th.</item>
        <item>The ten last entries are devoid of check lists, doodles, or poetry. His hand writing is much cleaner, and he speaks of his plans to Leave Iowa U and apply to \'Tintron College of Architectural Design\' No such College exists on record.\nThe checklists mainly consist of homework assigned through out the year, And club meetings.\nThe Doodles usually consist of sprawling spirals and squares with no obvious meaning or purpose.\nThe poetry is free form and of middling quality, Close inspection will show that every 5th poem will be about a character with same name as the first agent who picks it up. The last poem of this type details the Character\'s death at the hands of a angry gorrila, aged 98.\nThe Floor plans start out as random ideas for a TTRPG John wants to run. It\'s setting seems to be the modern day. A very close inspection will show that the floor plans are functionally identical to the childhood homes, Schools, and other frequented buildings of all agents in the group.</item>
        <item>A stack of post-it notes stapled together to form a small book. The \'book\' has 665 pages, and a final post-it note lies just to the side of the rest.</item>
        <item>The top note has a small curving line in red sharpie close to the center. The next note has a similar line just below the first one. If an agent flips through the pages quick enough, the lines form up to make an eye with a small piece missing.</item>
        <item>What happens if the final note is reattached is up to the GM.</item>
        <item>A diary that apparently belonged to a 16 year old girl named Miriam in 1994. The contents are inane and typical, but are written backwards on every other page.</item>
        <item>A copy of Robert Anton Wilson\'s novel "ILLUMINATUS," in which each instance of the word "fnord" has been highlighted with a yellow marker, with brief cryptic notes scribbled almost-illegibly in the margins each time.</item>
        <item>A hand-written notebook filled with just the word "ZALGO" over and over again ...</item>
        <item>Dozens of loose pages ripped out of an English-language copy of "Lonely Planet - Kathmandu". Each sheet has been stamped "DESTROY AFTER READING - NOFORN".</item>
        <item>A coroner\'s report originating from Orange County, California, which concerns the autopsy of an unidentified John Doe found on the side of a state highway. The cause of death is listed as cardiac arrest, but the coroner reports at length the anatomically impossible amount of blood the man\'s body contained. While most human beings possess less than five liters, this coroner indicates an amount in excess of twenty was drained from this corpse. He also notes that it actually spurted from the body with such force as to knock a scalpel out of his hand at one point, and advises referral of the case to a medical research team immediately.</item>
        <item>A set of autobiographies of the local magnate. They are heavily annotated and look like they\'ve been read over and over again.</item>
        <item>A handwritten copy of the Gospel of Judas Iscariot</item>
        <item>Instructions for the performing of a lumbar puncture procedure (aka a \'spinal tap\') hastily scribbled on Holiday Inn stationary. The procedure is accurate and correct though it outlines how to use everyday items to perform the procedure.</item>
        <item>A hand written account of a visit by three UFO conspiracy theorists to RAF Woodbridge. The account tells of them driving around the perimeter of the base photographing "MOD Property" notices. It then goes on to tell of their arrest by plainclothes security officers. The account ends with "then they shot us all and buried us in an unmarked grave."</item>
        <item>An ordinary recipe book, with file cards detailing assorted mundane recipes. An observant investigator will discover two of the recipe cards include very exotic ingredients. One card entitled "Traditional Stew" includes diced human liver as a main ingredient. The other recipe is entitled "Carne Agrippa" cites that grilled human thigh meat and chopped human bladder should be fried in fresh butter. The investigator should make a San roll or suffer 1d6 San loss.</item>
        <item>A sealed plastic bag marked "Item 27, J. Winifred Coll.". Inside is a small volume in a worn leather binding, stamped "Ye odd and lurid beleefs of the common peeple." (sic). The volume appears to have been printed in London in the mid eighteenth century, although no other record of either author (one Tobias Primm) or publisher (Folsom Street Binders) exists.\nThe volume is a lurid account of several odd sects and cults in the vicinity of London of the time. All but one seem innocuous. (Keeper\'s fiat what that one actually is).</item>
        <item>A worn yellow legal pad. On it are two texts - one in a very unsteady Urdu and the other a penciled-in English translation. The text is a portion of an account given by an unknown party recounting his brief visit to a location he calls \'Azhure Banehpal\', an ancient and forbidding ruin in central Asia. For reasons unclear in the text, he was one of two survivors of the party that reached the place. His discussion of his group\'s trip there is detailed enough to allow others to plot repeat his trip.</item>
        <item>A handwritten copy, in Aramaic, of of what seems to be the proclamation of Ashoka at Kandahar. This is written on a sheet of paper which appears to be torn from a Federal Supply Service notebook. There are multiple spelling errors, and an alteration is made to the sixth line which is not present in the original. The alteration describes the victory of the righteous army against the horde of the great r??k???asa and the subsequent banishment of said r??k???asa to Patala or the underworld.</item>
        <item>A battered VHS tape. It is marked as "Vol. 12, #98." The tape shows a grove of trees standing for what is marked in the corner of the screen as two weeks. On the 15th day, however, one of the trees appears to uproot itself and move towards the camera. As it approaches the camera, other trees in the background can be seen twisting around, as if to watch. The rest of the tape is static.</item>
        <item>An autographed copy of \'Life, the Universe and Everything\' printed in 2003</item>
        <item>A sketch book with a series of nude sketches of two nude models, one male and one female. The sketches go from artistic to sensual to pornographic to monstrous. Or the other way around. It\'s hard to tell which side is the beginning..</item>
        <item>A hardback copy of the book The Day Lincoln Was Shot by Jim Bishop. The inside is stamped "Property of the Texas Schoolbook Despository".</item>
        <item>Various accounts ledgers stolen from a bookkeeping company in Chicago. Much of it seems to relate to payments going in and out of an Asia-America air-freight transporter called Tiger Transit.</item>
        <item>"Book of Humble Prayers" - a thin black booklet seemingly of children\'s prayers, circa 1850. However, the children depicted in the line art drawings seem to have a disturbing otherworldly look, with knowing eyes and leering faces. Reciting the prayers leads to unpleasant dreams of eating human flesh and scrabbling through black earth (possible SAN loss on those of faith).</item>
        <item>A printed list of 200 US Military officers, from different branches, cross-referenced against their bank accounts. A succesful Library Use roll will reveal that they all are in some way connected to confirmed or rumoured war crimes. A succesful Accounting roll will show that they all received large sums of money, distributed in several smaller transfers, from classified sources both before and after the atrocities. Several of them have also died and disappeared in the last few years.</item>
        <item>A slim handsome leather-bound journal stamped with the name "Jas. Smythe" containing a record of his travels and encounters, most of which were banal. After the investigator examines it it vanishes the moment he takes his eyes off of it, reappearing in his pocket, his vehicle, or his current residence, at the Keeper\'s whim. It now bears his real name and contains the true version of his travels and encounters. Attempts to destroy or discard it prove fruitless; it always reappears in his possession and remains so until his death, at which time it reurns to the Green Box to await its next owner.</item>
        <item>The instruction manual to an unreleased flat screen HD TV. It has all the standard set up information, but also 15 pages on what to do if the TV begins to display strange images, including a chess piece, a green hamburger, a fox corpse and a bloody pentagram. The instruction for each scenario is simply "Unplug the device and burn it."</item>
        <item>Seeing the Light: A neon green, drawstring catalog envelope with the Japan Air Self Defense Force and the Hamamatsu Airborne Early Warning Group logos. The envelope has been sealed with tape bearing a bar code and caution that special permission from the Minister of Defense is required to open it. Contents include both the original shorthand flight log and transcription copies of a Boeing E-767 with an E-3 mission package flying into the North Pacific on 4 December 2005, 1250 Zulu time. The Intelligence Officer reports the cabin filled with purple light for two minutes and he felt the urge to open the bay door to attempt to fly away, an urge his crew mates shared and one attempted to act upon. Post-flight medical examinations and quarantine observation of the crew show each member reporting the ability to see "strange contours" and "glow" of varying intensity around them. An MRI caused the captain have a seizure. Eventual consultation with a foreign ornithologist, Dr. Dominik Heyers from the University of Oldenburg, determined the crew members had developed physical and biochemical features akin to migratory birds: they could see electromagnetic fields. And all felt the pull to travel south.</item>
        <item>A slightly dented and creased cardboard box of the sort copier or printer paper comes in. The box is filled with several reams of single-sided printout of posts from a Livejournal community called "Wikileaks Kink Meme," and features erotic fanfiction about publically known members and associates of Wikileaks as well as many and sundry people whom are suspected of being part of the Wikileaks team in a covert capacity. The fanfic (mostly slash) is about what you would expect, it\'s all over the spectrum of quality (ranging from claw-your-eyes-out bad to discreetly-save-it-for-later engaging) and paraphilia. 1/1D6 SAN, four weeks to read the whole archive, two weeks to skim for the high points.\nMost interesting of the whole morass are a handful of stories that prominently feature members of the (suspected) Wikileaks team engaging in fantastic black ops to gather classified information among the hot and heavy sex. Friendlies will probably not make head nor tail of these stories but Delta Green operatives may recognize missions that they were a part of or had peripheral involvement in. These stories are circled with red feltpen and annotated with such legends as "WTF?!?" and "This is a breach of security! Who wrote this????" The exact stories so noted are left to the fertile imagination of the Keeper.</item>
        <item>Alan Baker\'s "Invisible Eagle: The Hidden History of Nazi Occultism" (+2 Occult; No Sanity loss). A handwritten German cribsheet of all the salient points has been carefully folded between page 251 and 252 (an extra +1 Occult; No Sanity loss)</item>
        <item>An NYPD evidence bag for a rape investigation. It contains well-read copies of "Making Out In Korean (Revised Edition)", Neil Strauss\' "The Pickup Artist: The New and Improved Art of Seduction", and Beneveniste\'s "Diagnosis and Treatment of Sociopaths and Clients with Sociopathic Traits".\nThe case does not appear to have gone to trial.</item>
        <item>A map of a local park with 3 Xs marked by red sharpie ink. If the spots are investigated, they will find 3 dead drops containing a ziplock bag full of cocaine, a cigar box containing 5 %100 dollar bills and a voodoo doll, respectively.</item>
        <item>A 300-page, home-bound, draft-print biography of Jackson Elias, famed pre-Second World War explorer and occult investigator, who was murdered in New York in 1925. Almost half the book is about tying his death to the equally strange disappearance of the Carlyle Expedition some years earlier.\nAnyone reading the book will get the impression the anonymous author knew a lot more than they were letting on in the text, as they bring seemingly unrelated events that occurred in China and London to the story yet leave the reason for inclusion tantalisingly out of reach.</item>
        <item>A battered copy of Volume XIV of the History of United States Naval Operations in World War II: "Victory in the Pacific 1945" by Samuel Eliot Morison, published in 1964. The odd part are the handwritten notes in the chapter on the fighting on Okinawa, 7-13 April 1945. The map on p219 has been annotated to say "deep sea creatures here" next to the island of Tsugen Jima, on the east side of Okinawa. The text on p220 describes the fighting on Tsugen Jima. Handwritten notes say that the 234 Japanese defenders killed were creatures from the deep, and that the naval gunfire was critical to destroying them as they were invincible in combat with the USMC.</item>
        <item>A cookie tin full of New York vacation trinkets: used bus-tickets, maps, stickers, attraction guides. All of them are dated 1996, but somebody has gone through and whited-out the World Trade Centers wherever they appear.</item>
        <item>A black garbage bag overstuffed and abnormally shaped as it contains the body of an unnamed 24 year old woman who has been missing from a local Tcho-Tcho minority community. If her body is touched she will inhale sharply causing SAN loss 1/1D6 and revive becoming a witness to the case...</item>
        <item>A notebook filled with a detailed handwritten plan on how to burn down a particular brand of retirement homes, and how to make sure no one inside will be able to leave the building when the fire has started.</item>
        <item>A collection of dry, brittle and stained notebooks. Bound by a leather strap. Appears to be the lab journals of a "C. A. Hanse", and documents his dissection of various stolen corpses over a five year period, and his recombining them into "new, better forms". Final entries talk of an \'Elixir Vitae\' that could give these dead forms a new life.</item>
        <item>A DVD it appears to be an episode of \'Breaking Bad\' which crosses-over with \'Supernatural.\' If investigated no one associated with either show has any knowledge of this DVD or any memory of working on it. It is a very enjoyable episode though.</item>
        <item>Blueprints of a fancy new coastal resort being built in modern day Innsmouth.\nAn Architecture roll noticed several weird angles and hidden passages built into the hotel.</item>
        <item>Copy of "Suffolk\'s Defended Shore: Coastal Fortifications from the Air" published by English Heritage. There\'s dozens of holiday photographs of Dunwich, UK between pages 37 and 38.</item>
        <item>A collection of poems printed from the "Sky Journal", a small Seattle based arts magazine. A series of poems entitled the "Innana clouds" features prominently. There are many allusions to Yog Sothoth or as the poems states, Yagasoth. There is also mention of a "sky door" or portal.</item>
        <item>Behind a drop cloth is a piece of dry wall. It was obviously cut out of a wall in a hurry. On it is the instructions for the spell of your choice.</item>
        <item>A leather ziplock bag containing dozens of rolls of microfiche. On the sheets is a relatively comprehensive copy of the infamous "Grudge/Blue Book 13" on alien crashes and Project Moon Dust. The one the Air Force say never existed...</item>
        <item>A handwritten cook-book detailing several recipes based on Ghoul-meat. Most of them include the ingredient: "Chili! Lots of Chili!".</item>
        <item>A 20cm by 20cm chapbook of excellent cotton paper stitched at the spine with catgut. It\'s a personal journal kept by noted Russian artist Olga Vladimirovna Rozanova of the Supremus school of painters. She painted the text in water color, rather than write longhand. Her Cubist/Russian Futurist-like paintings of flattened dimensions illuminate the text. Of note, an entry from 13 October 1913: "Sleepless, four days: men of many pale colors and flat shapes stalk me along edges of buildings, rooms, anywhere with straight lines, corners. Sense them at edge of vision. If my skull were a clear glass, I could see them. Alexi and Velimir mock me, play at my fear with their cruel nonsense poems." Sharp anthromorphic masses emerging from pub scenes accompany this entry.</item>
        <item>A black, leather-bound book that has the word "FOOT" printed in every language on Earth--even extinct languages. The book runs to nearly a thousand thin pages with 500 entries per page in tiny type. On the cover is embossed the words "Volume 1" in gold leaf.</item>
        <item>A nation-wide FBI BOLO (Be-On-Look-Out) fax for one Johnny Carcosa, a known drug-dealer from Boston. A pock-marked Hispanic youth, he always wears a yellow bandana over the face. Lisps. Wanted in connection with a number of bizarre drug-related deaths across New England.</item>
        <item>A faded postcard sent from Madison, Wisconsin to Birmingham, Alabama. The picture shows a fisherman standing holding up fish with several tentacles protruding from odd places on it\'s body. The text on the post-card reads. "Come back soon Mary. The kids miss you."</item>
        <item>A journal seemly written by a serial killer. His M.O. does not match any past or present serial killings (or, at least those that have been discovered). Agents can make a Know check to realize that several of the described victims match descriptions of missing persons from across the country. However, contrary to the journals account of events, the missing people have yet to be found dead or alive.</item>
        <item>A set of some 50 surveillance photographs of a group of quite non-descript men and women. One picture has captured the face of one of the Investigators walking by in the background. On the back of the photo someone has written "Lies within lies?".</item>
        <item>A flip-book.depicting a clown laughing.</item>
        <item>A set of manila folders, all stamped with a logo consisting of three squares in an angular construction pointing up with lines joining them and a dot in the top square. Each is labeled with a name. They include: Alma Wade, Paxton Fettel, and one that is too smudged to read.</item>
        <item>Alma\'s file is a horrific account of a "telepathically gifted" child being impregnated in an effort to make a superior human. It states that the first child-"prototype" was a failure, for unstated reasons. The second prototype was a success, and was the focus of a new project. Alma was then locked in an underground vault for unstated reasons.</item>
        <item>Fettel\'s file reveals that he was the second prototype. He inherited the telepathic abilities of his mother, and learned to control an "experimental military deployment". However, a vague event in his past caused the project to be frozen.</item>
        <item>The third file is damaged by fire and water, but what little can be read talks about the first prototype having enhanced reflexes.</item>
        <item>The fourth file talks in detail about Armacham Technology, and its suspected links to MJ-12. This file is typewritten, with red ink annotations.</item>
        <item>An annotated copy of the (rejected) doctoral dissertation "Sky Devils: Archetypical Figures in Native American Mythology" (University of Indiana, Bloomington; 1975 by Karen Barr). 1d2/1d4 points of Sanity to read. +1 point Cthulhu Mythos. No spells.</item>
        <item>Manilla folders holding medical records of US senators that served in the 1960s with a special focus on their medication intake. Hand written notes in red ink cover the pages. The red notes make references to a number of compounds that are not found in any known medical text.</item>
        <item>"Sons of Earth" - leather bound manuscript, seemingly hand-typed with corrections and editing notes intact. No date or author. Rambling discourse on the idea that alien genetic material is shaping the evolution of the human race. Talks about how interaction with alien \'visitors\' is the key to unlocking human potential. Study reveals potential \'meeting places\' that may in fact be Mi-Go monitored.</item>
        <item>A notebook filled with frantic writing, certain words and designs overwritten multiple times. The journal repeatedly emphasises that the writer was stalked by an unnatural faceless creature.\nDocument box containing files from the office of a local psychiatrist. All files relate to patients with fixed delusions concerning occult or supernatural occurrences. A Psychology/Psyychoanalysis roll allows the reader to read "between the lines" of the files and determine that the course of treatment in every case has been at best highly unorthodox and at worst highly unethical and harmful for the patients. Further investigation reveals several former patients have commited crimes and others have disappeared under mysterious circumstances.</item>
        <item>A thick, worn manilla folder containing approximately 112 pages, all yellowed. Each page is typed, double spaced, rows of numbers.</item>
        <item>A stack of comic books. Several of them are marked up with pen, random words circled. It is possible there is a message or code somewhere in here.</item>
        <item>A lengthy handwritten novella outlining a future for Frankenstein\'s monster, after the events of the novel, of a rather graphic erotic nature. The yellowed paper dates back to the 1950s.</item>
        <item>A silver CD entitled "Yuggae Slam" (in black text). Contains 6 tracks of weird reggae-style music using electronic tones. Anyone who listens to the whole thing will invariably picture a twisted tower or helix of shining globes in their minds. This response is universal and the only sinister thing about the CD.</item>
        <item>An unmarked binder containing a handwritten treatise on the connections between bats in ancient Mesoamerican religions and modern death worship. A section on decapitation rituals hints at unidentified Delta Green Agents willingly participating in such rituals.</item>
        <item>What appears to be official military documents obviously originating from Nazi Germany. Members of the party that can read German will see that they are technical documents regarding two chemical compounds designated V-347-A, and V-347-B. If the translator is knowledgeable in the field of chemistry, they will see that the documents are instructions for the safe handling of the compounds. The section detailing the properties of the chemicals have been entirely redacted.\nThe documents are found in a large wooden crate that seems to have been padded to transport fragile goods. The documents are the only item within the crate.</item>
        <item>A paperback copy of Rollo Ahmed\'s "The Black Art", well covered in sticky-notes to mark pages (No Sanity loss; Occult +5%. No Spells)</item>
        <item>One notebook, meticulously filled with the same strange, twisting symbol.</item>
        <item>The first two pages of a letter addressed to Christie\'s auction house, London, dated January, 1975. The unknown author claims to have inherited from his father a rough draft copy of Shakespeare\'s Henry VI, part 2, with notable differences from the final version. The villain, Jack Cade, is depicted as having supernatural powers, and exhorting the populace to rebel against the nobility and, "...return to the worship of the eldest gods." The man who in the later version kills Cade for a reward on his head is depicted as his accomplice, who helps him to fake his death. In a grisly scene, the two kidnap and murder a pregnant woman and her husband during a ritual which will allow Cade to escape to France through a magical portal. The husband\'s head is later turned in for the reward on Cade\'s own. The author claims each of these three sections contain margin notes, presumably from the censors of the Company of Stationers, saying, "Leave this in at your peril!"</item>
        <item>20 reels of Super 8 film that appear to have all been shot in or around New York City\'s Central Park, probably in the early 1970s judging by the fashions and other hints. There is no sound on any of the reels and all of the footage seems to totally random.</item>
        <item>A shipping crate containing sixty brand new hardback copies of "Microbiology and Organic Chemistry, 2nd Edition" textbooks from a nonexistent \'Doris &amp; Green Publishing, Ltd.\'\nThe first sentence of the book says that Watson and Crick discovered DNA. Everything past that is subtly wrong. However, it takes a fairly advanced knowledge of the subject matter to detect the inaccuracies, and when the reader has caught multiple examples, they realize the author clearly has a doctoral-level understanding of the subject matter, but is deliberately choosing to subvert and misrepresent certain key facts about DNA, alleles, heredity, evolution, and similar fields.\nThe book starts off at a level of detail expected of a high school biology textbook, describing the various parts of the cell, mitosis and meiosis, etc., all with about 90% validity. However, as it continues, it becomes less of a textbook and more of an instruction manual, covering artificial creation of specific genotypes and phenotypes, selective breeding for complex traits, and the like, all while subtly expanding and misapplying the inaccuracies introduced at the beginning. By the end, it becomes a manual of applied eugenics consisting of completely false information.\nAt this point, an Idea roll can be made if the reader has detected the falsehoods of the book; if it is succeeded, then he or she realizes it has been deliberately written to sabotage anyone who tries to apply its contents in laboratory eugenics research.</item>
        <item>Paperwork relating to adoptions and fostering of Russian and Eastern European children in the local area. Attached newspaper clippings and police reports show a hitherto unseen correlation between the recent influx of such children and reports of "flying saucers".</item>
        <item>A slim book entitled "How to Legally Wed Your Close Relatives." Poorly edited and apparently self-published during the 1950s, most of the book is filled with the anonymous author\'s long rambling opinions on why family members should only wed other family members and lots of dubious legal advice on how to deal with "the authorities".</item>
        <item>A cheap paperback novel by an unknown author, published by an equally unknown printing house, dated 1947 and priced at 50 cents. It is set in a small midwestern town; the characters are local townspeople, all of whom seem to be sexually involved with at least two other people. After several lurid chapters it ends with a multiple murder involving most of the characters. Uncannily, whenever the book is read the characters\' names and descriptions match those of the current investigators, no matter who reads the book.</item>
        <item>A stained copy of \'Gray\'s Anatomy\'. Various muscle groups are annotated as "delicious".</item>
        <item>40 or so different adult magazines - all from September 2001. These have all been annotated in an unknown code (actually it\'s Aklo) - the notes are all detailing out the suitability of the various models (male and female) as breeding and host material.</item>
        <item>The other experimental notes of Mengele. San damage is at the DMs discretion</item>
        <item>An old world geography textbook, circa 1962. It reads as one would expect for a book of that time, except for about half a dozen instances marked with sticky notes in which the typeface abruptly changes and the writing shifts to a cryptic, almost mystical style. Successful History and/or Idea rolls leads the reader to believe they may have prophesied major world events such as the Yom Kippur War, the Challenger explosion, and the Rwandan genocide. The final prophecy seems unfulfilled, and hints at a great plague spreading across Asia.</item>
        <item>A spiral-bound notebook. It lists the GPS coordinates for about 20 "surveillance devices" scattered about a nearby state park. Each is accompanied by a short description like "in a spruce" or "between two rocks". The last entry is a request to contact \'Big Green\' if "entities" are observed.</item>
        <item>A rather standard looking Gideon Bible, of the type found in almost every hotel room in the United States. Every reference to the Devil has been replaced with a very small (small enough to avoid disrupting the typeface) pair of stylized glaring eyes. Looking at them makes the reader feel inexplicably uncomfortable.</item>
        <item>A carboard box containing 87 suicide notes, all written by persons who killed themselves in the greater Peoria, Illinois area between the years 1979 and 1998.</item>
        <item>The Yellow Pages for Billings, Montana. The Churches and Mental Health Providers sections are defaced with red permanent marker by large scrawled "LIARS!", repeated enough times to cover the entire pages.</item>
        <item>A red brick with silver etchings that when read aloud allows the investigator to cast a spell at random.</item>
        <item>A box containing videotaped copies of every episode of The Price is Right, up until July 2004, 3 episodes per tape. Also inside the box is a series of notes, what if anything the person was trying to prove is impossible to understand.</item>
        <item>A tall stack of very tattered tabletop RPG books. The books are crammed full of wrinkled and torn sheets of paper, sticky notes, and chewing gum wrappers are used as bookmarks. The margins are, unsurprisingly, full of scribbled notes. The notes are actually speculations and observations about which of the futures or parallel worlds might be the most likely future of the human race (in your Delta Green game). Three weeks to skim the whole mess, six weeks to comprehend the notes and cross references.\nIf the character makes it all the way to the end, they will determine that the most probable future will be that of Shadowrun (third edition).</item>
        <item>A reel of color 8 mm film of 1960s manufacture. It is stored inside a blue metal reel can that has "North Carolina, 1966" written on a masking tape label; the words \'Project GARNET - 7AE.L51.1\' have been stamped on the can just below the label.</item>
        <item>The footage initially consists of a trio of brothers on some sort of holiday in that state. The final exposed section takes place near Brown Mountain; they are hamming it up around a campfire when one of the brothers suddenly stands and points away from the camp. The other two (including the camera man) follow. The camera is trained towards a ridge some distance away where a group of oddly colored lights zig-zag above the treetops. This activity is captured on film for six minutes, until the end of the reel.</item>
        <item>A handwritten journal containing only strings of numbers written on every third line. There are signs of erased writing in the now empty lines. Different inks and writing styles indicate multiple authors over different time periods.</item>
        <item>A labeled sketch-map of Laurel Caverns near Pittsburgh, PA. Several points are marked as "potential contact locations". On the back the cave\'s security system is outlined as well as a workable plan to circumvent it and enter the cave without being detected.</item>
        <item>A very small bookshelf, loaded with books about the supposed UFO crash at Roswell and other such incidents. The books collected are: "The Day After Roswell" by Philip Corso, "The Roswell UFO Crash: What They Don\'t Want You to Know" by Kal K. Korff, "The Roswell Incident" by Charles Berlitz, "Crash at Corona" by Stanton Friedman and Don Berliner, "The Truth About the UFO Crash at Roswell" and "Roswell Revisited" by Kevin D. Randle, "Witness to Roswell: Unmasking the 60 Year Coverup" by Thomas Carey and Donald Schmitt, "The Roswell Legacy" by Jesse Marcel Jr., "Behind the Flying Saucers" by Frank Scully, "UFO Crash in Brazil" by K. Leir Roger, "Mexico\'s Roswell: The Chihuahua UFO Crash" and "The Other Roswell: UFO Crash on the Texas-Mexico Border" by Noe Torres and Reuben Uriarte, "Cosmic Crashes: The Incredible Story of the UFOs That Fell to Earth" and "Body Snatchers in the Desert" by Nick Redfern, and "UFO Crash at Aztec: A Well Kept Secret" by Wiliams S. Steinman.</item>
        <item>A slim, black book, written in English, cheaply bound and very tattered, with brown pages crumbling at the edges. On the title page, it is dated London, 1904, and authorship is attributed to someone calling himself "rother A. Poole, Opener of the Gate". The title of the book is "The New Revelation Revealed to the Elect".</item>
        <item>The actual text is quite strange, but boring, lots of borrowing from the book of Revelations and certain nastier parts of the Old Testament, with other sections apparently based on the works of people ranging from Charles Darwin to the philospher Jeremy Bentham to spiritualists and occultists like Madame Blavatsky; the result is a strange and turgid hodgepodge. The final summing up of the hundred or pages is a caution, or rather summons, to the "Faithful Brothers and Sisters of the Elect" to withdraw from the world and settle together in a "Secluded Spot" at the first oppurtunity.</item>
        <item>A wall map of the world. Even the most casual geographer will notice a number of irregularities: the PRC\'s Muslim-Chinese province of Xinjiang is labelled "East Turkestan SSR", Vietnam is shaded the 51st state of the USA, and much of Tibet and its surrounding lands are simply titled "Leng", among others...\nThe publisher\'s mark claims the map was printed by The People\'s State Cartographical Bureau (International Dept.) of Gdansk, People\'s Republic of Poland, 1975.</item>
        <item>An article ripped out of a national law enforcement journal. It documents a rising trend of arrests along the nations highways of down and out drug addicts who have heard a rumor that they could get high by finding and drinking from \'trucker bombs\', which are bottles that cross country truck drivers urinate into then toss from their windows, on the erroneous assumption that most truck drivers are speed or meth users. Although written in a humorous tone, someone has written across the page, "Italian folk magic/mojo/hoodoo? This bears further investigation."</item>
        <item>A large collection of lottery tickets, held together by several rubber bands. All the numbers have been filled in with strange, esoteric symbols.</item>
        <item>A 2009 undergraduate prospectus for Miskatonic University, Mass.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a hymnbook of classic Protestant hymns at first glance; however, multiple references to God in the lyrics have been changed to "Yosoth". The final few pages of the hymnal contain vocalise songs with carefully noted rhythm and melodies. A successful Cthulhu Mythos roll will recognize the songs as having the same rough structure as the spell Call Yog-Sothoth, though evidently blurred, mis-remembered, and stylized to the point of (fortunate) ineffectiveness.</item>
        <item>A Wisconsin highway map, with a section of highway 33 between Interstate 90/94 and the city of Baraboo marked in yellow highlighter and an FM radio frequency written in black ink and three sets of call letters. The second set is circled in red. If a car stereo is tuned to the radio frequency on that section of road there will be three radio stations competing for reception. The first and third of the call letters are normal radio stations-- one out of Madison and one out of LaCrosse. The station represented by the second set of call letters, however, is a bit odd. Along with the regular weather forecast, the radiation level is given. The U.S. president is named "Derzon", and announcements by the Department of Homeland Security are read along with the news, including a listing of enemies of the state. (Occasionally the names of characters may show up.) None of the songs played on the station will be recognizable. Additionally, the morning show is sponsored by Studebaker This station is received less often than the other two, and the reception is frequently poor.</item>
        <item>A sealed folder containing typed documents that have been encrypted in ROT13 - when decoded the documents turn out to be a dossier on Karotechia movements in Europe from 1999 to 2001</item>
        <item>An aged, yellowed pamphlet entitled "Satan\'s Chariot" which warns readers of the evils of riding bicycles. It is dated November 13, 1883.</item>
        <item>A map of the local area. Several locations are marked in red ink, and attempts have been made with a pencil to find a pentagram in the seemingly random pattern. If followed up on, they are revealed to all be locations of suicides in the last twenty-four months.</item>
        <item>A seemingly random collection of pornographic magazines dating back to the 1950s, ranging from 50s-60s era "girlie mags" to more modern softcore magazines and hardcore magazines to magazines pandering to a variety of fetishes and auidences. Every magazine has pages that have been marked, all pages with photographs of what appears to be the same blond haired, blue eyed woman. The woman in the pictures is always the same age, no matter what year a particular magazine was published.. Underneath these magazines is a collection of men\'s fitness magazines, dating back to the 1970s. Pages featuring a male model who could easily be the above woman\'s brother have been marked. He also appears to be the same age in all the pictures. When the models are identified and the magazines are of the same year, the man and woman share the same last name.</item>
        <item>A large sized, moderately thick glossy covered paperback book, with hi-tech style graphics and lettering entitled "Modern Enlightenment -Transhumanism Connections With The Occult" by Avis Lennox.</item>
        <item>A modern copy of "On The Summoning of the Seventy-Two Demons of Solomon", which was first written approx. 920 BC. It has been translated out of the original Hebrew into English. All of the rituals described are false.</item>
        <item>Thirty pages of photocopied, rambling conspiracy-theorist drivel, stapled together and annotated with more conspiracy-theorist ramblings in green ink. It refers to Mythos entities and rituals at several points, but it\'s clear from context that the author knew nothing of these entities beyond their names. Neither san loss or Mythos knowledge is gained from reading it.</item>
        <item>A folding pamphlet for a murder mystery dinner theatre held at the Green Goddess Theatre in Canaan, Connecticut. According to the pamphlet the show ran for six months in 1972, but research on the location will show that the theatre burned down in 1969, supposedly because of a wiring problem. The site was never rebuilt and the forest has reclaimed the location.</item>
        <item>A flash drive with mp3 audio files. They are mostly recordings of an unknown numbers station, speaking in Hebrew. The last one is a scientist explaining some salient points of anatomy on an anomalous humanoid.</item>
        <item>A military file on a Mossad operation, written in Hebrew. Players capable of reading it will find that it pertains to an operation in which agents extracted a purported psychic from a small town in Libya. The psychic proved to be a fraud, but had valuable information on unknown oil wells.</item>
        <item>A stack of loose graph paper, about 120 sheets\' worth; scrawled across each page, in increasingly deteriorating handwriting, is scribbled the phrase "I DO NOT FEAR THE WOLF FOR I AM THE WOLF", over and over again.</item>
        <item>The heavily revised text of a computer program, written in C.</item>
        <item>A computer use roll can identify the purpose of the program is to solve a lengthy series of complex topological problems. Mathematicians and computer programmers will find the program unsettling, as it somehow solves paradoxes by creating even greater paradoxes. (Study time: 5 days. SAN: loss 1/1d2)</item>
        <item>A detailed report from the vivisection of a male in his fifties only identified as "The Agent". The report notes indications that some unidentified biological entity has been present in the subject\'s chest-cavity, but is now gone. The vivisection ends with the subject being injected with a lehal dose of morphine. A handwritten note at the end of the report says: "Never call me again, you Green fucks!".</item>
        <item>A fragment of 8mm celluloid film, about thirty feet long. It shows a few seconds of a group of technicians inspecting a large apparatus centered on something that resembles a huge tuning fork. The film is of German manufacture, dating from the early 1940s.</item>
        <item>A CD jewel-case with a crudely photoshopped cover advertising itself as "The Complete Spoken Word NECRONOMICON (Unabridged)". If played, the CD actually contains 33 tracks of someone reading extracts from the neo-Nazi novella "The Turner Diaries". Sounding bored, the reader mispronounces the bigger words and stops every so often to have a drink or eat something. The accent is untraceable Mid-Western, but definitely rural in inflection.</item>
        <item>Printouts of every piece of legislation and treaty pertaining to Antarctica, annotated with queries and clarifications regarding who would have juristiction over an "extra national citizen".</item>
        <item>"A slim book entitled "How to Legally Wed Your Close Relatives." Poorly</item>
        <item>edited and apparently self-published during the 1950s, most of the book</item>
        <item>is filled with the anonymous author\'s long rambling opinions on why</item>
        <item>family members should only wed other family members and lots of dubious</item>
        <item>legal advice on how to deal with "the authorities"."</item>
        <item>A 1989 Seattle phone book, with a relatively large percentage of names highlighted seemingly at random. If examined closely for any pattern, the only one that can be found is that every person highlighted has the same letter at the start of their first name as the end of their last name, i.e. "Sandy Stevens", "Robert Baker", "Norman Brown", "Katherine Nowak", etc.</item>
        <item>A collection of a now defunct monthly counter-culture magazine that was published from the early 60\'s to the late 70\'s. Called the \'Monthly Undergrounder\' it was a mix of news of the day with a slant towards youth of the era, oped articles calling for the change of society, anti-war news, new age religion and conspiracy theory. Since it reported on some odd stuff as well as the what was going on in the world it would make a good resource for agents looking into that time period. The collection itself is worth something, the magazine was a niche product and very few copies remain period.</item>
        <item>A handwritten manuscript simply entitled "Service"; if one of the investigators was in the military during war, he or she will find that it contain details that the author couldn\'t possibly have known about unless they had been in the investigator\'s platoon (or equivalent unit); though the book is written in the first person, there isn\'t enough information about the narrator for the investigator to determine which member of his/her unit actually wrote it; the handwriting, prose, descriptions, etc. are unfamiliar,</item>
        <item>"A Case for Eugenics, with Historical Antecedents and Modern Analysis", a 1916 work discussing of specific genetic defects associated with certain New England communities as well as their eradication, with photos. The book is quite rare. It argues that such defects could be bred out of the population through vigorously applied legislation requiring the sterilization of their sufferers. One particular case, that of Caleb Island, ME, discusses the case of a now-vanished fishing village where a large number of inhabitants suffered from spinal curvature, skin problems, cranial dysmorphia, and hair loss that grew worse with age. Anyone familiar with the Deep Ones will recognize their traits in the few poorly reproduced daguerreotypes of the villagers. The settlement at Caleb island is reported to have been abandoned in the 1850s due to declining harvest.</item>
        <item>A folk-art piece depicting the Rapture. Intermingled with figures of angels are several fungi from Yuggoth. The angels attending God (who is depicted as a swirling golden light) are all bearing flutes while Satan is three-legged and bears a single enormous red horn. An art historian can place the origin of the painting to the Ozarks, probably in the early 1970s but the painter is unknown.</item>
        <item>An antique copy of Machiavelli\'s \'The Prince\', with all interior typeface inverted as though via mirror-writing. Judging by how well-centered it is, and the overall quality of the print, it appears intentional rather than accidental.</item>
        <item>A 16mm film reel in a can labeled "SIRHAN B SIRHAN 1967" If played it appears to be surveillance footage of Sirhan Sirhan walking about the streets of Pasadena, CA approximately half a year before the RFK assassination.</item>
        <item>Box containing hundreds of notebook pages covered with what appears to be license-plate numbers and the make and colors of the automobiles that carry them as well as lists of items found in various trashcans at scores of locations and dates, all written in an elegant, almost calligraphic handwriting.</item>
        <item>Manilla folder containing some newspaper clippings and a couple of faded, dingy flyers. The flyers are advertisments for the appearances of a band called Scorched Earth at two separate L.A. rock clubs (both now long since defunct). The clippings are stories from L.A. newspapers about the band\'s frontman and lead singer "Joey Gestalt" aka Frank Rodker or rather his mysterious murder back in 1989. His body was found in an alley behind a Chinese restaurant. While his body was emaciated and showed signs of severe drug abuse what caught everyone\'s attention was that the top of Gestalt?s head had been removed, along with his brain, "with surgical precision". Police detectives speculated it was the work of a serial killer.</item>
        <item>Scorched Earth had broken up about a year before Gestalt\'s body was discovered; they and their occult-reference flavored sound had enjoyed a very short-lived vogue in the L.A. rock club scene. Gestalt had, according to several of the articles, been completely broke at the time of the break-up and supposedly been living on the streets since then.</item>
        <item>A confoundingly convoluted and heavily annotated (with cramped handwritten notes that are variously in red ink, black ink, and pencil) staple bound monograph claiming to record the "Wisdom of the Hyperboreans and their Magicks", specifically the creation of "Portals linking places many leagues distant and Higher Realms" (Cthulhu Mythos: +3, Sanity loss: -1d4/-2d4, Study time: 24 weeks). Requires a read English and three successful mathematics rolls due to the archaic language and obscure concepts.)</item>
        <item>A manila folder entitled "R. Costas". Inside are 48 typed, single spaced pages detailing the health of Mr. Robert Costas of Pierre, South Dakota. Further reading will show that Mr. Costas suffered from a degenerate lung condition unknown to the doctors and staff in his care. By all accounts he was a healthy man of 52. He was in fine condition, until the summer of 1982. He complained of breathing trouble after a camping trip in the Oregon wilderness. The last 3 pages detailing the autopsy reports have been blacked out in strategic places.</item>
        <item>A stack of ready-made "fill-in-the-blank" ransom notes.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>