<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_mundane_weapons">
        <item>A Mendoza PUMA semiautomatic rifle and 50 rounds .22 long rifle.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing eleven .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>A wooden box lined with a thick layer of bubble wrap contains two RKG-3 anti-tank grenades.</item>
        <item>A plastic ankle-holster containing a fully loaded (5 shot) Ruger LCR .38 revolver with 1.875" barrel and black rubber grip.</item>
        <item>A Gerber Gator machete with an 18-inch blade, in a nylon sheath.</item>
        <item>An early 20th-century Madsen machine gun chambered in .30-06 Springfield, very well preserved. Oil and cleaning gear can be found next to it, along with four boxes of ammo: three of them hold 100 modern .30-06 rounds each, while the last one has only 76. A note taped to this last box says: "1912 VINTAGE - PACE YOURSELF - OLD AMMO IS HARD TO COME BY"</item>
        <item>A box of .25 ACP ammunition. It contains 20 rounds.</item>
        <item>Three antique German Panzerfausts from the second World War. They are old and partially rusted. User discretion is advised.</item>
        <item>Several late-model cavalry sabers, mostly American Model 1913 "Patton" sabers. Each one is authentic, but also very well-maintained and just as ready for combat as the day they were forged.</item>
        <item>An M1928A1 "Thompson" SMG, with four 50-round drums and six 30-round "stick" mags. The serial number has been obliterated but gun is stamped "PROPERTY OF U.S. NAVY"</item>
        <item>A prewar Colt Woodsman .22 semiauto pistol with a threaded muzzle and no serial number. Box also contains a crudely machined and finished, but very effective silencer that fits the threads, several magazines for the pistol, and a few dusty old partial boxes of .22 ammunition, perhaps 50-60 rounds total. The silencer has the words "RETIREMENT PLAN" scratched crudely onto the side of the tube.</item>
        <item>A brand new M60 machine gun with bipod, an instruction manual and 3 boxes of ammunition (200 cartridges per box, 7.62mm).</item>
        <item>A hard case containing a 7.62x51mm DSA SA58 OSW carbine with an 11" barrel, folding stock, EOTech red dot sight, a vertical foregrip, a sling and three spare 20-round magazines.</item>
        <item>One Mossberg 500 12 gauge pump shotgun fitted with a deer slug ( rifled ) barrel. Two boxes of slugs ( 10 rounds total ) are with the shotgun in a zippered nylon case.</item>
        <item>A pair of M18 Smoke (red) grenades.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .22 "Dixie Derringer" mini revolver.</item>
        <item>A 10-foot braided rawhide bullwhip.</item>
        <item>A cardboard case. Inside are twenty 50-round boxes of 9mm 115-grain FMJ ammunition manufactured at Tula Cartridge works of Russia.</item>
        <item>A Stoeger Coach Gun. This double-barrel shotgun is chambered for 20-gauge shells, and several vertical lines have been carefully drawn on its stock and barrel in grease pen. It\'s fairly obvious that they were placed by someone attempting to decide where and how to saw the weapon down.</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing an assortment of ammunition: eighteen .32 rounds, twelve .38 rounds, nine .357 Magnum rounds and four .44 Magnum rounds.</item>
        <item>A brown paper bag containing a worn Colt Detective Special .38 revolver with 2" barrel. The snubnosed gun has two fired and four unfired rounds in the cylinder.</item>
        <item>A cheap replica cavalry saber, not actually meant for use in fighting. A few good hits will bend it, a few more will snap the hilt from the blade.</item>
        <item>Four 50-round boxes of .38 Special 158-grain LRN (lead round nose) ammunition manufactured by Magtech.</item>
        <item>A cheap Pakistani copy of a Colt 1911 .45 pistol. It has no serial number but is in dubious condition with a fair amount of rust on the frame. The magazine contains five rounds.</item>
        <item>A Colt Delta Elite pistol and two empty magazines.</item>
        <item>A soft training bag containing an oily towel, a heavy hunting knife in a leather scabbard, four 12 gauge rounds and a fully loaded (4 rounds) Norinco Hawk 982 12 gauge pump action shotgun with a 14" barrel.</item>
        <item>This footlocker contains a heavy old military rifle partially wrapped in rags; the rags turn out to be a faded, dirty, somewhat ragged old T-shirt that says "BE A MAN AMONG MEN, JOIN THE RHODESIAN ARMY" The rifle is a well-worn but lovingly maintained late-pattern FN FAL with its plastic buttstock, handguard, and pistol grip sloppily painted in a tiger-stripe camouflage pattern of olive drab, black, and dark green; the paint is worn and chipped. There are also a half dozen or so FAL mags in the footlocker, painted to match the pattern on the rest of the gun and two sealed "battle packs" of 7.62x51mm NATO rifle ammunition, each ten 20-round pasteboard boxes sealed in airtight heavy green plastic; the markings on the packaging and the headstamps on the cartridges indicate they were manufactured in Portugal in the 1980s.</item>
        <item>A slightly rusty but functional Llama XA .32 pistol. The small gun is fully loaded (7 rounds) and comes with a cheap plastic belt-holster.</item>
        <item>A pair of Yugoslavian M59 carbines (near-identical copies of the SKS) stashed inside a steel gun safe along with 24 ten round disposable stripper clips of 7.62x39mm ammunition resting in a box on the little shelf above the carbines.</item>
        <item>An empty two-shot .45 Derringer pistol.</item>
        <item>A fish gutting knife, inlaid with burnished silver.</item>
        <item>An Artillery model Luger pistol, complete with wooden stock/holster and 32-round snail drum to make it an antiquated but functional carbine. It would, of course, fetch thousands on the collectors\' market.</item>
        <item>A drum that\'s been turned into a massive improvised pyrotechnic device. Stenciled on the side is a around pointing down. If opened it will be found to have been filled with an oil gas mixture as well as a homemade napalm. It is designed to set the mixture alight and then allow it to flow out a hole in the bottom.</item>
        <item>A pair of Beretta PM12S 9mm submachine gun with a metal folding stock - 6 40-round magazines are included.</item>
        <item>A small bottle of Pepper Mace Spray.</item>
        <item>An unloaded Smith &amp; Wesson Model 10 revolver, c.1973. A quick check reveals it still has a colonial-era Royal Hong Kong Police stamp on the grip.</item>
        <item>A home-made flail. It has a wooden weight attached via a single chain link to another wooden shaft about 1.5 the length of the bludgeoning end.</item>
        <item>An unopened box of .357 Magnum handgun ammunition. It contains fifty rounds.</item>
        <item>A cigar box containing a jumble of 9mm Winchester Silvertips and Speer Gold Dots.</item>
        <item>A Star Model BM 9mm pistol with the Starvel finish (electroless nickel), three spare 9-round magazines and two 50-round boxes of Winchester 9mm hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>Fifty-nine rounds .45 ACP HydraShock ammunition.</item>
        <item>A steel hand-and-half-sword with sharpened edges. Obviously of modern making and stamped with a small rose that can be traced to the Czech smith Pavel Moc.</item>
        <item>A Taurus Model 689 chambered in .357 Magnum with a custom ported 6-inch barrel.</item>
        <item>A large pink faux-leather woman\'s purse, containing several telescoping police batons as well as various models of stun guns and Tasers.</item>
        <item>Leg from a coffee table</item>
        <item>An extra magazine for a Colt 1911 pistol. It contains seven .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>Three different modern replicas of the Colt 1873 Single Action Army revolver. First is a Cimarron Model P with a case-hardened frame, smooth walnut grips, a 7-1/2" barrel and is chambered in .44 Special. Second is a Taylor &amp; Co. Smoke Wagon with a 4-3/4" barrel and checkered walnut one-piece grip, chambered for .45 Long Colt and last is a Heritage Rough Rider with a nickel finish, 5-1/2 barrel, and one-piece cocobolo grip. It is also chambered for .45 Long Colt. There are also three belt-holster rigs for the revolvers, as well as three fifty-round boxes of .45 LC jacketed flat-nose rounds and a fifty-round box of .44 Special jacketed hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A Remington 870 twelve-gauge shotgun with a Trijicon reflex sight mounted on top and a Speedfeed synthetic stock with molded-in tubes that can hold four extra rounds, zippered up in a carrying case.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box which was addressed to a PO box in the city the Green Box is located in, with a return address somewhere in Alaska (Label has been blacked out). Inside the box is a single, loaded, Heckler &amp; Kock MK23 Mod 0 pistol, with suppressor and laser aiming module attached. The pistol has the serial number removed, but has "MK23 USSOCOM" engraved on it. Under the pistol is a gray bandanna.</item>
        <item>This large, heavy steel ammo can contains eight hundred rounds of 5.56mm ammunition, in four 200-round belts for the M249 Squad Automatic Weapon, linked four rounds tungsten-core AP to one tracer.</item>
        <item>One 8mm Type 14 Nambu pistol, with a single magazine containing 3 rounds. The pistol bears significant pitting and rust, and the action is coated with a brown powder. Upon analysis, the powder is dried human blood.</item>
        <item>Three Steyr M357-A1 semi-automatic pistols chambered for the .357 SIG round. Each comes with a spare 12-round magazine. The pistols sit next to a stack of three 50-round boxes of Federal Premium .357 SIG 125-grain JHP (jacketed hollowpoints).</item>
        <item>There is a cardboard shipping box. Inside are 36 plastic cases, each holding a semiautomatic pistol &amp; 2 standerd magazines. They are .22LR, .25ACP or .380ACP. They also lack serial numbers.( the guns were made by low quality southern california manufacturers,AKA the "Ring of Fire".More cam discovered in the PBS Frontline report.) Should one be fired, it will jam before emptinga six round clip.</item>
        <item>One "spam" can containing 440 rounds of Bulgarian surplus 7.62x54R 147grn FMJ rifle rounds.</item>
        <item>This small cardboard box contains a nickel-plated Vietnamese copy of the Walther PPK pistol, but in .22 caliber, with one spare magazine. The pistol is worn and its nickel plating is scratched and peeling in places. It has equally worn, slightly dirty-looking red plastic grips with a picture of a dragon molded into them. The gun is filthy and in need of a thorough cleaning and perhaps a wee bit of oil. The weapon has no serial number. No ammunition is present.</item>
        <item>An evidence bag from a nearby police department containing a blood stained \'smiley,\' a homemade weapon composed of a red bandana with its ends tied together, with two large padlocks hanging from it, most commonly used by biker gangs.</item>
        <item>A commercial-sized Folger\'s coffee can, mostly full of breakfast blend ground coffee. Buried near the bottom is a Colt Detective Special .38 snub-nose, sealed in a plastic bag to keep out the coffee.</item>
        <item>A gun rack holding two Beneli M4 Super 90 Shotguns. These are the Law Enforcement versions, meaning they hold 7+1 rounds. One is loaded with saboted slugs, the other with 00 buckshot.</item>
        <item>A civilian-legal Uzi carbine, with 16-inch barrel and fixed wooden stock. This particular model is chambered in .22LR, and fires in semi-automatic only. Six magazines for it are present, along with a block of 500 .22LR rounds.</item>
        <item>One bowling ball, particle resin, psychedelic colours, slightly bloodstained.</item>
        <item>A FN FNP .45 caliber pistol inside a foam-lined aluminum pistol case, with two spare 14-round magazines.</item>
        <item>One North American Arms .22 Magnum mini-revolver (5-shot capacity, 1 and 5/8th-inch barrel)</item>
        <item>One Mossberg M500 Cruiser pistol grip 12 gauge shotgun and a box of 25 rounds of 00 buckshot in a nylon gym bag.</item>
        <item>A Heckler &amp; Koch UMP .45 caliber submachine gun fitted with a C-More red dot sight and Surefire M900 weaponlight foregrip. Comes with 7 25-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A Vietnam era M16 with starlight scope and silencer attached.</item>
        <item>A USMC KA-BAR Combat Knife. A tuft of black hair clings to the handle.</item>
        <item>A police shoulder holster containing a Manurhin MR-73 Revolver in .357. It is fully loaded, with six spare rounds attached to the holster. The serial number on the gun and the name sewn into the holster match that of a french police officer who vanished in 2006.</item>
        <item>An old Mosin Nagant M1891/30 sawn down into an "Obrez" configuration for easy concealment. The base of the grip has a hand-made sling attached to it. A full 5 round clip of 7.62x54mm R is nearby.</item>
        <item>A full shipment of fifty M9-pattern bayonets, still in the original manufacturer\'s crate. It was evidently rerouted here before it entered the Army\'s supply chain.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (10 round) Springfield M1A Scout .308 Win. semi-automatic rifle.</item>
        <item>A Mendoza K-62 single-shot .22 pistol, with a 5-inch barrel manufactured in Mexico during the 1960s. Fires .22 Short, Long and Long Rifle. The gun has three slots on each side of the frame that can hold extra cartridges for easier reloading. The pistol rests in a cardboard box along with an original English language advertisement.</item>
        <item>An empty pizza box. Any investigators who open the box discover a fully loaded MAC-10 submachine gun. A note scribbled onto the inside of the box reads "She\'s dead" (in the language of the Keeper\'s choice) repeated 1d100 times.</item>
        <item>A suicide-bombers vest with four blocks of C4 plastic explosives on the front and a dead-mans-grip detonator. There are cut up pieces of silver forks, spoons and other eating utensils duct taped to the explosives.</item>
        <item>A well oiled katana sword, with a sword skill of higher than 60 the player can discover that this is a traditionally forged hand crafted katana, engraved on the hilt is "To my brother budd the only man I ever loved" - bill</item>
        <item>Smith and Wesson M36 snub nosed revolver with 30 rounds remaining from a box of 50 .38 special FMJ rounds</item>
        <item>Inside a zippered case is a homebuilt 9mm bullpup-configuration carbine assembled from various modified parts: the stock is part steel and part polymer thumbhole stock from a H&amp;K SL8 rifle, the bolt and barrel come from a Sten gun, the recoil spring from an FN FAL rifle, etc. Accepts 32-round Sten magazines, of which there are 7 inside the case. A Picatinny rail has been installed on top of the gun, with flip-up iron sights.</item>
        <item>One well-worn Chinese K50M submachinegun (Chinese copy of Sudayev PPS43, minus the perforated steel heat shield around the barrel to simplify production), with a battered leather satchel containing six 35-round curved magazines.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded Smith&amp;Wesson 3914 9mm pistol in a leather belt-holster.</item>
        <item>An pre-ban Cobray M11 9mm submachine gun with a AWC Mk9 suppressor and five 32-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A powerful crossbow of the type used by deer hunters in some portions of the US, and two dozen aluminum arrows for it, razor broadheads already installed.</item>
        <item>Wrapped in oiled cloth is a large and heavy S&amp;W M1937 .45 ACP caliber revolver, showing some signs of wear but in excellent mechanical condition. Its serial number has been filed off, which is a shame because collectors pay a lot of money for them these days, but it\'s illegal to sell it through "normal" civilian channels with a defaced serial number. Also present are two dozen three-shot "half moon" clips for it; it is normally loaded with a pair at a time for a total of six. No ammunition is present, but this caliber is relatively common, at least in the US.</item>
        <item>A Taurus Judge revolver in a Western-style leather holster. Someone has painted the cylinders with an alternating red/black pattern, and when popped open the logic can be seen: each cylinder painted red is loaded with a .410 shotgun shell, and each cylinder painted black contains a .45 LC round.</item>
        <item>2 Unertl MEU SOC 1911 .45 semi-automatics with two spare clips each.</item>
        <item>A Vietnam War-era Claymore anti-personnel mine.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Red Label 12ga. over-and-under shotgun with 26-inch barrels.</item>
        <item>Several drop guns. All are pistols involved in crimes in the state of Arizona. They have been cleaned to avoid linking them to the FBI agent who stole them from crime scenes over the course of five years. Except for one finger print on the internal mechanisms and whatever finger prints the players leave on them.</item>
        <item>A Glock 17, one round chambered and three in the magazine.</item>
        <item>Five steel-bladed machetes with different blade styles, types of handles and lengths.</item>
        <item>A Para-Ordnance OEF IX-2008 .45 ACP caliber pistol; a special edition high capacity Para-Ordnance P14 with night sights and a Coyote Brown finish, with a matching color M3X tactical light that can be mounted under the barrel; comes a pistol box and 2 extra high-capacity 14-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A tray of seven stoppered glass vials, each containing white powder. The powder is weaponized anthrax, from stocks held by the Rhodesian government during the Apartheid era. There is space for an eighth, missing, vial...</item>
        <item>A Pelican gun case containing a Heckler &amp; Koch MP5/10 10mm submachine gun; the SMG has been customized with a PDW-style folding stock, a Surefire foregrip with an integral weaponlight, an Aimpoint red-dot sight, and a stainless steel screw-on suppressor. There are also eight 30-round straight magazines, all loaded with 180-grain jacketed hollowpoints inside the case.</item>
        <item>A DeLisle silenced carbine in .45 ACP, made during the Second World War. No magazines or ammo are present for it, however it does use the relatively common (at least in the US) .45 ACP pistol cartridge and the same magazines as the M1911A1 .45 pistol.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (30 round) Heckler&amp;Koch MP5K 9mm submachinegun with a laser-sight attached.</item>
        <item>A 12 gauge Stoeger Model 2000 semi-automatic shotgun with a 18.5 inch barrel and a black synthetic pistol grip stock. Comes in a carrying case along with 6 five-round boxes of 00 buckshot.</item>
        <item>An broken hand air pump for bicycles.\nCloser inspection shows that the "air pump" is actually modified to fire a shotgun shell, with the bottom of the pump directed at the target. A single shot close-range weapon.</item>
        <item>A CRKT Hissatsu tactical knife with a curved 7.125 inch blade, in a Kydex sheath.</item>
        <item>A Sig-Sauer P226 9mm pistol, in a cheap plastic shoulder holster. It has four rounds left in the magazine.</item>
        <item>A single TBG-7V thermobaric rocket for a russian RPG-7 launcher.</item>
        <item>A SOG Fasthawk tactical tomahawk, with a short 12" handle wrapped in parachute cord.</item>
        <item>A thermos filled with thermite and broken thermometers. The play on words is not lost upon you though a bad jolt could set the thing off.</item>
        <item>A cheap briefcase containing a worn Taurus 92B 9mm pistol and two empty extra magazines. There are three rounds in the gun\'s magazine.</item>
        <item>An oil-stained handkerchief wrapped around an old Ruger Security Six .38 revolver. The gun has a 4" barrel and is fully loaded.</item>
        <item>A baseball bat with a railroad spike driven through the end, which makes it resemble a medieval warhammer.</item>
        <item>A battered but still serviceable Browning Hi-Power 9mm, stamped with Rhodesian Light Infantry markings. A full 13 round magazine, loaded with FMJ ball ammunition, is inserted into the weapon.</item>
        <item>A steel and titanium ice-axe as used to climb glaciers and icy cliff-walls.</item>
        <item>An opened box of .45 handgun ammunition. It contains ten .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>An extremely small handgun, barely smaller than a derringer and easily concealable in the palm of the hand, that is chambered for a single .410 shotgun shell. Obviously useless beyond point-blank range, and also packing an absurd recoil due to its diminutive size.</item>
        <item>A sawn-off double-barreled 12 gauge shotgun from an indeterminate manufacturer. One of the barrels have been filled with lead, presumably to facilitate the gun\'s use as a club. The other barrel is loaded.</item>
        <item>A tied-up handkerchief containing nine 12 gauge shotgun shells.</item>
        <item>A disassembled and ammunition-less FN SCAR-H STD assault rifle (chambered for 7.62 NATO). The parts have been neatly laid out in an "exploded" schematic.</item>
        <item>A Franchi SPAS-12 shotgun with a missing shoulder stock.</item>
        <item>A Carl Gustav M1 with no ammo.</item>
        <item>Boobytrap: an old 1950 RCA television capacitor with a standard wall plug. The capacitor is fused to a mount that will seat on most doorknobs. A few other modifications include a hyper-sensitive mercury switch that will cause the capacitor to discharge into the doorknob upon which it\'s seated.</item>
        <item>An aluminum bat, spray painted white, with the word "White Power" done in black paint on it. The bat has several dents and patches of blood or flesh. Testing the gore reveals someone had a sense of Irony, as the blood matches a White Southern Preacher, and suspected member of the KKK, who was found brutally beaten in the middle of nowhere. There are no suspects because the murder weapon was never found.</item>
        <item>A fifty round box of .38 ammunition.</item>
        <item>A 50-round factory box labeled Remington UMC 9mm 115gr FMJ but which actually contains odd lots of 9mm factory JHPs, a few PMC Starfires, some Winchester, some Gold Dot, and some Georgia Arms 147gr for a total of 28 rounds.</item>
        <item>2 M14 incendiary grenades.</item>
        <item>A prop 1921 Thompson SMG in a beat-up violin case.</item>
        <item>A 12 gauge Remington Spartan Sawed Off shotgun, hidden under a desk and pointing towards the door.</item>
        <item>A Winchester Model 70 bolt-action rifle, chambered for .243 Winchester. This rifle was reported stolen from an El Paso, Texas gun store five years previously.</item>
        <item>A pair of fully automatic AK-74s, both weapons were used in the murder of 5 gang members and an undercover DEA agent. If the weapons are used and the bullets are recovered federal investigators will be on seen with in a few days.</item>
        <item>A Rubbermaid container with 60 assorted AK-74 magazines ranging from 20 rounds to 40 rounds. They are all loaded but some are not fully loaded. The number and type of each magazine is up to the game master.</item>
        <item>A Webley Mk. VI revolver in the old .455 British service caliber, very old and worn with a few small freckles of rust here and there, but mechanically sound. Box also contains several boxes of World War I vintage ammunition for it; at Keeper\'s discretion, the gun may occasionally misfire with this ammunition due to possible deterioration of the nearly century-old primers.</item>
        <item>A heavily customized Colt 1911 handgun. The most obvious modification is the handgrips, which have a stylized naked woman on them. The gun is not loaded.</item>
        <item>A custom-made folding knife with a four-inch, partially serrated kriss blade with a gladiator point. The blade is matte black, precision crafted ceramic, strong as folded steel but much lighter and sharper, invisible to metal detectors.</item>
        <item>4 Daewoo USAS-12 12-gauge selective-fire shotguns - with 2 clips and 1 drum each.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing eight 7.62mm rifle rounds.</item>
        <item>A blue blanket wrapped around an empty Mossberg 590 Cruiser 12 gauge pump shotgun and a plastic bag containing twelve 12 gauge shotgun shells.</item>
        <item>A two foot long piece of iron pipe with skateboarders grip tape wound around one end.</item>
        <item>Resting on a crate is a Pelican foam-lined weapons case that contains a collection of handguns chambered for the 10mm round, These include a full-sized Glock 20 and a compact Model 29; a Smith &amp; Wesson Model 610 revolver with a 4-inch barrel; a Smith &amp; Wesson Model 1076 semi-auto pistol; an EAA Witness Elite Match semi-auto pistol; a Kimber Eclipse Custom II semi-automatic and a Colt Delta Elite. There are five spare magazines for each automatic and four preloaded speed loaders for the revolver. Inside the crate are boxes containing a total of 4000 rounds of 165-grain Speer Gold Dot 10mm hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>Footlocker: 3 S&amp;W 686 4" barrel .357 magnum revolvers, 3 Browning Hi-Powers (9mm w/ 9 magazines), 2 Mossburg 12 gauge shotguns (collapsible stock), 2 Colt Commando/AR-15s w/8-30 round magazines</item>
        <item>A styrofoam take-away box for chinese food containing a fully loaded Walther PPK 7.65mm (.32) pistol and a switchblade.</item>
        <item>A large garbage bag and a shopping cart filled with empty, crushed aluminum cans, like one would expect to see a homeless person pushing around. The garbage bag is filled with ratty, grimy clothing, and contains a note saying "FOR GOING DEEP UNDERCOVER."\nShould the investigators rummage through the cans, they\'ll find an H&amp;K MP7, two Makarov pistols, and a pistol-grip Mossberg shotgun, all loaded and wrapped in Wal-Mart bags to keep out the sticky soda-can sludge.</item>
        <item>A Stevens 311 .410-gauge double barreled shotgun. Comes with 5 20 round boxes of 000 buckshot.</item>
        <item>An opened box of .357 Magnum semi-jacketed hollowpoint bullets produced by Bitteroot Valley Ammunition of Montana. There are forty rounds left out of fifty.</item>
        <item>Case containing eight M67 hand grenades, Five have been painted pastel pink, the remaining three have been painted a fluorescent yellow.</item>
        <item>Some sort of bull-pup semi-to-full-automatic assault rifle, totally unlike anything even the most gun-fondling agent can recognise. There are no distinguishing marks, no logos, no serial-numbers on it - and all the workings appear to have been made specifically for this (unknown) make of gun. Considering its space-age qualities, it uses a 5-round 5.56mm stripper clip.</item>
        <item>This crate contains two dozen US M67 fragmentation hand grenades.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Vaquero revolver, chambered in .45 Long Colt, with a beautifully made leather holster and gun-belt made to look like that of an Old West gunfighter. The revolver itself is unloaded, but a total of thirty-six rounds have been slipped into the loops of the gun-belt.</item>
        <item>A stag-handled hunting knife in an old brown leather sheath. The blade is 6 inches long and has the initals "K.A.R." inscribed on one side.</item>
        <item>3 full cardboard boxes of police 12 gauge rubber bullets, 20 in each. The boxes are all stamped "Defective: do not use against civilians"</item>
        <item>A knife with a hand-forged, hammered 6-inch blade, a curved staghorn handle and a brass guard.</item>
        <item>A SIG P-228 with four, 20 round magazines.</item>
        <item>A seemingly broken television set; however, closer inspection reveals the screen to have been removed and replaced, and if it is taken off (or shattered) it will be discovered that most of its internal parts have been removed to make room for a Mini-Uzi, three magazines, and a suppressor.</item>
        <item>A .45 Norinco M-1911A1C pistol with two shots remaining.</item>
        <item>A red dufflebag with the Adidas logo on it; it contains ten 20-round boxes of Federal Premium Hydra-Shok .45 ACP 230-grain hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Mark II (Government Target Model) .22LR pistol and four factory magazines loaded with Eley Tenex pistol ammunition.</item>
        <item>A fiskars hatchet, worn from use but serviceable and sharp.</item>
        <item>A Taser X12 Less-Lethal shotgun. 12 Gauge, but modified so that it only accepts less-lethal rounds, such as beanbags and rubber bullets. The gun has four rails for mounting accessories. It is fully loaded (4+1 in the chamber) with specialized Taser rounds. An additional 5 Taser rounds are mounted on the side.</item>
        <item>Unloaded Beretta DT-10 shotgun.</item>
        <item>A high end sound suppressor for a Glock 9mm. It has built in sights on top.</item>
        <item>Wrapped up in a camo-colored Snuggie you find a Rock River Arms AR-15 .223 carbine with a collapsible stock and a PIcatinny quad-rail grip mounting a green laser, a 230 lumen flashlight and an Aimpoint Red-Dot sight. Two pairs of 30-round magazines are also to be found, each pair taped together "jungle style".</item>
        <item>A worn Russian Nagant M1895 revolver with a threaded barrel and supressor (most revolvers can\'t be suppressed, but this design can be).</item>
        <item>An open 50-round box of 7.62x38R ammunition, with 21 rounds left</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (6 rounds) Taurus PT145 Millennium .45 pistol. The small gun comes together with a cheap plastic ankle-holster.</item>
        <item>One Remington 870 12 gauge shotgun, police magnum model. Two boxes ( 50 rounds ) of 00 buckshot are with the shotgun.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a Sig-Sauer P226 9mm pistol. The gun is soot-blackened as if it has passed through fire, but is fully functional and has four rounds in the magazine.</item>
        <item>A javelin.</item>
        <item>A Chiappa Rhino revolver chambered in .40 S&amp;W. It has a 5-inch barrel and comes in a carrying case along with five full-moon clips preloaded with six rounds of .40 hollowpoints each.</item>
        <item>A heavily soiled Mendoza M1934 light machine gun</item>
        <item>Two H&amp;K G3A3 battle rifles, with seven empty magazines and 200 rounds of surplus 7.62x51mm ammunition. A sheet of notebook paper wrapped around the handguard of one indicates they went from the Mexican Army, to the Mexican cartels, to an Arizona militia, to this room, with multiple murders along the way.</item>
        <item>This footlocker contains four .303 caliber Short Magazine Lee Enfield rifles. Close examination reveals them to be rather crude-looking, with sloppy machine work, crooked stampings, poor finish on the metal and wood, etc.; an ARMORER skill roll reveals that these are "Khyber Pass" copies manufactured from assorted scrap metal by Pathan gunsmiths in what is now Pakistan, but they seem to be functional and safe to fire. Probably. No ammunition is present.</item>
        <item>A C-9 Hi-Point 9mm handgun with two magazines and a note with "LIFETIME WARRANTY" scribbled on it.</item>
        <item>A golf bag containing a small arsenal consisting of a 12-gauge Beretta UGB semi-automatic break-open shotgun with over-under barrels, a pair of Heckler &amp; Koch MK23 Mod 0 .45 caliber pistols and a pair of Armalite AR-24 9mm semi-automatic pistols.</item>
        <item>A Monadnock brand side-handled nightstick, wrapped in an LAPD T-shirt.</item>
        <item>Straight razor with a four-leaf clover etched on one side of the blade. The handle incorporates a rabbit\'s foot.</item>
        <item>A home-made dirty-bomb, about the size of a large trash-can, in a lead casing. Built by a Jihadi cell in Denver back in 2009. Recovered by a NEST team soon after. Stolen by Delta Green in 2010.</item>
        <item>A Smith &amp; Wesson M&amp;P .40 caliber pistol ( use Glock 22 for stats ) with three fifteen round magazines, all loaded with HP ammo. A trace of the serial number reveals it was purchased by the Columbus, Ohio police department five years ago.</item>
        <item>An H&amp;K UMP .45 ACP submachine gun with silencer and 7 25 round magazines.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing a tiny two-barreled "Derringer"-style handgun (loaded with two .38 rounds) and four loose .38 rounds.</item>
        <item>A Mendoza RM2 light machine gun in excellent working condition.</item>
        <item>A singular rocket for the M20 Super Bazooka, its age has made it unstable and dangerous to handle.</item>
        <item>Two long-gun cases. Each contains a weapon that resembles an M-16 rifle except larger. These are a pair of Akdal MKA 1919 12-gauge semi-automatic shotguns, fed by magazines, three 10-round magazines are stored in each case. One of the shotguns has a matte black finish, the other a woodland camo finish.</item>
        <item>A pair of brass knuckles.</item>
        <item>.22 LR single-shot American Derringer Model 2 Pen Gun, unloaded.</item>
        <item>An unopened box of twenty-five 9mm rounds.</item>
        <item>A small fabric bag with eighteen .45 rounds in it.</item>
        <item>A 5 gallon bucket full to the brim with snub-nose .38 special revolvers of various makes. All are unloaded. A paper tag tied to the bucket\'s handle features a handwritten note: "It\'s Steve\'s turn to reload - M." Below this note is a scrawled reply in a different hand, which says "No it\'s not. -S."</item>
        <item>Four M7 CS gas grenades.</item>
        <item>A powerful metal slingshot.</item>
        <item>Note on this container says "Militia Kit." Contains four new Chinese SKS semiauto carbines with chrome-lined barrels, complete with folding spike bayonets, cleaning kits, and Chinese surplus load bearing vests with ten pockets each holding three loaded ten-round SKS clips, plus two sealed steel "spam cans" each with another thousand rounds of Rumanian surplus 7.62x39mm ammo. Box also contains a motley mix of surplus camouflage clothing: East German pants, Czech tunic, and US Vietnam-era surplus olive drab "boonie hats," all in sizes to fit most anyone in the PC group.</item>
        <item>SIG-Sauer P220 .45 ACP pistol with one 8 round magazine, loaded with five rounds. If the serial number is traced, it will lead to an National Park Service Park Ranger who went missing two years ago.</item>
        <item>An empty bottle of fine wine, its original contents replaced with a significant number of .22LR rounds.</item>
        <item>A bloodstained black t-shirt (size Medium) wrapped around a Heckler&amp;Koch USP Compact .45 pistol (four rounds of the full eight remains in the magazine) and one extra magazine (empty).</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing a SIG Sauer Mosquito .22 pistol and, an extra magazine and a box of fifty .22 rounds.</item>
        <item>An old Walther PPK 7.65mm pistol with 3 rounds left in the magazine.</item>
        <item>Colt Combat Commander pistol chambered in 9mm plus two extra 9-round magazines.</item>
        <item>An M240D medium machine gun. The M240D is, unfortunately, designed for aircraft use, and is poorly suited for (though still usable for) individual operation. It has spade grips and lacks any sort of bipod or other stand, but at least it has sights.</item>
        <item>An Vietnam-era M60 machine gun and several belts of ammunition.</item>
        <item>An old wooden box holds two pistols (a H&amp;K USP and a Ruger MK II), two magazines and ammo for each, and matching silencers. The accompanying note says: "You cowboys love to take your brash Jewish girls to the Opera, but you should try a Fraulein or a red-blooded American gal sometime." Quickly scribbled under it, in another person\'s handwriting, says: "THE RUGER MUST NEVER SHOW UP IN TUCSON."</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing eighteen .38 rounds.</item>
        <item>An H&amp;R Pardner Protector 12-ga. pump-action shotgun.</item>
        <item>A box of fifty .22 rounds.</item>
        <item>A pair of Nagant M1895 Revolvers in a leather saddle bag. Both are loaded and there are roughly 50 odd rounds loose in the bottom of the bag.</item>
        <item>An M1 Garand rifle with two en bloc clips.</item>
        <item>A large can of .22 ammunition. There are ninety-eight rounds remaining in the can.</item>
        <item>A plastic ziploc bag containing a syringe and a small vial of clear liquid marked "H". The liquid is a heroin solution and strong enough to kill even a habitual addict.</item>
        <item>One Luger P08 9mm pistol. In perfect working order and loaded with one full clip.</item>
        <item>1d4 Russian hand grenades, hidden within a non-functional rice cooker.</item>
        <item>Three sticks of dynamite duct-taped together, with an attached detonator and a ten second fuse.</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing an assortment of handgun ammunition: nineteen .22 rounds, fourteen .25 rounds, ten .32 rounds, eight 9mm rounds, four 10mm rounds and a single .45 round.</item>
        <item>A black plastic box containing a fully loaded Glock 19 9mm pistol and one loaded extra magazine.</item>
        <item>One Smith and Wesson Model 10 .38 special revolver in a zippered nylon pistol case, unloaded. Also present is a box of 50 rounds, .38 special, SJHP ammo. On the backstrap of the revolver is engraved "RHKP 8842".</item>
        <item>An FN FNP-45 Tactical .45 caliber semi-automatic pistol with a threaded barrel and a Trijicon RM02 reflex sight.. Comes in a FN carry case along with two extra magazines, a cleaning kit, and an Advanced Armament Corp. Ti-RANT suppressor,</item>
        <item>A scuffed wooden box containing an old Smith&amp;Wesson Model 10 Victory .38 revolver. The gun was made in 1943 and quite worn, but still functional and fully loaded.</item>
        <item>Four AK47 type rifles, very beat-up looking (those with appropriate skills may recognize them as the Yugoslav M72 variant), a bit scratched and rusty with crude Cyrillic carvings on the wooden buttstocks (linguists may note Bosnian Serb "CCCC" "Serb Solidarity" slogans, etc.). The rifles are full-auto military versions, and all serial numbers have been removed. There is also a satchel of five or six 30-round magazines for each rifle, and a few ammo cans containing a total of maybe 500 rounds of old Chinese copper-washed steel-case 7.62x39mm ammo--not quite enough to load all the mags. The rifles are filthy and could use a good cleaning and oiling but will work.</item>
        <item>A Ruger 22/45 .22LR target pistol mounted with a Primary Arms green dot sight, a Viridian green laser slight, threaded barrel and a Gemtech Alpine suppressor. Comes with 4 (empty) 10-round magazines.</item>
        <item>Several jars of black gunpowder.</item>
        <item>A heavy hunting knife with scabbard.</item>
        <item>An adjustable leather shoulder-holster containing a fully loaded Smith&amp;Wesson Model 60 .38 revolver with a 4" barrel.</item>
        <item>A large-ish and rather heavy box from amazon.com. Opening the box reveals a half-dozen boxes of 9mm ammunition. Opening each of those boxes reveals that the boxes are actually mislabeled; rather than containing standard parabellum ammo, they\'re actually full of hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A single-shot Cooey Model 84 20-gauge shotgun.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded Glock 17 9mm pistol. It has been painted pink.</item>
        <item>A very large Bowie knife of the type once popular among 19th Century frontiersmen and adventurers, in a sheath made from some unidentifiable cellType of spotted leather. Engraved on the side of the blade is the motto, "DO NOT DRAW ME WITHOUT HONOR, DO NOT SHEATHE ME WITHOUT JUSTICE."</item>
        <item>A pair of .45-caliber Smith &amp; Wesson 4506 semi-automatic pistols in a plastic case, complete with 3 spare 8-round magazines and a double shoulder-holster rig.</item>
        <item>500g block of C4 plastic explosive, still in its demo wrapping; wrapped in shiny red paper and tissue.</item>
        <item>One Glock 17 9mm pistol, three loaded magazines ( 17 round capacity, HP ammunition ) and one kydex on the waistband holster in a watertight metal ammunition box.</item>
        <item>A balisong knife duct-taped to the inside of an empty tissue box.</item>
        <item>Footlocker: 1000 rounds each of 5.56 NATO &amp; 7.62 NATO. 100 rounds each of 12 gauge and 16 gauge., US Army soldier\'s manual (level 1)</item>
        <item>Improvised unguided small rockets, made by combining commercially available model rockets and filling the nose-cone elements with home-made flash powder wired to an impact detonator. While it is unlikely they would cause damage (if they hit at all), they do produce a bright light and might work as an incendiary device.</item>
        <item>A Citadel LE Tactical 12-gauge pump action shotgun.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a standard issue US Military M4A1 Carbine (With Safe, Semi, Auto fire selectors), and an ACOG scope mounted to the rails. The shell of the weapon is done in an almost cartoonishly bright desert camo pattern, which matches none used by any military. "This machine kills terrorists" has been clumsily scratched, as if with a knife, into the stock. The magazine for the weapon is empty, but there is a bullet in the chamber.</item>
        <item>.338 Lapua Surgeon rifle customized by GA Precision.</item>
        <item>Hand lapped and trued action, 27 inch Krieger heavy fluted barrel, Jewell trigger, McMillan stock, 3-20x50 Schmidt and Bender rifle scope mounted on a pair of Badger Ordnance rings.</item>
        <item>Comes with a box of 50 hand reloaded 300 gr. Sierra Match Kings on fire formed brass and a proper range card</item>
        <item>A disassembled Heckler&amp;Koch MP5 9mm submachinegun. The clip contains twenty rounds. It requires some skill to put it back together.</item>
        <item>SIG-Sauer P238 .380 ACP pistol in a lockable case (with two spare 6-round magazines and an IWB holster)</item>
        <item>A collection of sharp and well maintained kitchen cutlery in a leather folding case with the words "Kiss the Cook," embroidered across the covering flap.</item>
        <item>A brown paper bag containing a worn and slightly rusty Colt 1911 .45 pistol and two extra magazines. The gun and the magazines are fully loaded.</item>
        <item>A box of twenty .44 Magnum rounds.</item>
        <item>Thick black disk, bigger than a dinner plate and weighing more than fifteen pounds; hastily scribbled notes left with it say it is a Yugoslav TMA-4 antitank mine, with instructions telling how to set it up and arm it, but not how to disarm it once set up.</item>
        <item>A single-shot break-open twelve-gauge shotgun held together by scotch tape and Mighty Putty. It comes with twenty slug shells.</item>
        <item>A Makarov pistol with one magazine and a white cardboard box containing 50 9x18 hollowpoints. Close inspection will reveal that the pistol was maunfactured in East Germany in 1973.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (8 rounds) SIG-Sauer P239 9mm pistol in a cheap plastic ankle-holster.</item>
        <item>An SKS carbine with sling and chest pouch containing 10, 10 round stripper clips loaded with FMJ ammunition. There are no importation marks and the serial number is untraceable, indicating it was not imported legally. It appears to have been made in 1952 in the USSR.</item>
        <item>Five 50-round boxes of .22 LR subsonic 38-grain lead hollowpoint bullets from Fiocchi Shooting Dynamics</item>
        <item>An Enfield No.2 snubnosed .38 S&amp;W revolver.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (5 rounds) Smith&amp;Wesson 340PD .38 revolver with an 1.875" barrel. The snubnosed gun comes with a nice leather belt-holster.</item>
        <item>A dented metal cookie box containing a fully loaded Ruger Vaquero Bisley .357 Magnum single-action revolver, with ivory grips. There are also four loose .357 Magnum rounds in the box.</item>
        <item>An HK MP5 submachinegun with a silencer attached. There are four spare magazines with it, all loaded with 9mm Glaser Safety Slugs. Checking the serial number reveals that it was purchased in 1985 by a "security consulting" firm known to be a front for the CIA.</item>
        <item>An Israeli \'Hush Puppy\'. A modified Ruger 10/22 with integrated silencer. Short and light, it can be fired with little more sound than the firing pin striking the round.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .45 Ruger SR1911 pistol, with a leather belt holster.</item>
        <item>A 20-rd box of Hornady 10mm Auto 155gr XTP JHP with 11 rounds left.</item>
        <item>Simonich Crowfoot knife with a 3-inch blade, contoured G-10 handles and a Concealex neck sheath supplied with 24" Para Chain.</item>
        <item>A tomahawk of modern design. It has a fairly short wooden handle a spike on the reverse side of the head, and a leather sheath. A successful roll of an appropriate skill might reveal that it appears to be a genuine Peter LaGana "Vietnam Tomahawk."</item>
        <item>Customized Smith &amp; Wesson Model 10 .38 Special revolver with a heavy barrel, action job, hard chrome finish, and a Tasco Pro-Point sight.</item>
        <item>A Beretta 92FS pistol. Attached to the trigger guard is a note reading "Magazine = bomb. Trigger = detonator. Have fun."\nTrue to form, the pistol is booby trapped to explode when the trigger is pulled.</item>
        <item>A Casull .454 Revolver produced by Freedom Arms. There are two boxes of ammo for this massive handgun with a total of 38 rounds. Several are missing from one box.</item>
        <item>4 Glock 21 .45 ACP pistols (strangely, these have no serial numbers - they were not filed off - they are just not on the guns at all; pointing to the fact that they are very good copies or have been manufactured illegally) There are 10 13-round magazines for these.</item>
        <item>A Bersa FS22M .22 pistol with a silencer. The magazine contains four shots.</item>
        <item>You find two containers next to each other. One is a large rifle case with a genuine and well maintained Red Jacket Firearms RTS-ZK-S/S-12 suppressed automatic shotgun.</item>
        <item>The other is a plastic olive drab military style box. Inside are 14 fully loaded clips for the weapon, a modified and adjustible Multicam tac-vest for said clips (holds 6 normally, however a crafty agent/investigator can slip in two more), and a large unopened bottle of Moorehen\'s Shredded Sporran 18 Year Old Blended Scottish Whiskey.</item>
        <item>A small note in the box reads "Don\'t be an ass! When you\'re done clean the weapon, put the weapon back, replace the ammo, and replace the bottle of scotch! This weapon has served many well. Treat her with respect, and it will be there to save your ass when the shit hits the fan. Good hunting and watch your back!"</item>
        <item>Six Glock 22 .40-caliber pistols, twelve fully-loaded magazines, and a half-dozen shoulder holsters, all contained in fresh butcher paper and hastily wrapped in white electrical tape. If traced, the weapons were reported stolen from an LAPD armory in May, 1999. They have never been fired.</item>
        <item>A Mendoza HM-3S sub-machine-gun</item>
        <item>A sawed-off .410 double-barrel shotgun, taken from the body of a mugger who was foolish enough to accost a Delta Green agent during a mission. Sixteen shells lie beside it.</item>
        <item>A Remington 870, alongside a package of 1d20 rounds of blank shotgun ammunition.</item>
        <item>Desert Eagle Mark VII .44 Magnum pistol with two clips - unloaded.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a well-oiled Astra A-100 Panther 9mm pistol and one extra magazine. Both the gun and the magazine are empty of ammunition.</item>
        <item>A 20-round box of Triton 10mm Auto 155gr "Quik-Shok" with 7 rounds left.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded Springfield Armory 1911 Ultra Compact 9mm pistol in a leather belt-holster.</item>
        <item>A three-inch folding-blade. The plastic handle has been painted in acrylics with an intricate floral pattern.</item>
        <item>A Serbu Super Shorty 12-gauge custom compact, a stockless short shotgun with a spring-loaded folding fore stock, built from a Mossberg Maverick 88. The weapon is mounted inside a cheap dresser with a cardboard back and facing the entrance to the Green Box.</item>
        <item>A Hi-Point 4095TS .40 S&amp;W carbine in a black carrying case. The case also contains a breakdown tool and 7 factory standard 10-round magazines.</item>
        <item>1 large Zippo-type lighter. It is actually an assassination weapon. When opened and squeezed in proper way it fires one .22LR bullet coated with cyanide. It needs to be fired at point blank to hit.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded 9mm Glock 19 pistol, in a leather belt holster.</item>
        <item>A WASR 10/63 Kalashnikov pattern rifle. Ostensibly semi-automatic with a bullet button restricting free magazine removal and fittings for accepting magazines with ten rounds maximum. It comes with a single twenty round magazine.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Mk. III .22 caliber heavy barrel target pistol with adjustable target sights and two spare magazines, serial number obliterated.</item>
        <item>A semi-automatic civilian copy of a Yugo M70, 7.62x39mm AK-47 type rifle. Three loaded 30 round magazines are present and the rifle is fitted with a sling.</item>
        <item>A used styrofoam fast-food container with a fully loaded (9 rounds) Bersa Thunder 380 .380ACP pistol inside. The gun is quite greasy could use a good cleaning.</item>
        <item>A "dime" machete, the kind famous for hacking off the limbs of African children in various genocidal cleansings. Stamped metal, mass produced in China for a dime apiece.</item>
        <item>A Springfield M1A SOCOM16 .308-caliber rifle. Comes with three 20 round magazines.</item>
        <item>An Ithaca 37 12 gauge police riot shotgun of the eight-shot variety, with old dried blood and bits of hair on its hard plastic buttplate and what look like tooth marks on the sides of the wooden buttstock.</item>
        <item>A high-quality replica Viking longsword.</item>
        <item>A 33-round magazine for a Glock 18 machine pistol. It also fits a Glock 17, 19, 26 or 34 ( all 9mm Glock pistols ). It is loaded with 9mm FMJ ammunition. Concealing a pistol using this magazine would be laughable.</item>
        <item>A folding entrenching tool ("E-tool") that has been sharpened to a razor edge.</item>
        <item>A submachine gun that resembles a scaled-down M3 \'Grease Gun\'. It is chambered for .22LR and packed inside a foam-lined carrying case along with three 30-round stick magazines. The SMG is obviously a custom job, and features no serial numbers or manufacturer\'s marks.</item>
        <item>A large messenger bag, containing a H&amp;K HK416 Assault Rifle, with an aftermarket ACOG scope, integral suppressor and vertical foregrip. Also in the bag are three fully-loaded 30-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A large Boombox-style CD-player, loaded with a CD-single from MC Hammer: "Can\'t Touch This". The back of the CD-player has been partially removed and someone examining the inside will find a fully loaded Glock 19 9mm pistol carefully nestled among the electronics.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box containing an MK Arms MK-760 9mm submachine gun - a carbon copy of the Smith &amp; Wesson M-76 submachine gun manufactured in the 1980s.</item>
        <item>A pair of 70cm long Rattan sticks, as used in Eskrima or similar Filipino martial arts. One of them has deep bite-marks in it and the handle sections of them are heavily stained by dried blood.</item>
        <item>An authentic medieval broadsword.</item>
        <item>A box of Winchester .40 Black Talon with 9 rounds left,</item>
        <item>A Winchester model 70 in .375 H&amp;H equipped with a Leupold 1.5-4x scope, the rifle is stored in pelican case and accompanied by two boxes of premium ammunition.</item>
        <item>A Vepr .309 semi-automatic rifle with a 20-inch barrel, customized with a Troy Battle Ax polymer adjustable buttstock on a recoil-reducing ITT hydraulic buffer tube, an Aimpoint CompM2 red-dot sight and an SGM Tactical forend with a Magpul Rail Vertical Grip mounted underneath. Stashed inside a soft rifle bag along with four 20-round magazines and 5 20-round boxes of 168-grain polymer-tipped .308 Winchester Hornady TAP Personal Defense Ammo.</item>
        <item>A replica Fairborn-Sykes fighting knife, made famous by the British Commandos of WWII. It is definitely a combat grade replica, and has been painstakingly sharpened.</item>
        <item>1 J.C. Higgins Model 20 12-gauge pump-action shotgun.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (6 rounds) Raven Arms MP-25 .25 pistol, with a cheap plastic ankle holster.</item>
        <item>A singular rocket for the M20 Super Bazooka, its age has made it unstable and dangerous to handle.</item>
        <item>An entire crate of M72 Light Anti-Armor Weapons, whose packaging seem to imply they were shipped to the Israeli Defense Forces during the Yom Kippur War in \'73.\nHowever, this crate was withheld from final shipment, because it contains training units. Their rocket will fire as usual, but when it hits, it produces a cloud of light-blue powdered chalk rather than an explosion. There is no external indication that these are training units, unfortunately, and odds are the only way the investigators will find out is through trial and error.</item>
        <item>A collection of assorted bayonets from several countries, mostly AK bayonets from the Warsaw Pact.</item>
        <item>Two mat black sealable, waterproof military crates. Inside one are 6 FNP90s and 24 magazines Inside the other are 6 100rnd boxes of AP 5.7x28mm ammo and two boxes of silver coated \'\'loup-garou Industies\'\' bullets, the label for these boxes is obviously home made and easily comes off.</item>
        <item>2 Ithaca Model 37 Stakeout shotguns (12-Gauge)</item>
        <item>VSS Vintorez integrally suppressed sniper rifle</item>
        <item>Fires a rare 9x39 round. It\'s fully automatic as well as semi-automatic</item>
        <item>Inside a Doskocil plastic carrying case is a DPMS Panther Arms AR-15 carbine chambered for the Remington 6.8 SPC cartridge. It has been fitted with an EOTech holographic sight and a vertical foregrip with a Surefire flashlight built into it, just below the muzzle. Two extra 20 round boxes of 6.8 SPC ammunition (manufactured by Silver State Armory) are included.</item>
        <item>A dozen unopened 100-round value packs of Winchester .45 ACP 230-grain FMJ (full metal jacket) rounds.</item>
        <item>An SOG Trident TF-1 folding knife.</item>
        <item>A Steyr MPi81 9mm submachine gun, stashed in a foam lined case, with three spare 32-round clips.</item>
        <item>A Radom Vis-35 pistol and 3 empty magazines.</item>
        <item>A large popcorn container full of stale popcorn and a worn Colt Python .357 Magnum revolver with 6" barrel. The gun is fully loaded.</item>
        <item>Four Colt revolvers in a long pistol case: a pair of snub-nosed Colt Cobra revolvers with 2-inch barrels, one is chambered for .38 Special, the other for .22LR; a Colt Lawman MK III .357 Magnum with a four-inch barrel; and a Colt Diamondback .38 Special.</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing a small Bersa Thunder 32 .32 pistol and an extra magazine. Neither the gun nor the extra magazine is loaded.</item>
        <item>A 1970\'s vintage stainless steel Norton TP-70 .25 semiautomatic pistol, with two spare 6-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A shoebox containing twenty \'Dragon\'s Breath\' incendiary twelve-gauge shotgun rounds. These shells are filled with a napalm-like mixture, and create a twenty-foot-long cone of fire when used.</item>
        <item>A Tekna Dive Knife with a 3 3/4" double-edged blade inside a plastic sheath.</item>
        <item>Armalite AR-10 7.62x51mm semiauto target rifle with heavy match-grade stainless steel barrel and a large and expensive target scope, plus five 20-round magazines and a dozen 20-round boxes of US military surplus 7.62x51mm M852 Match ammunition. Small notebook taped to rifle\'s buttstock indicates rifle and scope are zeroed at 300 meters and has exhaustively detailed elevation, trajectory, and wind drift data for this ammunition out to 1000 meters.</item>
        <item>Five WW2-era 90 mm anti-aircraft shells in wooden box. Black writing on the side says, "Do not jostle or shake."</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .44 Magnum Taurus 444 revolver, with an adjustable leather shoulder holster.</item>
        <item>A Mateba Model 6 Unica Autorevolver, in a leather shoulder holster. The semi-automatic revolver is chambered in .357 Magnum, and is fully loaded.</item>
        <item>Resting on a chamois cloth in the bottom of a carton are a matched pair of nickel-plated Rock Island Armory 1911-A1 .38 Super pistols. Also in the carton are four empty 9-round magazines and a fifty-round box of 130-grain FMJ.</item>
        <item>A side-handled Monadnock police nightstick, with carrying loop for a utility belt.</item>
        <item>Two Tokarev TT-33 pistols, chambered in 7.62x25mm, and in very worn condition. One of them has the word "o" engraved on its slide, while the other is engraved with the word "." Included are three very corroded, probably dangerous to fire, rounds of 7.62x25mm ammunition, and an autographed photo of Joseph Stalin.</item>
        <item>A plastic ice cream box containing fourteen .38 rounds.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing twenty-four .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>An STI Tactical 4.15 9mm semi-automatic in a carrying case, with several 18-round flush fit magazines loaded with Hornady hollowpoint rounds. A Silencerco supressor will fit right on the pistol\'s threaded bull barrel.</item>
        <item>A Hi-Standard Sentinel .22 rimfire revolver (will accept .22 Short, .22 Long and .22LR) with a 4-inch barrel and a blued finish.</item>
        <item>A cardboard pizza box marked with "Luigi\'s Pizza". The box contains a Beretta 92FS 9mm pistol with an attached silencer. Only thirteen rounds are left in the magazine.</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing a fully loaded (5 shot) Smith&amp;Wesson Model 357 "Night Guard" .357 Magnum revolver with a 2" barrel. Together with the snub-nosed gun the box also contains a speedloader with five extra .357 Magnum rounds.</item>
        <item>A suitcase containing a disassembled Galil SAR Assault Carbine chambered for 5.56mm rounds, and three loaded 35-round magazines. It takes a successful Rifle skill roll to re-assemble the gun.</item>
        <item>A loaded Husqvarna 310AS double-barreled 12 gauge shotgun. The barrel has been slightly shortened and a laser-sight attached to the top.</item>
        <item>An old swedish M45 9mm submachinegun, with fourteen rounds remaining in the clip. The wooden handle is carved with tiny Vietnamese script which roughly translates to "Always the Company".</item>
        <item>A WWII flare gun modified to fire grenades. One such grenade is loaded.</item>
        <item>A 9mm Ruger P89. This weapon was used in the unsolved fatal shooting of a local police officer.</item>
        <item>Beretta M9 9mm pistol, 3 15 round magazines, UM82 holster, pistol belt and dual magazine pouch in a gym bag with two boxes ( 100 rounds ) of 9mm FMJ ammunition. A trace of the pistol\'s serial number indicates it was sold to the New York State National Guard ( 42nd infantry division ).</item>
        <item>A Louisville Slugger baseball bat with several wood screws embedded in the head. It looks well used, judging by the caked blood.</item>
        <item>A brown cardboard box. Neatly hand written on the lid is: "For Aggie." Inside are a Para-Ordance Nite Hawg .45 pistol with three magazines and a Charter Arms Undercover .38 Special revolver with a blued finish and 2-inch barrel. Also present are a fanny pack holster for the Night Hawg, 4 20-round boxes of Hornady .45 ACP 230grn FMJ ammunition, a 20-round box of .45ACP 230grn Hyra-Shok hollowpoints and a20-roud box of .38 Special +P jacketed hollowpoints. The .45 and it\'s accessories were legally purchased by one Nick Levac, a school teacher in a small town in California, and the gun is registered to him. It has never been fired. The .38 was a cash purchase from a Nevada gun store in the mid-1980s.</item>
        <item>Reloading equipment for 12-gauge shotgun shells. Unfortunately there\'s no powder or primers left. Otherwise enough gear to do about 20 shells or so.</item>
        <item>A pair of Walther MPK 9mm submachine guns - 6 spare 32-round magazines.included.</item>
        <item>2 Benchmade folding knives.</item>
        <item>A .38 Colt Detective Special snub nosed revolver. The grip is covered in rubber-bands and it is fully loaded with hand-made dum-dum bullets.</item>
        <item>A single .45 round with the name "ADAM" carved around the bullet.</item>
        <item>An Egyptian Port Said submachine gun chambered in 9X19mm. It is missing a barrel shroud.</item>
        <item>Ka-Bar BK9 Becker Combat Bowie knife with a 9-inch carbon-steel blade, Micarta handles and a custom made leather sheath from Adams Holsters.</item>
        <item>A hand grenade with a post it note stuck to it. The note reads "Don\'t pull the pin idiot!"</item>
        <item>An L-shaped bomb with a pin hanging out of the longest end. The engraving reads "Glock".</item>
        <item>A Bren light machine gun. This particular weapon is of the L4 variety, which was modified after WWII to fire 7.62x51mm rounds. Its condition is singularly miserable: the connection between the stock and receiver has become loose, and most of the rifle is coated in rust (with malfunction stats reflective of this decay, perhaps MALF 70 would be accurate).\nShould serial numbers be run, it comes up as being used by Irish forces during peacekeeping missions during the Congo Crisis of the 1960s. Judging by the amount of corrosion, it can be inferred that the weapon must have stayed there without care for years before Delta Green (somehow) obtained it.</item>
        <item>This footlocker contains six identical blue pasteboard boxes, each containing a new S&amp;W Model 10 revolver in .38 Special. All six are marked with identical serial numbers. If the serial number is investigated, it will be listed as having been purchased by a small rural police department in North Carolina in 1958 and still in inventory there.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box marked with a stylized chinese dragon containing eight handmade 12 gauge Dragonsbreath shotgun shells.</item>
        <item>A coarse brown blanket wrapped around a fully loaded (8 shot) Remington 870 Marine 12 gauge pump-action shotgun with a 18" barrel. There are also six loose 12 gauge rounds wrapped up with the nickel-plated gun.</item>
        <item>A fully-loaded Ingram Mac-10 submachine gun along with three loaded spare magazines. An evidence tag suggest that it was confiscated during a narcotics raid during in 1989 in Miami and was supposedly destroyed the following year. It is in poor condition and will need to be stripped and cleaned before it is used otherwise it will jam on its first use.</item>
        <item>A Daisho pair of Japanese swords. They are modern replicas made of stainless steel, with a factory mark on the blades.</item>
        <item>An X26 Taser</item>
        <item>A typical drawer, removed from whatever piece of furniture held it and filled to the brim with various combat knives, bottles of pepper spray, telescopic batons, and cheap stun guns.</item>
        <item>A garotte made of four feet of wire that has been carefully braided together out of multiple thinner strands to make it much more sturdy. A pair of dry and abused highlighter markers form the handles.</item>
        <item>9x18mm Makarov pistol, Bulgarian make, with three loaded eight round magazines and a black shoe string in a brown paper bag.</item>
        <item>An antique cap-and-ball Colt Navy revolver, in excellent condition. Next to it is a container of black powder, as well as several percussion caps and bullets.</item>
        <item>A faggot of dynamite sticks linked to a single fuse.</item>
        <item>Ruger Speed Six revolver chambered in .38 Special. 2 3/4 inch barrel, blue finish, in it\'s original box.</item>
        <item>A standard 9mm glock 17 with an empty 17 round clip inserted. The top slide has been painted fluorescent pink, and someone has scratched "Dai Lung Motherfucker!" into the metal.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (5 rounds) Smith&amp;Wesson Model 36 .38 revolver with a 2" barrel. The snubnosed gun is quite scratched and there are spots of rust on the frame. It comes with an adjustable shoulder-holster.</item>
        <item>A canvas duffle bag containing:</item>
        <item>a Sphinx AT 2000 9mm pistol + 2 extra clips</item>
        <item>a Daewoo DP-51 9mm pistol + 2 extra clips</item>
        <item>a Astra Model 44 .44 Magnum revolver</item>
        <item>a Milkor BXP 9mm submachine gun + 1 extra magazine</item>
        <item>a Noble Model 50 12-gauge pump-action shotgun.</item>
        <item>4 boxes of 9mm ammunition (200 rounds).</item>
        <item>a box of .44 Magnum ammunition (25 rounds).</item>
        <item>1 box of 12 gauge shotgun shells (20 rounds).</item>
        <item>A Gigli flexible wire saw. This one consists of a loop of tempered steel wires with finger rings on the end. While used for amputations, it can be an effective and easily concealable weapon.</item>
        <item>24 M33 "baseball" grenades.</item>
        <item>3 Yugoslavian Model 57 Tokarev 7.62x25mm caliber semi-automatic pistols with holsters and two 9-round magazines for each. Next to the pistols are four 50-round boxes of 85-grain 7.65 Tokarev FMJ ammuntion, manufactured by Prvi Partisan of Serbia.</item>
        <item>A large, water-cooled Maxim gun bearing Mexican Army markings. It is clearly WWI-era and shows its age in terms of reliability issues.</item>
        <item>A slender walking stick tipped with a silver knob in the form of a stylized eagle\'s head. There are nicks down the sides of the stick as if it has been used to parry something sharp. While the stick itself appears to be made of black wood the core is actually a steel rod.</item>
        <item>A modern-made kukri with a black blade and a hardened plastic grip. It also has a black faux-leather sheath.</item>
        <item>A worn Vietnam-era 5.56mm M16A1 asssault rifle, with 8 rounds remaining in the magazine.</item>
        <item>A 1928 West Hurley Thompson .45 caliber submachine gun in rather good condition, stashed inside a carrying case along with one 50-round drum magazine and five 30-round stick magazines.</item>
        <item>A .50 caliber desert eagle. This version has an elongated barrel and a telescopic sight, making it better suited for target shooting or hunting. An Olive-Drab bandanna is tied to the grip.</item>
        <item>A 9mm Smith &amp; Wesson Sigma SW9F semi-automatic pistol in a plastic gun case, complete with two spare 17-round clips.</item>
        <item>200 rounds (4 boxes) 9mm FMJ ammunition</item>
        <item>A rusty machete, which upon examination appears to be of Mexican origin. With a good cleaning and a little sharpening it could be made serviceable.</item>
        <item>A KRISS Vector.45 ACP submachine gun with an EOTech holo-site, flip up iron sights, folding stock, vertical foregrip and comes with five Glock G-21 13-round magazines that have been converted to 30-round magazines with extensions (this SMG will also accept regular 10- and 13-round G-21 magazines).</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a fully loaded (6 rounds) Ruger GP-161 .357 Magnum revolver and a speedloader with six extra .357 Magnum rounds. There are deep scores along the 6" barrel of the gun, as if it has been used to parry something sharp.</item>
        <item>Two crates containing (12) Diemaco C7A2s and (12) Diemaco C8A1s, respectively.</item>
        <item>An electric cattle prod.</item>
        <item>A telescoping plastic toy lightsaber, complete with red LED lighting and motion sound effects. However, the tip conceals a "bangstick"- a single 12ga shotgun shell rigged to fire on a strong jab.</item>
        <item>Colt .45 ACP</item>
        <item>An F.I.E. Brute twelve-gauge double-barreled shotgun with 19-inch barrels and a short stock. A tag tied to the trigger guard reads: "Fire from hip or waist, don\'t fire near eyes or face."</item>
        <item>Four boxes of Thunderzap ammunition.</item>
        <item>A WWII-era De Lisle carbine. The weapon has been professionally rebuilt and serviced over the years and comes with two spare 10 round magazines and 35 rounds of subsonic .45ACP ammo</item>
        <item>A Mossberg 500 shotgun with the 8-round tube magazine. The shotgun has been modified with a pistol grip and synthetic stock, and shorter barrel. Lying next to the gun is a box of twenty "Dragon\'s Breath" incendiary shotgun shells.</item>
        <item>A small bundle of what appears to be 6 sticks of TNT taped together with a makeshift timing device and detonator attached.</item>
        <item>Inside a foot locker is a SCAR: Sniper Support Rifle equipped with a Trijicon 4x ACOG, a vertical foregrip and a AN/PEQ-2 IR Designator.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a fully loaded (8 rounds) Ruger P345PR .45 pistol and four extra .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>An elegant leather purse containing an empty Glock 19 9mm pistol, three loose 9mm rounds and a pair of brass knuckles (size small).</item>
        <item>An authentic kuhkri knife, with a leather sheath and hardwood handle.</item>
        <item>A two gallon plastic petrol can with an emergency flare duct taped to its side.</item>
        <item>A small leather satchel containing four 12 gauge shotgun slugs and a brass knuckleduster.</item>
        <item>An AKS-74u with a worn-down wooden foregrip and scratch marks all over the metal parts\' finishes. Etched into the left side of the receiver is, in Russian, "THIS MACHINE KILLS TRAITORS". The actual term used is \'suki\', which is a massively derogatory Russian criminal term for police informants which, translated, means \'bitches\', though that translation loses a good part of the stigma.</item>
        <item>A Savage Model 1907 .32 ACP pocket pistol in great working condition, with a pair of double-stack 10-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A box of twenty .357 Magnum rounds.</item>
        <item>A small backpack containing a towel, a small flashligt, an empty bottle of Evian mineral water and a Sig-Sauer P230 .32 pistol. While the gun\'s magazine takes eight rounds only three remains.</item>
        <item>A box of fifty .40S&amp;W rounds.</item>
        <item>A Charter Arms Bulldog .44 Special revolver with a 2.5 inch barrel. It has been magna-ported, the action smoothed and it has been fitted with a hammer shroud. It is loaded with five 135-grain .44 Special Glaser Safety Slugs. Two 6-round boxes of more Glaser Safety Slugs are nearby.</item>
        <item>A Rossi M92 lever-action rifle with a 20" barrel chambered for the .454 Casull round, with a 10 round capacity. Comes in a carrying case along with a box of 20 260-grain .454 Casull semi-jacketed soft-point rounds manufactured by Magtech and a box of 50 rounds of 300-grain jacketed flat-nose rounds manufactured by Buffalo Bore.</item>
        <item>A Sykes-Fairbairn double-edged commando knife with a leather scabbard..</item>
        <item>A British Army L1A1 SLR, which has been damaged by an amateurish attempt to convert it to fully automatic. However, it can be brought back into service with the appropriate rolls.</item>
        <item>A brown paperbag containing a snubnosed (3" barrel) .38 Smith&amp;Wesson Model 10 revolver. It is fully loaded (5 shots).</item>
        <item>An extensively modified .22LR lever-action rifle, with a handmade but well-machined suppressor, a perfectly aligned laser sight, and a shortened barrel. Its stock has been removed past the lever, and in its place a sliding wire stock, like that of the MAT-49 SMG, has been installed. The entire weapon has been painted black, and a small etching on the receiver christens it "The Rat Gun".</item>
        <item>An older 1950\'s era Kalashnikov with Cyrillic letters carved into the stock with the old smooth-sided magazines. The bayonet is a rubber phallus.</item>
        <item>An Ak-47. Inside a shoebox are 2 rounds.</item>
        <item>An ammunition box containing fifty 7.62x39mm rounds. The casings are black soviet steel, marked in Cyrillic.</item>
        <item>One Glock 21 .45 ACP pistol, two 13 round magazines loaded with FMJ ammunition and one Glock plastic belt holster in a clear ziplock freezer bag.</item>
        <item>A large sealed can with cyrillic inscriptions on it. A number sequence reads: "7.62 X 53P".</item>
        <item>Two Heckler and Koch MP5 magazines that have been taped together allowing for easy and swift reload. Each magazine contains 25 rounds of standard clean burn NATO 9mm fully jacketed rounds.</item>
        <item>Two SIG SG550 assault rifles, as used by the Swiss armed forces. A check of their serial numbers indicate they were listed as converted to semi-automatic only and sold to retiring Swiss soldiers; the two problems with that are, of course, that these are capable of fully automatic fire, and are nowhere near Switzerland.</item>
        <item>A plain cardboard box that has a warning label, "Caution! Live Turkeys!". The box has no air holes, and doesn\'t smell of fowl, and also isn\'t large enough to hold more than one turkey.\nIf opened, the box is filled with styrofoam packing peanuts, a fully loaded US Government model FN P90 with reflex sight and sling, and two spare magazines. The 5.7mm ammunition is the Armor Piercing variety only sold to Government or Law Enforcement contracts. If the serial number is checked, it is shown to be in inventory of a Police Department in Texas.</item>
        <item>A two year old local newspaper folded over a small Taurus 25B .25 ACP pistol. The tiny gun is fully loaded (9 rounds).</item>
        <item>A Puma gym bag containing a Rocky Mountain Arms Stakeout 12-gauge cut-down over/under shotgun and a fist full of shells.</item>
        <item>An unfired, pristine condition 1911 Pistol. It has US Army markings from 1940. The slide reads " S. MFG. CO. "</item>
        <item>Buried in a large crate filled with Army surplus blankets are three M16A2 5.56mm assault rifles stored in soft rifle cases, with three 30-round magazines supplied for each.</item>
        <item>An UZI 9mm submachinegun, seven bullets in the magazine.</item>
        <item>A No.4 Mk.1* Lee-Enfield rifle, manufactured by Savage Arms in 1944.\nAttached to it are an inexpensive aftermarket scope mount, scope and nylon sling. Its magazine contains 10 rounds of hand-loaded HPBT match ammunition. Someone has engraved the letters \'C. F.\' on the buttplate.</item>
        <item>A Benchmade 42 Balisong butterfly knife.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a mix of handgun ammunition: twelve 9mm rounds, fourteen .357 Magnum rounds and six .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>One AT4 Light Antitank Weapon.</item>
        <item>A guitar case. Inside is an FN PS90 5.7x28mm carbine with an extended 16-inch barrel, a semi-automatic variant of the FN P90. A Vortex Strikefire red-dot sight is mounted on top and a Streamlight TLR-1 weaponlight attached on top of the barrel. Three fifty-round magazines loaded with 5.7mm FMJ are inside a magazine pouch.</item>
        <item>4 Heckler &amp; Koch MP-5A3 9mm sub-machine guns with five spare loaded magazines each.</item>
        <item>A heavy crowbar caked with dried gore.</item>
        <item>A kitchen knife with knuckles and a trench spike crudely welded to it. It has been sharpened obsessively.</item>
        <item>A small briefcase containing a fully loaded (12 rounds) Heckler&amp;Koch MK23 .45 pistol with an attached suppressor and a laser aiming module. There are also three extra magazines (all loaded), a pair of surgical gloves and a small flashlight in the briefcase.</item>
        <item>A small plastic box with padded lining containing three blasting caps of the electric type.</item>
        <item>A pair of brass knuckles with spikes crudely attached.</item>
        <item>A 14"x10"x4" highly polished rosewood box with the word "Daddy" picked out on the lid in cubic zirconium. Inside is a platinum plated .50AE Desert Eagle with mother-of-pearl grips. The trigger, hammer, safety catch and slide release are gold plated, and the letter \'D\' is inlaid in gold on the grips. The pistol is unloaded but eight, highly polished, rounds of .50 Action Express are included in the box. Incidentally the box is lined with day-glo pink crushed velvet.</item>
        <item>Stoeger Cougar .45 semi-automatic. 3 empty eight-round clips, two unopened boxes of .45 ACP bullets.</item>
        <item>An M-16. This is not the Armalite assault rifle, though; this is an "M-16" described by Che Guevara in his book \'Guerrilla Warfare\'. It is a 16-gauge sawed-off shotgun converted into an improvised mortar by attaching a stand to its muzzle, and its ammunition is in the form of Molotov cocktails whose neck has been sealed with a wooden dowel rod that fits into the shotgun\'s barrel. Upon firing a blank from the shotgun, the force propels the Molotov up to 100 yards away, much like a rifle grenade.</item>
        <item>An Emerson CQB-7 tactical folding knife.</item>
        <item>A loaded C2 Taser Stun Gun.</item>
        <item>A shoebox full of M67 frag grenades. Anyone with military knowledge will recognize that the light blue stripe on them indicates they are inert, for training purposes only. An all-civilian party, however, may not.</item>
        <item>An Kimel AP-9 9mm pistol that comes with 4 spare 20-round magazines.</item>
        <item>An M224 60mm mortar, as issued at the company level by the US Army and Marine Corps.\nOf course, its usefulness is somewhat hampered by the lack of mortar rounds.</item>
        <item>Inside a rifle case is a Knight\'s Armament SR-25 with suppressor, bipod and a rifle scope. There are two 20 round magazines loaded with match grade rounds.</item>
        <item>A 9mm Luger P-08 pistol with three rounds in the clip. A crude three-barred cross has been carved into the handle. A check of the manufacturing number reveals it was made in 1941.</item>
        <item>A rusty Chinese Type 56 Carbine with half the stock ripped out by something with very large teeth.</item>
        <item>An olive-drab Czechoslovakian Army gas suit balled up and crammed into a large messenger bag; at the center of the wad is a busted gas mask and a Micro-Uzi, fully loaded along with a single spare magazine.</item>
        <item>A single 40mm fragmentation grenade for an M79 or M203 hand-held grenade launcher.</item>
        <item>A Heckler &amp; Koch UMP40 .40S&amp;W submachine gun, complete with four spare 30-round box magazines.</item>
        <item>Two 7.62x54R Chinese Type 53 Carbines (clones of the Mosin-Nagant M44 carbine). Each comes with a sling and two boxes of 20 rounds. One is equipped with a spike bayonet which has several nicks and blood stains. This carbine also has a chunk of blood and hair stuck to the butt plate.</item>
        <item>A longslide 1911 with an elaborate laser-sight attached by a special mount to the top. The sight looks like it was surely space-age technology in the 80s, but is now outdated and cumbersome, especially given it\'s palm sized activation switch at the end of a long wire. The sight and gun both work however. One full 8 round magazine is loaded, and 2 more full ones are nearby. The sight has 20 minutes of sustained charge in it\'s battery.</item>
        <item>A beat up old M79 grenade launcher with various marks and carvings etched onto it. The sliding tab used for adjusting for elevation on the sight is missing.</item>
        <item>A plastic carry-case containing a Mossberg 500 Home Security shotgun (chambered for the puny .410 bore cartridge, 1d6+2 damage), a large shotgun silencer (reduces Listen rolls to hear by 25%) and 50 cartridges.</item>
        <item>A locker containing two M-14 battle rifles, chambered in 7.62x51 NATO. The rifles both look considerably worn, and are beginning to develop some rust, but they will still function quite well. A trace of the serial numbers reveals that these guns were part of a shipment of arms that was meant to go to the South Vietnamese army.</item>
        <item>A giant antique single shot punt gun. Loaded.</item>
        <item>A 1-lb Block of Semtex - but no other detonating hardware.</item>
        <item>A DSA-built FN-FAL.</item>
        <item>A scratched plastic case containing a fully loaded, but quite worn, Taurus Model 94 .22 revolver and twelve loose .22 rounds.</item>
        <item>A box of twenty .45 rounds.</item>
        <item>A 500g block of russian Semtex plastic explosive, including a timer-detonator (1-30 minutes).</item>
        <item>A 50-round box of Winchester Ranger .40 155gr (RA40155HP) with 44 rounds left.</item>
        <item>A sawn off shotgun. This is particular type is the infamous Lupara. Has the name "Giovanni Antonelli" inscribed in silver on the stock.</item>
        <item>At first glance this resembles pieces of pipe assembled in such a manner as to suggest a heavy, bulky handgun. A successful ARMORER roll will tell the PC that this is a "Welrod" silenced pistol from the Second World War, and in working order. It is in caliber .32 ACP, with a seven-round detachable box magazine housed in the grip frame. It is a manually-operated bolt-action, requiring the user to manually operate a handle to extract and eject the fired casing, load a fresh cartridge, and cock the mechanism. It is large, heavy, bulky, and difficult to conceal, but very quiet indeed when fired. No ammunition nor spare magazines are present.</item>
        <item>A long, matte-black case. Inside is a lovingly maintained .55 caliber Mk. II Boys Anti-Tank Rifle from WWII. The weapon has a fully loaded (5 shot) magazine. It has sufficient force to penetrate the armor of light WW2 tanks, but lacks the power to penetrate modern armored vehicles.</item>
        <item>One large gasoline powered chainsaw with a very long blade. Someone appears to have modified the engine for increased power output as two large exhaust pipes exit the motor to the rear.</item>
        <item>Dagger, Double edged 12" long, low steel</item>
        <item>A replica produced STG-44 assault rifle. While it looks close to the original, this is a recently produced model for civilian use. It chambers .22 LR ammunition, and can only fire semi-automatic. It has two magazines and a box of 100 .22 LR rounds.</item>
        <item>One Sig Sauer "Mosquito" .22 caliber pistol. Comes with three extra ten-round magazines. Jams often.</item>
        <item>An IMI Mini-Uzi with six 32 round magazines of 9x19mm rounds. The barrel has a silencer threaded onto it, and another silencer next to it. The ammunition is somewhat unusual: the slugs are copper jacketed with nickel-iron-manganese alloy cores.</item>
        <item>A leather shoulder-holster containing a fully loaded (7 rounds) Taurus Model 627 Tracker .357 Magnum revolver with a 4" barrel. The titanium frame has small pits in it as if something horribly acidic has spattered it.</item>
        <item>A crate containing a WW2 era MG34 general-purpose machine gun that requires some cleaning. It has a bipod and two barrels included with it. Along with two 250 round belts of 7.92x57mm Mauser.</item>
        <item>A well-worn but maintained Mosin-Nagant M91/30 rifle, with fixed bayonet and classic green canvas sling, along with one hundred rounds of ammunition in stripper clips. The right side of the stock bears a painstakingly etched carving of a scorpion, its stinger raised and ready to strike.</item>
        <item>A small case holding two FN Five-SeveN 5.7mm pistols. The first pistol is a civilian version for restricted markets, which only holds 10 rounds and uses normal 5.7mm ammunition. The serial number shows that it was owned by a Gun Store near or in the town where the Green Box is located that closed down six months ago, and the owner moved away.\nThe second pistol has a 20-round magazine, attached suppressor and LAM, and is loaded with the Armor Piercing ammunition only sold to military or law enforcement. It shows no sign of a serial number.</item>
        <item>A soft carrying case holds a Savage Model 111 bolt-action rifle chambered in 7mm Remington Magnum, mounted with a Simmons 3-9x40 scope. Four pre-loaded detachable 3-round box magazines are also stashed in the case.</item>
        <item>A sack of badly cast iron spikes bent into 4-pointed caltrops.</item>
        <item>Bryco-Jennings Junior .22 LR single shot rifle, blued finish, synthetic stock, equipped with a Simmons 4X scope.</item>
        <item>A heavily customised Browning Hi-Power Mk. III 9mm pistol, with a Commander-style hammer, extended ambidextrous safety, extended slide release, and wide combat trigger installed by Cylinder &amp; Slide, Inc. of Fremont, NE. The magazine disconnect has been removed, the trigger pull lightened to five pounds, and a set of Novak combat night sights installed. The pistol has also been given a graphite black Cerakote finish and a permanent Slipstream lubrication treatment by Crusader Weaponry of Murray UT, and a set of gray G10 pistol grips from MilTac. It is contained in a brushed-aluminum case along with four loaded 15-round high capacity flush fit magazines from Mec-Gar of Italy, a cordura quad mag pouch for carrying the magazines and three different holsters: shoulder, hip and inside-the-waistband. There\'s also two fifty-round boxes of 9mm Winchester Ranger 127-grain +P+ hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A traditional forged katana that dealers 2d10 damage and can attack 1/2 per turn.</item>
        <item>A screwdriver with the head sharpened to a fine point.</item>
        <item>A Remington Model 1100 LT-20 20-gauge semi-auto shotgun in a carrying case along with 30 rounds of deer slugs</item>
        <item>Some scattered gunsmithing tools surrounding six Tec-9 pistols; closer examination indicates an amateur attempted to convert them from semi-automatic to fully automatic. Five of the six have been ruined beyond repair, but the sixth was close enough that a single Armorer, Gunsmith, or halved Mechanical Repair skill roll can finish it out into a working (though questionably reliable) machine pistol</item>
        <item>One 9x18mm Makarov pistol, 2 loaded 8 round magazines and a cleaning rod all contained in a well worn brown leather flap holster.</item>
        <item>A 20-round box of Winchester 10mm 175gr Silvertips, containing 15 Silvertips and 3 of what appear to be 180gr Double Tap jacketed hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A SPAS-12 shotgun, there bag of 12 gauge shells laying next to it. How many is up to the GM.</item>
        <item>2 Beretta 90-Two 9mm pistols with Gemtech Trinity suppressors and 6 15-round magazines.</item>
        <item>Three "Bucket o\' Bullets" full to the brim with .22 Long Rifle rounds. A fourth bucket is half-full of 22 LR #12 shot cartridges (so-called "rat-shot")</item>
        <item>A brown paper bag containing an oil-stained rag wrapped around a worn Ruger P90 .45 pistol. Four rounds remain out of the gun\'s full eight shot capacity.</item>
        <item>A Marlin 70 .22 rifle with one round in the chamber</item>
        <item>A surgical scalpel, its handle covered in rubber bands.</item>
        <item>A vintage M1918A2 Browning Automatic Rifle (fitted with a bipod), in rather excellent condition. Also included are 10 boxes of 20 rounds of Hornady .30-06 Springfield ammunition.</item>
        <item>One nylon gym bag containing a Beretta M9 pistol with barrel fitted for a quick detachable silencer, one silencer, five 15 round magazines loaded with subsonic 9mm ammunition and a cheap, black, nylon shoulder holster. The pistol is stamped US GOVERNMENT PROPERTY. Silencer is wet type: liquid must be poured through the silencer to ensure effective use.</item>
        <item>Rolled in a carpet is a USMC-issue 83.5mm Shoulder-Launched Multipurpose Assault Weapon (SMAW) with three rockets. Deafeningly loud, it can collapse a building or destroy a tank in one shot. This one was "liberated" with five rockets from Fort Lauderdale, Fl. by a disgruntled US Marine in 1998 and subsequently sold on the black market.</item>
        <item>A Savage 775A 12-gauge semi-automatic shotgun; the aluminum-alloy receiver is engraved with three ducks in flight on the left side and a pair of pheasants on the right side.</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing an old BLU-43/B "Dragontooth" air-droppable land mine, as used in large numbers by the US in Vietnam. This tiny (3" long) mine was intended to maim rather than kill and is quite unstable by now. Any Agent moving it may well join the many Vietnamese soldiers and peasants needing a replacement limb.</item>
        <item>A diver\'s harpoon rifle with one barbed steel harpoon.</item>
        <item>Three stainless steel throwing knives</item>
        <item>A 9mm ITM AT-84 pistol with an extra magazine.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (five rounds) Ruger M77 .308 Win. precision rifle with bipod and a scope attached.</item>
        <item>A stack of DVDs, the edges of which have been filed down to a razor edge.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .38 Taurus 731 snub-nosed revolver, in a leather ankle-holster.</item>
        <item>One Ruger GP-100 .357 magnum revolver, loaded with 6 rounds SJWC ammunition in a nylon shoulder holster. A pouch on the holster contains a speedloader loaded with 6 rounds SJWC.</item>
        <item>A vintage German anti-tank magnetic mine, of the type used in the opening years of WWII before man portable rockets were invented. Its use would have required the near-suicidal act of running up to a tank and slapping it onto the armor, though it would have practically guaranteed a kill.\nIt is still definitely a powerful shaped charge, but its age may cause it to malfunction at the Keeper\'s discretion.</item>
        <item>A Dan Wesson .41 Magnum revolver with a 6 inch vent rib heavy barrel and a barrel-mounted scope mount with a removable Millett 2X20 scope. Someone has thoughtfully included a 50-round box of 210-grain .41 Magnum jacketed hollowpoints manufactured by Bitteroot Valley Ammunition.</item>
        <item>Three atlatls (spear throwers) made of bone and bundled together by a rubber band. They each have catalog markings from Chicago\'s Field Museum of Natural History; they were part of a large collection of Native American artifacts that went missing from a storeroom in 1981.</item>
        <item>Three switchblade knives sitting on a shelf. One has had the spring removed, so the blade is fixed open.</item>
        <item>A full 20-round box of Cor-Bon 10mm 200gr FMJ "Penetrators".</item>
        <item>Half a dozen lead-filled custom-made leather saps, ranging in length from 6.5 inches to 14 inches and in weight from 8oz. to 16oz.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing seven non-lethal "Bean Bag" rounds for a 12 gauge shotgun.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded Star Model 30 9mm pistol. The gun is quite worn and the risk of malfunction is increased by 2%,</item>
        <item>A Micro-UZI 9mm submachinegun, with eight rounds in the magazine.</item>
        <item>A Charter Arms Off Duty .38 Special revolver in a plastic bag. This gun was the murder weapon in the case of a slain local college student a few years ago. The case is still open.</item>
        <item>A needle-sharp ice-pick, its tip covered with a piece of cork. The wooden handle is worn smooth from long use.</item>
        <item>A small single-gun safe. Inside is an STI Duty CT 1911 .45-caliber pistol with a 4.15 inch slide and an extended, threaded barrel, and a pancake holoster. A small pouch contains an Advanced Armaments Evolution suppressor. Three spare magazines loaded up with TTI 250-grain hollowpoints are included in another belt pouch.</item>
        <item>One red and three green flares for a flare gun.</item>
        <item>A black plastic box containing a fully loaded (14 rounds) Smith&amp;Wesson Model 459 9mm pistol and two (empty) extra magazines.</item>
        <item>A small workbench has a complex hand-cranked tool bolted to its top. A successful ARMORER roll reveals that it is a reloading press, for reusing fired centerfire cartridge cases to load ammunition, along with appropriate dies, etc., for several popular handgun and rifle, but not shotgun, calibers, and several yellowed, dog-eared manuals of loading data, full of brief scribbled notes and highlighted portions. Also present are cartons of primers and canisters of various types of smokeless powder suitable for reloading a wide range of handgun, shotgun, or rifle cartridges. No cases or bullets are present, though.</item>
        <item>Three plastic cases, each containing a Springfield xD9 in good condition, three 12 round magazines, a suppressor with no markings, and 36 rounds of subsonic FMJ 9mm ammunition. A large sheet of green printer paper taped to the top case reads "For use in populated areas. Ammo pre-treated to defeat NIBIN/IBIS ID".</item>
        <item>A foldable straight razor.</item>
        <item>A Mark III SMLE which has been sawed off down to the magazine, something common in WWI trench warfare. The rifle is empty, but a box of 20 .303 rounds is found nearby</item>
        <item>A box containing ten 308 Win. rounds.</item>
        <item>4 Glock 21 .45 ACP self-load pistols (no serial numbers there at all) with 5 13-round magazines for these.</item>
        <item>An Indonesian Parang machete with a razor-sharp 1.2 foot blade. The handle is made from reddish wood and carved into the shape of a leaping tiger. There is also a wooden scabbard made from the same wood. Down the side of the scabbard is written in Bahasa Indonesia : "Travel Light. Strike Hard.".</item>
        <item>In a weapons case is a Heckler &amp; Koch HK416: D10RS. It is fitted with an ACOG scope, a fore grip, and a spring loaded back up iron sight. There are no magazines or ammo; the players will need to find some.</item>
        <item>A Calico M960A 9mm submachine gun stashed inside a canvas sack along with four 50-round helical magazines.</item>
        <item>A set of four M3 carbines, of 1960\'s vintage. Ten thirty round magazines are included, along with the original (very dated) infrared night vision scopes and mounting equipment. They are also integrally suppressed (also dated). Other, more modern infrared scopes could also be used with them.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (10 rounds) Glock 26 "subcompact" 9mm pistol, with a rubber ankle-holster.</item>
        <item>An imitation broadsword.</item>
        <item>This narrow seven-foot-long crate contains a massively heavy "antimateriel rifle" of the sort wealthy enthusiasts or lavishly equipped armies might purchase in .50 BMG, but this one is bigger yet. It is a single-shot bolt-action in 14.5mm Soviet, weighing over 20kg and longer than a man is tall. No serial number or other markings are present on it, though it is obviously used, and lovingly maintained. It has been equipped with a very expensive European target scope, for which Keepers may award appropriate modifiers. No ammunition for it is present, however, and Wal-Mart doesn\'t stock this caliber.</item>
        <item>Contained in a drag bag is a Mauser SP66 precision sniper rifle. The weapon has been rechambered from the original 7.62 x 51mm NATO caliber cartridge to .300 Winchester Magnum and is fitted with a Bausch &amp; Lomb 6-24 power variable magnification telescopic sight.</item>
        <item>An opened paper box containing thirty-two 10mm rounds.</item>
        <item>A green gym bag containing:\n- A Charter Arms Mag Pug .357 Magnum revolver.\n- A compact Bersa BP9CC 9mm pistol with two spare magazines\n- A Bulgarian-made Arcus 98 9mm pistol with two spare magazines\n- A sawed off 20-gauge over/under shotgun\n- A FAMAE Mini-SAF 9mm compact submachine gun with two spare magazines\n- 4 50-round boxes of 9mm FMJ\n- 1 25-round box of Rio Royal 20-gauge 00 buckshot shells\n- 1 50-round box of 125-grain .357 Magnum hollowpoints\n- four white plastic full-face masks with eye and mouth holes;</item>
        <item>400 rounds of 9mm 158 grain FMJ subsonic ammunition, manufactured by Fiocchi.</item>
        <item>A modern hunting crossbow made by Barnett International. There are eight bolts with the weapon, so ammo shouldn\'t be an immediate concern.</item>
        <item>Hidden among a box of Christmas lights is a pair of Makarov PB with integral suppressors. Each weapon is loaded but there are no extra magazines.</item>
        <item>A collection of exotic 40mm grenade rounds, such ass canister-shot and flechette, tear gas, parachute-flare, and a singular mysterious round bearing only sizable yellow biohazard symbols on its casing. Keeper\'s discretion as to what it actually contains.</item>
        <item>A small folding case about the size of a deck of cards made out of cheap nylon fabric and velcro. Opening the packet reveals five steel playing cards with hand-sharpened edges, ostensibly for throwing (20% penalty to attempts to actually use them because they\'re not practical weapons). Together, the cards make up a full house in poker.</item>
        <item>A Kimber TLE-2, stainless steel, .45 ACP pistol with three loaded, 8-round Wilson Combat magazines (also stainless steel). The pistol is heavily engraved with floral designs and images with a Western motif (steer skulls, cacti, etc.). It has ivory (or faux ivory) grips laser engraved with the image of a star in a circle, similar to a Texas Ranger badge. The pistol is accompanied by a brown leather gunbelt with an attached holster and double magazine pouch. The belt, holster and magazine pouch are heavily carved with a floral pattern that matches the pattern on the pistol. "E. Calvera - Maker" is stamped on the inside lining of the gunbelt.</item>
        <item>12-gauge Browning BPS pump-action shotgun with a 28-inch barrel.</item>
        <item>A 16-gauge Fox/Sterlingworth double-barrelled shotgun in a carrying case along with three 10-round boxes of HEVI-Shot No.4 16-gauge shells.</item>
        <item>A Norinco Type 85 with integral suppressor and 10 loaded magazines.</item>
        <item>A Fireman\'s axe. Spray-painted black.</item>
        <item>A zippered carry case containing a modern replica of a bolt-action Springfield 1903-A4 .30-06 sniper rifle, manufactured by Gibbs Rifle Company complete with an authentic replica M84 2.2x riflescope and mounts and replica M1907 leather sling.</item>
        <item>A tied-up handkerchief containing eight 9mm rounds, three .45 rounds and a single .44 Magnum round.</item>
        <item>Glock 37 .45 GAP pistol with attached 150 lumen tactical LED light, three loaded 10 round magazines (FMJ ammo), a thigh holster in a black gym bag.</item>
        <item>A rusty Remington Rand M1911A1 .45 automatic pistol with a fully loaded clip. Works, but with a doubled chance of a misfire.</item>
        <item>A three foot long shovel with an ash wood handle and steel fittings and blade. The blade is sharpened to a fine edge and is stained with dried blood. An analysis of the blood shows that it does not match that of any known creature.</item>
        <item>A loaded sawed-off double-barrelled 12 gauge shotgun.</item>
        <item>A brand new SRM Arms M1216 12-gauge semi-automatic shotgun, with two 16 round rotary quad-tube detachable magazines, which can be loaded with either 2 3/4- or 3-inch shells. The amidextrous receiver and controls can be set up for either right or left handed shooters. It also has Picatinny rails for mounting optics and accessories.</item>
        <item>An M1 Garand rifle. Carved into the stock is a swastika and twenty tally marks.</item>
        <item>A well-worn Glock 17 9mm pistol in a plastic shoulder-holster. The gun is fully loaded and in a pouch on the shoulder-rig two additional (loaded) magazines can be found.</item>
        <item>An antique Martini-Henry rifle, chambered in the .577/450 black powder cartridge. A few dozen such cartridges sit next to it in a moth-eaten burlap bag labelled " Property of the Belgian Ministry of Colonies" in French.\nThe weapon is in fairly decent shape for a weapon of its age, and could probably fetch a few thousand dollars at auction.</item>
        <item>A sledgehammer, covered with dust. Unknown, dried green liquid on the edge.</item>
        <item>A plastic trash can with rags on top. Under the rags are seven Makarov PM pistols. There are magazines present for the weapons but there are only 20 rounds present.</item>
        <item>Three well used Republiek van Suid-Afrika Vektor SS-77 machine guns with bipods and six belts of (200) 7.62x51mm NATO rounds each.</item>
        <item>This heavy olive-drab steel ammo can is about three quarters full of loose .22 LR cartridges--it contains three or four thousand rounds at least. Oddly, the cases have no headstamps, and anyone with the ARMORER skill will notice they\'re a little odd looking. When examined closely by someone with the ARMORER skill, it is revealed that the ammunition is loaded with full metal jacket bullets rather than the normal pure soft lead bullets, rather unusual for commercially made .22 LR. An ARMORER skill roll will suggest that it was probably made this way for some military black-ops unit for use in suppressed weapons in combat, to comply with the Hague Convention laws of war. For game purposes there is no difference between this ammunition and any other, except that the lack of a manufacturer\'s code or logo on the headstamp will make it rather more difficult for anyone finding the casings to trace where they came from, which is why they are unmarked.</item>
        <item>2 Remington 870 12 gauge pump shotguns with 20" rifled deer slug barrels.</item>
        <item>A munitions crate containing a dozen heavily used STEN Mk V 9mm submachineguns, along with three 32-round magazines for each. A relevant roll will determine the set as being of Israeli provenance.\nAn Armorer roll will reveal that the weapons are all in terrible condition. All of the guns will fail to fire for a variety of reasons if used, and most of the magazines\' springs have rusted into immobility. The guns can be used for parts to cobble together perhaps 2 or 3 functioning weapons.\nAs a side note, STEN guns have a reputation for accidental discharge, which age would do no favors for. These weapons can, at the Keeper\'s discretion, go off when jostled, dropped, or if it would generally be incredibly inconvenient for the players - additional fun potential in deciding what the unintended fire hits!</item>
        <item>An ex-Argentine Navy Mathogo ATGM launcher with a single rocket. The rocket is in poor condition, and it is the Keeper\'s discretion whether it works at all.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (twenty rounds) czech Skorpion Vz. 61 E .32 submachinegun, with a plastic shoulder holster. On the opposite side of the holster harness hangs another loaded twenty round magazine.</item>
        <item>A Carl Gustav M/45 9mm submachine gun. It is quite worn and has a small ivory Buddha statuette hanging from the barrel by a leather thong. One full 30-round magazine is inserted in the gun.</item>
        <item>4 unopened boxes (25 rounds each) of Hornady "Zombie Max" 115-grain 9mm ammuntion and 2 unopened boxes (25 rounds each) of Hornady "Zombie Max" 165-grain .40 S&amp;W ammunition.</item>
        <item>A 1891 Mosin-Nagant bolt-action rifle. It has not been cleaned for upwards of 50 years and is covered in cosmoline.</item>
        <item>A heavy butcher\'s cleaver. The blade is pitted with rust and stains.</item>
        <item>A silenced .22 Browning Buckmark target pistol with a full 10 shot magazine inserted.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .38 Smith&amp;Wesson Model 36 snub-nosed revolver, with a leather belt holster.</item>
        <item>A German MP40 submachinegun from World War II, with six spare magazines. It appears almost new.</item>
        <item>10 1 lb. cans of black powder.</item>
        <item>A Ruger 10/22 rifle with a crude homemade suppressor, consisting of an automotive oil filter soldered onto the barrel. To compensate for the added length, the stock has been sawed off and replaced with a cheap sliding-wire design, as seen on sub-machine guns like the MAT-49.</item>
        <item>A small metal carrying case, which inside contains a .308 Upper for an AR-15 or similar model weapon, and the tools required to install it.</item>
        <item>A single Soviet F1 hand grenade.</item>
        <item>A one-shot M72 LAW disposable light anti-armour weapon. It has been armed but not fired.</item>
        <item>A small vial of pure nicotine.</item>
        <item>Must be combined with a stabilizer when exposed directly to the elements.</item>
        <item>A white manilla envelope from AARP, ostensibly about someone\'s retirement plan. Rattling around inside the envelope are five 9mm bullets (unfired).</item>
        <item>A russian PKP Pecheneg 7.62mm light machine gun, complete with a loading belt containing 40 rounds.</item>
        <item>Smoke Grenades\nAlong with mini-flares, these can be used to mark out a landing zone, as well as provide concealment for an escape or disruption for an assault.</item>
        <item>Three .40 S&amp;W caliber Glock 23 pistols. The serial numbers have removed. The pistols sit beside a box of .40 caliber S&amp;W ammunition.</item>
        <item>A well worn copy of the King James Bible, there\'s a silver Celtic cross on a steel chain wrapped around it. The bible has been hollowed out and now holds a S&amp;W 627 revolver loaded with 357 magnum hollow points.</item>
        <item>An aluminum Zero Halliburton briefcase. Nestled inside are a pair of Dan Wesson RZ-10 ten-millimeter semi-automatic pistols and in between them rests a customized Glock 19 converted to .22LR with a threaded barrel. Gemtech silencer and a box of subsonic ammunition. There are extra magazines and concealment holsters for each weapon.</item>
        <item>A 16-gauge double-barreled shotgun of Turkish manufacture and six rounds loaded with flechette darts.</item>
        <item>1 Claridge Hi-Tec S9 9mm semi-automatic pistol; two 20-round magazines and three modified Beretta 92 15-round magazines (which the pistol will take) are included.</item>
        <item>A CZ 712 Utility 12-gauge semi-automatic shotgun placed inside a shotgun carrying case along with a box containing ten No. 4 buckshot shells.</item>
        <item>An LAPD evidence bag containing an IMI Uzi mini with an empty 20 round magazine loaded.</item>
        <item>A painstakingly-recreated example of John Kelly\'s handgun from Tom Clancy\'s "Without Remorse". It is a Government model M1911A1, which has had its internals swapped to fire .22LR using a commercial conversion kit. Attached to the barrel is a homemade but still effective suppressor, and over its ejection port a handmade brass catcher has been installed to collect the spent cartridges.</item>
        <item>A very worn, but well maintained M3 "Grease Gun" SMG in .45 caliber, with a silencer and about a dozen spare 30-round magazines. All serial numbers have been removed. A partial box of .45 ammo is present, enough to load a single mag with two or three cartridges left over.</item>
        <item>An ugly, crude-looking submachinegun that appears to be made of steel tubing and sheet metal, with several spare magazines. An ARMORER roll will identify it correctly as a World War II-era "Sten Gun," designed in the UK for simplicity of manufacture. Weapons like this one were once made by the thousands in clandestine workshops in occupied Europe. And this one looks rather new, come to think of it... which might explain the files and chisels in the toolbox with it. The gun has a threaded muzzle and the box also contains an equally crudely made silencer that fits the threads, and a few boxes of subsonic 9mm ammo. Note that this is an open-bolt, straight-blowback SMG and though the silencer is effective at slowing the release of propellant gases and muffling the sounds of individual gunshots, the normal operation of the gun will still make a very loud mechanical clattering sound when fired with the silencer attached.</item>
        <item>A trunk with three AK-103\'s, 45 magazines and four 200 round ammunition boxes.</item>
        <item>A Vietnam-era M79 40mm grenade launcher. It is not loaded.</item>
        <item>A FR Ordnance MC51 carbine with retractable stock. It is fitted with a Surefire flashlight (fully charged) and a red dot sight (fully operational). Three empty twenty-round magazines are with the weapon. A cleaning kit and a bandolier containing fifty 7.62mm NATO armour-piercing rounds are also present.</item>
        <item>Three FN SCAR-L 5.56x45mm with subcarbine configuration. They were fabricated without serial numbers and have never been fired. There are two extra clips for each weapon, in addition to 200 rounds floating in a cut-off plastic carboy. A gun cleaning kit sits next to the extra ammo.</item>
        <item>A 1911A1 pistol with 10 magazines loaded with a mix of 230 grain hardball and 200 grain hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>Old military rifle. Bolt action rifle chambered in 7.62x54mmR. Magazine holds 5 rounds, and is loaded. 2 spare, loaded stripper clips lie next to it. The gun is well worn and smells slightly of cosmoline.</item>
        <item>A KelTec PLR16 5.56mm semi-auto pistol, equipped with a short folding stock, Battlecomp muzzle brake to reduce muzzle climb, a Midwest Industries forend, a Magpul AFG (angled foregrip) a Primary Arms micro green dot reflex sight, and a Viridian X5L green laser sight/taclight combo. Comes with three loaded 30-round lightweight polymer Magpul PMAG magazines.</item>
        <item>A 12 gauge Escort MarineGuard pump-action shotgun with 5-shot magazine capacity, an 18-inch barrel and nickel finish, inside a soft shotgun case.</item>
        <item>Six shells which could be classified as either gigantic bullets or tiny artillery shells by a layman; someone with a military background will recognize them as 25mm rounds from a naval autocannon. The yellow-painted tips indicate them to be MK210 High Explosive Incendiary Tracers.</item>
        <item>A heavy machete with soot blackened blade and a well-worn wooden grip. There are three notches carved into the grip.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Mini-14.</item>
        <item>A rusted trench knife, stamped \'U.S 1918". The name \'Laura\' is scratched into the opposite side of the handle.</item>
        <item>A Taurus PT-92 9mm pistol with a matte-black finish, stuck inside an ambidextrous Bianchi belt-holster. Comes with three spare 15-round clips.</item>
        <item>Astra Constable .32 ACP caliber pistol, in it\'s original box, with a 7-round clip.</item>
        <item>An unremarkable black plastic comb, labelled only as "made in China". When the handle is pulled from the teeth, about a foot of garrote wire unspools from inside, connected to both sides for use as handles.</item>
        <item>Smith &amp; Wesson Model 1076 10 mm Auto (10x25 mm) semi-automatic pistol with two 9-round, two 11-round, one and 15-round clips plus 50 hollow point rounds. Slide marked with "Caution - Capable of Firing With Magazine Removed". Two punched dots under the de-cocker lever.</item>
        <item>An opened box of .45 ammunition. Twelve rounds remain.</item>
        <item>One M1 carbine with three 15 round magazines, WWII era.</item>
        <item>A Serbu Super Shorty 12-gauge custom compact. stockless short shotgun with a spring-loaded folding forestock, built from a Mossberg Maverick 88. There is also a black nylon ambidextrous thigh holster for the shotgun, with a partial break-front which holds the forward grip folded and loops on the outside that can hold three extra shells.</item>
        <item>A metal footlocker, containing several boxes of .40 S&amp;W ammo, totaling to about 1000 rounds.\nA Post-it note, in a woman\'s handwriting, is stuck to the inside lid of the footlocker. It reads:\nPlease keep restocked if able. We go through a lot of these around here.\n-- SANDRA</item>
        <item>A coffee can filled with assorted pistol rounds. It is mostly made up of 9mm rounds but intermixed are .45 caliber, .357 magnum and .38 special rounds.</item>
        <item>A sniper drag bag. Inside is a McMillan M88 PIP .50 BMG bolt-action sniper rifle with a 4-16x Horus Falcon steel tactical scope mounted on it. The five-round magazine is empty, but a plastic ammo box holding ten rounds of 619-grain M20 APIT (Armor Piercing Incendiary/Tracer) is taped to the buttstock and another is inside one of the bag\'s side pouches.</item>
        <item>A Guard Dog Security Cell Phone Stun Gun, a 2,700,000 volt stun gun made up to look like an innocent cell phone.</item>
        <item>An original production run M1921 Thompson SMG in a canvas bag, with a sling, and two drum magazines, one loaded one empty. The weapon is well maintained, except for three tally marks carved into the stock.</item>
        <item>A .357 revolver with three rounds left in the cylinder. This weapon was involved in a police shooting in Texas, so obviously having your finger prints on this gun would be a very bad idea. It can be used to frame someone as the suspect in question was never caught or identified.</item>
        <item>This soft cloth gun case contains a Winchester Model 1894 lever-action hunting rifle in .30-30 caliber, clean and well maintained, with target-type peep sights but no scope. There is also a leather bandoleer with loops to hold up to forty cartridges, but only fourteen are present. They are loaded with soft-nose hunting bullets.</item>
        <item>A folding knife with a serrated 4-inch blade - it is a cheap knockoff of a Spyderco Civilian.</item>
        <item>An M4A1 carbine with eight rounds remaining in the magazine. No extra ammunition or clips. The serial number is still persent and if traced will show it was reported as missing from Vandenberg Air Force Base.</item>
        <item>A Mossberg 500 shotgun, with a worn leather bandolier containing 15-20 shells.</item>
        <item>An unloaded Russian RPG-7 rocket propelled grenade launcher.</item>
        <item>A Smith &amp; Wesson 276 Gas Gun with six 37mm tear gas grenades.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .357 Magnum Taurus Model 65 revolver with 4" barrel. The gun is quite worn and the serial numbers have been filed off.</item>
        <item>A case for an electric key board inside is a Barrett .50 caliber sniper rifle and a homemade suppressor. The suppressor is nearly as long as the rifle making it an unwieldy setup. There is no ammo present.</item>
        <item>A one-shot veterinarian\'s tranquilizer pistol and four tranquilizer darts. The darts are strong enough to put a large animal like a bear or lion to sleep in a minute or two, and are quite likely to be lethal for an old or weak human.</item>
        <item>An empty 9mm Glock 17 pistol with an attached post-it note saying "Emergency use only! Ballistics will match Arizona cop-killing!".</item>
        <item>A shoebox containing a Glock 26 subcompact Pistol and a spare magazine.</item>
        <item>A wood carrying case. Inside are a Smith &amp; Wesson M76 9mm submachine gun and a pair of Browning Hi-Power 9mm semi-automatics, set into recesses. There\'s also a pair of extra magazines for each pistol, a plastic ammo box containing 100 rounds of 9mm hollowpoints and, set into recesses in the interior of the lid of the case are 9 pairs of magazines for the M76, taped together "jungle style".</item>
        <item>A Taser X3 with five cartridges. The X3 cartridge holds 3 shots before it must be exchanged for a fresh one.</item>
        <item>A box with a dozen M18 smoke grenades. There are about four that produce red smoke and eight that produce green.</item>
        <item>Intratec TEC-38 polymer-framed two-shot derringer chambered in .38 Special</item>
        <item>A paperbag containing a fully loaded CZ75 9mm pistol and two extra magazines (both loaded).</item>
        <item>A Bohemian earspoon, a polearm with a forward-facing spear-like spike and two outward facing spikes. It\'s not an original medieval artifact but a replica that appears to have been produced by White Rose Armoury of England.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Super Redhawk in a black leather case; it is chambered for the high-powered .454 Casull round, and a box of 12 sits next to it. A box of .45 Long Colt, which can be fired from guns chambered for the .454, has also been included for less enthusiastic shooters.</item>
        <item>M-4 carbine with 5 magazines.</item>
        <item>A battered and slightly rusty 7.62x39mm AK47 rifle with a side-folding stock. Close examination reveals that it is very crudely made and finished, with sloppy machine work, and ugly bluish-green plastic tape wrapped around the pistol grip and handguards; an ARMORER skill roll reveals it is a "Khyber Pass" copy made out of scrap metal by Pathan gunsmiths in Pakistan. It is in good working order and safe to fire. There are also about a dozen rusty steel 30-round magazines with it, but no ammunition is present.</item>
        <item>A Chinese Type 56 assault rifle, loaded with twenty-four rounds of 7.62X29mm soft point bullets and caked with dry blood.</item>
        <item>Rifle case containing a Ruger AC-556K 5.56mm select-fire automatic rifle with a pistol grip and folding stock. Four 30-round detachable box magazines and two 20-round box-magazines are in the case.</item>
        <item>A small plastic box containing five .38 rounds.</item>
        <item>A Rossi Model 851 6-shot .38 Special revolver with a 4-inch barrel.</item>
        <item>A bundle of 14 SKS 7.62mm rifles, in various states of condition and age wrapped with duct tape and all with erased serial numbers. About half of them are loaded, some are even chambered. The weapons have a envelope attached to a barrel by a string. The envelope says, "Clean and cheap guns, use one, drop, replace."</item>
        <item>A bloodstained handkerchief wrapped around a fully loaded (6 shot) Glock 36 .45 pistol with a 3.78" barrel. There is also a spare (loaded) magazine alongside the small gun.</item>
        <item>A British Army armament crate with a sturdy padlock, containing one mothballed and obsolete Blowpipe anti-aircraft missile launcher and two missiles. A note attached insists the users \'not waste\' the missiles, complaining of how difficult it was to get through customs.</item>
        <item>A cabinet filled with a collection of twenty or so pocket-knives, ranging from brand new to several decades old.</item>
        <item>A shoe box containing an Ingram MAC 10 machine pistol with 3 full 30 round magazines of .45 ACP. Two of the magazines are taped together "Jungle Style" for ease of reloading.</item>
        <item>A police issue 21" telescopic baton (8" long when collapsed).</item>
        <item>A cardboard box containing three 9mm Walther P38\'s as well as twenty-four 8 round magazines.</item>
        <item>A .45 Ingram MAC-10 submachine gun with a screwed on suppressor. It is quite worn and have deep scratches along the handle. The clip contains 12 rounds.</item>
        <item>A Norwegian made Heckler &amp; Koch G3A1 rifle, with "Kongsberg, 7,62N, No83838" stamped into the metal. It has black electricians tape wound around the pistol grip, and a yellow plastic tag bearing the inscription: "Slethei" tied to the foregrip. One fully loaded 20 round clip is inserted.(If traced, this rifle is one of 15 stolen from Terningmoen camp in Norway in 1997.)</item>
        <item>This carton contains six small black plastic cases, each containing a Glock 22 .40 caliber pistol and three fifteen-round magazines. The serial numbers have been removed. There are also several boxes of .40 caliber hollowpoint ammunition and one partial box of armor piercing ammunition.</item>
        <item>A beautiful hand-made atlatl. It would look perfectly at home on the wall of an anthropology professor\'s office but the fire-hardened point of the spear and razor-sharp blades set along the tip speak to someone serious about getting the job done.</item>
        <item>One Springfield XD-40 pistol with 2 loaded magazines.</item>
        <item>A hunting knife with a twelve-inch blade, a large brass cross guard and wooden grips. The blade is slightly rusted and heavily pitted by what appears to be acid.</item>
        <item>A Finnish-made Tikkakoski M31 Suomi 9mm caliber carbine, comes with one 36 round stick magazine, two 71 round drums and s soft carrying case.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Redhawk .44 Magnum revolver, with 5.5" barrel. There are two fired and four unfired rounds in the drum.</item>
        <item>A 3D printed, Liberator-style, plastic pistol. Chambered in 9mm, an attached sticky note reads: "TRUST ME - DO NOT USE" .</item>
        <item>A 3 pack of bear mace. A sticky note attached to the package reads, "not just for bears."</item>
        <item>An empty 9mm Ruger SR9 pistol.</item>
        <item>A nickel plated Star Model B 9mm with pearl grips and two extra magazines and a chromed Auto-Ordnance M1911A1 .45 with pearl grips and two extra magazines.</item>
        <item>A paper bag containing eighteen .38 rounds.</item>
        <item>A burlap sack filled with several sickles, of varying degrees of quality and age. Most of them are rusty, and some with wooden handles are beginning to rot, but they seem to be well-balanced for fighting, and perhaps even throwing if the need were to arise.</item>
        <item>One Mossberg 590 pump shotgun, 9 shot capacity, with sling and 50 rounds 00 buckshot in a padded nylon firearm case. A note is in the case, handwritten on plain paper: "Leave this for the noobs. Hopefully they won\'t shoot you with it by accident."</item>
        <item>A Vz.52 pistol chambered in 7.62X25 Tokarev with a crude star etched in the grips and a single full 8-round magazine.</item>
        <item>A CZ 550 Safari Classic rifle chambered for .500 Jeffery rounds, pokes out of a roughed-up golf-bag. This bolt-action mammoth, designed for bringing down elephants and bruising the shoulders of even experienced shooters, takes 3 rounds internally. At the bottom of the golf bag are 10 rounds (worth about $50 altogether).\nA successful ARMORER roll (or after testing it) finds that the gun has been custom built for a specific user and anyone else firing it will suffer a 15% penalty to their RIFLE skill.</item>
        <item>A first generation (1970s) Charter Arms Bulldog .44 Special revolver with a 2.5-inch barrel. Comes with a holster, ten defensive hollow-point rounds and a speed-loader.</item>
        <item>A M224 60mm Mortar with four shells and the M8 base plate is attached which brings this monster down to 18 pounds but requires it be fired hand held. Only two of the shells are High Explosive the other two are Infrared Illumination rounds.</item>
        <item>A shipping crate with markings indicating that it contains an M60 machine gun. If opened, the box appears to be filled with kitty litter. If the litter is pushed aside, beneath it are several bottles of vegetable oil, karo syrup, a metal bottle marked, "DANGER: Contains Picric Acid (Wet)" and hand printed instructions for how to turn the box and its contents into an extremely hot and slow burning incendiary device.</item>
        <item>Two pairs of brass knuckles and one Bowie knife.</item>
        <item>Resting in a wooden case along with a leather sheath is a vintage Ithaca Auto &amp; Burglar Gun, a factory built 20-gauge shotgun-pistol with 10-inch smoothbore double-barrels and a contoured pistol grip that comes to a total of 16 inches in length. Only a few thosand were manufactured before Ithaca discontinued it in the wake of the 1934 National Firearms act. It only takes 2 3/4 inch shells.</item>
        <item>A small, uncomfortable mattress of the type found in college dorms or prisons. Made all the more uncomfortable by the fact that someone has hollowed out a football-sized area and filled it with half a dozen Ka-Bar knives.</item>
        <item>A .357 Magnum revolver in mint (i.e., never before used) condition nestled in a finely finished wooden box lined with ice blue crushed velvet. Also in the box are a dozen rounds for the weapon. Inlaid in gold leaf on the lid of the box are the words "Miss Snuggle-bunny" in cheesy Country-Western script.</item>
        <item>A set of brass knuckles with the word "punish" crudely scratched onto their backs, probably with a knife.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag with assorted pistol ammunition (twenty-two 9mm, twelve .38, forty .22, nine .45, four .44 magnum and eight .357 Magnum).</item>
        <item>A J.P. Sauer &amp; Sohn "Western Marshal" single-action revolver chambered for .357 Magnum; this Colt Peacemaker clone, manufactured in West Germany in the 1960s has a six-inch barrel and rosewood grips.</item>
        <item>An AGM-114 Hellfire air to surface missile. Stolen from an airbase in Iraq, it was reported as damaged and destroyed as unstable. It lacks everything you\'d need to use the weapon as intended.</item>
        <item>A pair of worn leather saddle-bags; one containing an empty Glock 17 9mm pistol, the other containing an opened box of 9mm ammunition with twelve rounds left,</item>
        <item>A pistol case containing a Bersa Thunder 9 9mm pistol and two spare 17 round magazines loaded with hollowpoint rounds.</item>
        <item>Eight unopened 50-round boxes of CCI Blazer .45 ACP 230-grain FMJ ammunition.</item>
        <item>A replacement tire and wheel for a large pickup truck (F350 or F250). It\'s much heavier than usual. If one were to pull the tire away from the rim, one would note that it is packed full of C4, not inflated with air. A compact radio detonation assembly has been squished into a crevice in the C4, and can be armed by unscrewing the cap on the valve stem (removing the magnet from a normally-open reed switch).\nSome wonk has written on the chassis-facing side of the wheel "Well, there\'s your problem!" in feltpen.</item>
        <item>An extremely tacky sword-cane, with a little crystal human skull at the top. The release switch sticks a little, but the blade is sharp.</item>
        <item>A crude one-shot zip-gun chambered for a .32 round. It is not loaded.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a fully loaded (8 rounds) Hi-Point C-9 9mm pistol and an opened paper box with seventeen 9mm rounds left. The small gun has been meticulously cleaned of all finger-prints, both external and internal.</item>
        <item>1 AR15 (20-inch barrel, A4-style upper) with attached EOTech and backup iron-sights.\n3 30-round magazines loaded with M885 \'Penetrator\' 5.56 NATO ammunition.</item>
        <item>This long plastic case contains, in addition to a number of packets of silica gel to absorb moisture, a heavy-barreled bolt-action rifle. A successful ARMORER roll will tell the player that it appears to have been built using a postwar Mauser commercial action, and is built to a general pattern--very heavy barrel, spring-loaded scope mounts to protect a delicate target scope from heavy recoil, straight-grain walnut stock--that was back around 1960 very popular among long-range target shooting competitors in the US and Europe. It is also completely free of serial numbers or manufacturers\' markings. It shows signs of use but is clean and lightly oiled. It has an old, possibly European-looking (but unmarked, of course) 20x target scope in the spring-loaded mounts and is in caliber .300 Holland &amp; Holland Magnum. Also present are several unmarked pasteboard boxes each containing twenty rounds of hand-loaded match-grade ammunition with hollowpoint bullets in .300 H&amp;H Mag and a notebook containing trajectory and wind drift data for this ammunition in this rifle out to 1200 meters. Notebook says the rifle is zeroed at 500 meters and has instructions to change the zero point from any point from less than 100m to 1200m.</item>
        <item>A box containing twenty-five .32 rounds.</item>
        <item>2 suppressed Ingram MAC-11 .380 ACP machine pistols, each with an extra clip. (These need to be cleaned before use or there is x4 the normal chance for an accident)</item>
        <item>Two fully-loaded and well-kept ArmaLite AR-18/180s wrapped in sackcloth. Serial numbers show they were manufactured in Japan under license. However, the FBI and the British authorities can link the weapons to an IRA attack on a Belfast pub in 1978 which left five civilians and a British soldier dead.</item>
        <item>A small box stuffed with sticks of dynamite and primacord.</item>
        <item>A scuffed leather pouch containing a fully loaded Ruger Blackhawk .44 Magnum revolver with 4 5/8" barrel, as well as twelve loose .44 Magnum rounds.</item>
        <item>An old sock containing an M84 Stun grenade.</item>
        <item>Six missiles for the FIM-92 Stinger shoulder-fired surface to air missile system, in an unopened US Army ordnance crate. There is no launcher, but they could still be useful for the production of IEDs.</item>
        <item>Hanging unevenly on the wall is a Pink Floyd poster. Lifting it up reveals a Madsen M50 hanging from a hook behind it.</item>
        <item>The parts of an AR-15, distributed and concealed within a rolled-up rug, a coffee can, and a cereal box. About twenty rounds are also present, wrapped in a cloth and placed in a cashew can.</item>
        <item>2 Model 7290 flashbang grenades.</item>
        <item>An opened box of .357 Magnum hollowpoints. Contains only 8 rounds.</item>
        <item>A piece of PVC piping approximately three inches in diameter, a coiled piece of extremely thin wire, a small metal pulley, and four fragmentation grenades. The PVC piping has been spraypainted in camouflage colors, and one side is plugged with a very loose stopper tied to one end of the wire. Appropriate rolls would deduce that this is a booby trap kit similar to ones used by the Viet Cong, in which the pins of the grenades are pulled, then crammed into the pipe. The walls of the pipe keep the safety lever of the grenades from detaching until the tripwire is triggered, removing the stopper and letting the grenades roll out.</item>
        <item>Harrington &amp; Richardson 622 six-shot .22LR revolver with a 6-inch barrel; comes with a belt holster rig.</item>
        <item>A black plastic box containing an empty Ruger P89 9mm pistol and an (empty) extra magazine.</item>
        <item>A black leather shoulder-holster containing a fully loaded Ruger Super Redhawk Alaskan .44 Magnum revolver with a 2.5" barrel and black rubber grip.</item>
        <item>A table leg, with the bottom portion wrapped in electrical tape. Wear and tear suggests it was used as an improvised club.</item>
        <item>A single high explosive round for a British 30 mm ADEN aircraft cannon. The round was manufactured in 1983, but remains stable and viable.</item>
        <item>A high end sporting crossbow, fitted with a light-amplifying scope and a quiver of 16 broadhead composite-shafted bolts.</item>
        <item>a 5-foot long walking staff made of gnarled oak. The words "Hittin\' Stick" are engraved on the top. The bottom third has recently been sanded and re-varnished.</item>
        <item>A can of Pringles potato chips stuffed with homemade C1 Explosive compound.</item>
        <item>Roll of quarters</item>
        <item>A box of twenty 9mm rounds.</item>
        <item>Collection of small pistols in their original boxes with a single magazine each.\n- A Jennings Model J-25 .25 ACP\n- A Bryco 38 .380 ACP.\n- A Tanfoglio Model GT27 .25 ACP\n- A Lorcin L32 .32 ACP\n- An FIE Titan Tiger .25 ACP\n- A Sundance Industries BOA .25 ACP</item>
        <item>A custom rifle case containing a LaRue Tactical OBR carbine with a 12" barrel, chambered for 5.56mm. An EOTech XPS3 holographic weapon sight is mounted on top. There are five black polymer Magpul magazines in the case, each loaded with 28 rounds of Black Hills 77-grain OTM (Open Tip Match)</item>
        <item>A well maintained and polished Marlin Model 1895 lever action rifle, chambered for .45-70. The stock of the gun has a number of cheap beads and a dream-catcher tied to it and "Big Medicine" as been very carefully engraved into the stock. It is unloaded by a dozen .45-70 JSP rounds are found standing in a line next to the gun.</item>
        <item>A Buck knife with stag horn grips and an acid-etched image of a winged serpent on the blade.</item>
        <item>A crudely and apparently hastily assembled piercing weapon made out of a fancy metal pen with a small knitting needle snapped off and jammed inside. The part that would separate has been super-glued shut.\nOn the side of the pen is "Happy 5th Anniversary" The weapon is very slightly bent and there are flecks of blood someone neglected to wash off the tip.</item>
        <item>A sizable survival knife has been lashed with parachute cord to the end of a roughly-hewn oak limb, creating an improvised spear. Anyone who watches survival shows would recognize this as a favored technique of Survivorman star Les Stroud.</item>
        <item>A makeshift knife made out of a sharpened toothbrush and wrapped with a duct-tape handle. It will pass through a metal detector.</item>
        <item>A 9 iron with the words "A man chooses, a slave obeys" engraved on the club face.</item>
        <item>One WWII-era Finnish Mosin M39 rifle, chambered for 7.62x54R., featuring adjustable sights and a canvas-and-leather sling. A box of 20 FMJ rounds is also with the rifle. The weapon (one of the many Finnish factory reworks of captured or purchased Mosin M/91 rifles) is in exceltent condition.</item>
        <item>A olive drab duffel bag, which contains a Heckler &amp; Koch PSG1A1 Sniper Rifle. Also inside the duffel are two 20-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A potato gun that seems to have been retrofit for an actual magazine of three potatoes</item>
        <item>A paper box with fifty .32 rounds.</item>
        <item>A Russian made TM-62M anti-tank mine. Normally it requires a pressure of 200kg to detonate. However this has been modified with a MS-3 anti-personnel mine so that it will detonate with a pressure of just 6kg.</item>
        <item>An adjustable black leather shoulder-holster containing a fully loaded Springfield Armory 1911 .45 pistol with stainless steel finish.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing a fully loaded (15 rounds) Ruger P95 9mm pistol and a loaded extra magazine. The serial number on the gun has been clumsily defaced.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (5 shots) 308 Win. Winchester Model 70 hunting rifle with a mounted scope.</item>
        <item>A well-loved and gently used Stanley Fubar - a titanium allow tool incorporating the best aspects of a wrecking bar, fireman\'s axe, sledgehammer, pickaxe, and chisel. When you absolutely, positively want something to not be there (and you don\'t have power for a Sawzall) this is the tool you want to use.</item>
        <item>An olive-drab green crate that holds five Singaporean-manufactured CIS SAR 21 bullpup 5.56mm rifles. Located in the crate are several translucent plastic thirty-round magazines, enough for 6 magazines for each rifle.</item>
        <item>Glock 17 with night sights, 3 17 round magazines loaded with HP ammunition and a kydex OWB holster</item>
        <item>One Cold Steel Safe Maker I push dagger with a 3.25 inch blade</item>
        <item>.338 Lapua Surgeon rifle customized by GA Precision.</item>
        <item>Hand lapped and trued action, 27 inch Krieger heavy fluted barrel, Jewell trigger, McMillan stock, 3-20x50 Schmidt and Bender rifle scope mounted on a pair of Badger Ordnance rings.</item>
        <item>Comes with a box of 50 hand reloaded 300 gr. Sierra Match Kings on fire formed brass and a proper range card</item>
        <item>A japanese Wakisashi short sword in a simple wooden scabbard. It is marked with japanese script indicating it was made for the military in 1931.</item>
        <item>Footlocker: 500 rounds of each type of ammo (.38, .357 magnum, .44 magnum, .40 S&amp;W, .45 ACP, 9mm)</item>
        <item>A piece of cloth wrapped around an old and sligthly rusty .45 Colt M1911 pistol, with four rounds left in the magazine.</item>
        <item>An dirty rag wrapped around an empty Glock 17 9mm pistol, a spare empty magazine and two loose 9mm rounds.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box sealed with masking tape that has the words "Caution! Explosive!" scribbled in marker on it. Inside the box are ten glass bottles with rags stuffed in the top, filled with homemade napalm.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag containing eight .308 Win. rounds.</item>
        <item>A reconstruction of a pepper-box pistol</item>
        <item>An unused Fire Ax.</item>
        <item>A "zoot stick" (a 2 x 4 set with several razor blades). It looks decades old and badly cared for.</item>
        <item>A long carved walking stick. Or perhaps "staff" is more appropriate, given the tacky occult symbols carved into it.</item>
        <item>A AMT AutoMag V pistol chambered for the .50 Action Express cartridge. Factory compensated with original grips. Comes with three 5-round stainless-steel magazines and two unopened 20-round boxes of Speer 300-grain .50 AE Gold Dot hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A black steel telescoping baton, a high-end police variety. Has a glass-breaker point at the base of the grip. Worn with age, with dried blood on the tip.</item>
        <item>A very small, obviously handmade, derringer-style one-shot pistol loaded with a single 9mm round. Along the barrel the text "Made in Lahore" is written in arabic.</item>
        <item>A well cared for Glock 17 9mm semiautomatic pistol. Someone has lovingly and ornately engraved the name "Scud" into the finish on the slide.</item>
        <item>Four Heckler &amp; Koch G36 assault rifles, with four spare 30rd magazines each and one fully loaded Beta-C 100rd drum magazine.</item>
        <item>A Benchmade Stryker folding knife.</item>
        <item>A well-worn PPSh-41 submachinegun and 4 drum magazines, two empty, one full, one half-full. Someone has zip-tied an EOTech to the top of the barrel and a vertical forward grip-light to the bottom.</item>
        <item>H&amp;K SOCOM Model 23 .45 with silencer, laser aiming module, and 2 extra magazines in a nylon carrying case.</item>
        <item>One fiskars hatchet, worn from use. Dried blood and human hair are stuck to the blade.</item>
        <item>A brand new Kel-Tec KSG 12-gauge pump shotgun, notable for having two ammo tubes under the barrell and a bullpup configuration. Magpul flip-up iron sights are attached to the upper rail, and a foregrip with integrated flashlight is attached to the lower rail. The left tube is loaded with six 3 inch Dixie Terminator slugs and the right with twelve Aguila 1 3/4 inch mini shells. The weapon is clean and ready for use.</item>
        <item>Inside a plastic case lined with dense, high-impact foam padding is a Sig-Sauer P229 Elite in .357 SIG with a Nitron finish. Also included in the case are 6 12-round magazines, a cleaning kit and a Safariland speed scabbard for concealed carry.</item>
        <item>A cardboard carton containing five pistols in glassine bundles, coated with Cosmoline - a snubnosed Smith &amp; Wesson 696 .44 Special revolver, a Colt Woodsman .22LR target pistol, a Colt Python .357 Magnum revolver, a Walther P-38 9mm and a single-shot .22LR target pistol.</item>
        <item>Small arsenal of vintage submachine guns inside a wooden crate: A Madsen M/53 9mm with two extra curved 32-round magazines, a pair of Uzi 9mm SMGs with wooden stocks and two 40-round magazines for each, a Carl Gustav M/45 9mm that has tiny Vietnamese script etched into it\'s wooden grip, and comes with three extra 36-round magazines, a Port-Said 9mm SMG (a licensed Egyptian copy of the M/45) with two extra magazines, a Thompson M1A1 .45 with two extra 30-round magazines and a Mendoza HM-3 9mm that has three extra 32-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A pair of brass knuckles.</item>
        <item>An oil-stained blanket wrapped around a fully loaded Glock 17 9mm pistol.</item>
        <item>An M2 Flamethrower, empty of catalyst fluid and fuel.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (9 rounds) Lorcin Engineering L-22 .22 pistol, with a cheap plastic belt holster.</item>
        <item>A full 50-round box of Winchester Ranger .40 165gr Partition Gold</item>
        <item>A plastic box containing sixty-three .357 Magnum rounds.</item>
        <item>Wrapped in an old carpet is a FN M249 SAW Paratrooper. The weapon has a bipod, telescoping stock and an EOTech holographic weapon sight. There are three 100 round ammo bags with it. Its condition is up to the keeper and may need some cleaning before use.</item>
        <item>4 linked belts of 7.62mm ammo for an M-60. (lying over some larger item or box.)</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (32 round) Intratec TEC-9 9mm pistol, converted to a fully-automatic submachinegun.</item>
        <item>A small briefcase containing a Glock 18 full-auto 9mm pistol, two 33 round magazine and two ordinary 17 round magazines. All the magazines are fully loaded.</item>
        <item>Two 84X246mmR cartidges meant for a Carl Gustav recoilless rifle.</item>
        <item>A small ziploc bag containing five .38 rounds.</item>
        <item>30 rounds (6 boxes) 12 Gauge 00 Buckshot</item>
        <item>A modern blowgun including half a dozen needle-sharp darts with tips covered in a dried substance (old, and quite useless, curare).</item>
        <item>A German-style longsword (AKA \'hand-and-a-half sword\') with a black scabbard and a matching leather belt. All appear to be of modern manufacture. The sword is about 39 inches in total length, including the 30 inch blade. The razor sharp, lightly oiled blade is shiny but exhibits patches of discoloration. The word \'Windlass\' is engraved on one side of the blade near the hilt.</item>
        <item>An old double barreled hunting shotgun in 20 gauge with a box of 14 rounds of accompanying ammunition. The box describes the rounds as being designed for hunting pheasant.</item>
        <item>An Vietnam-era M60 machine gun and several belts of ammunition.</item>
        <item>A package containing five (5) Taser XREP (TM) shotgun shells. When fired each shell lauches a small projectile that delivers a 20 second electrical pulse to the target it strikes, similar to the charge from a Taser stun gun. These shells can be fired from any 12 gauge shotgun, but the fine print on the packaging warns the user not to load or carry the less-lethal shells in combination with conventional shotgun shells, as accidental serious injury or death could result.</item>
        <item>A well-preserved British Sterling Submachine Gun (9x19mm) wrapped in an oilcloth, along with a pair of empty 34-round magazines.\nSome joker with a mind for trivia has taken the time to etch "This machine kills Rebel scum!" below the receiver, and filled the letters in with white lacquer.</item>
        <item>One Smith &amp; Wesson model 10 .38 special revolver, unloaded, wrapped in a oily black cloth.</item>
        <item>A oil-stained rag wrapped around an old Astra 250 .32 revolver with 2" barrel. The snub-nosed gun is fully loaded (5 rounds).</item>
        <item>A pair of black ostrich-skin cowboy boots, size 11. Tucked into the left boot is a Colt Detective Special wrapped in a wad of paper towels, and in the right is a 20-round box of .38 Special ammunition and a stiletto-style dagger, also wrapped in paper towels.</item>
        <item>A reproduction blunderbuss, without powder or shot, that has been modified so that it may be fired. The barrel shows signs of use.</item>
        <item>A police-issue nightstick.</item>
        <item>Several Colt Diamondback .22LR revolvers, popular with novice shooters for their virtually nonexistent recoil.</item>
        <item>A well-worn M1 Carbine made in 1944, and six 30-round magazines for it. No ammunition is present, however.</item>
        <item>A medium-sized metal case, about the size of a traveling trunk, on the outside there is some stuff printed or labeled in French. Opening it up reveals five FAMAS F1 assault rifles, which appear to be French military surplus. Each weapon is fully loaded (25 rounds), and has two spare magazines. These rifles are particularly confusing, as a serial number check shows them to be in inventory in a Alaskan National Guard Armory, but the French shipping information on the outside says it was sent to a non-existent Army base in Alaska.</item>
        <item>A black gym bag containing 14 50-round boxes of Winchester 9mm 115-grain silvertip hollowpoints.</item>
        <item>A plastic bucket containing a very dirty Glock 19 9mm pistol with five rounds left in the magazine. The risk of malfunction is increased by 5% until the gun has been cleaned up.</item>
        <item>A Z-Force ZF-ST 300,000 volt stun gun.</item>
        <item>A Heckler &amp; Koch MP5K-PDW 9mm compact submachine gun with 6 magazines loaded with 147-grain subsonic rounds and an SWR Trident 9 suppressor.</item>
        <item>A worn .45 Colt Commander pistol, with three rounds in the magazine. Strange iridiscent stains can be seen along the top of the gun.</item>
        <item>Two spare magazines for a 9mm Glock 17 pistol. Both are full.</item>
        <item>A Knight\'s Armament SR-25 7.62x51 NATO semi-automatic sniper rifle - featuring a Harris bipod, a Leupold Mark 4 LR/T M1 riflescope, a suppressor and four 20-round box magazines.</item>
        <item>A crude pipe-bomb filled with black powder and nails.</item>
        <item>A small briefcase containing an adjustable shoulder-holster, a fully loaded (7 rounds) Desert Eagle XIX .50AE pistol with a 6" barrel, and two extra (loaded) magazines.</item>
        <item>A French FAMAS G2 assault rifle (unloaded) in spec-ops configuration, with a red dot sight and a M203 grenade launcher (unloaded), with 7 clips of 30 rounds and 3 40mm grenades, and a French PAMAS G1 pistol (unloaded. It\'s a licenced copy of the Beretta 92F) with 3 clips of 15 rounds. All the stuff was obviously never used and is brand new.</item>
        <item>This cardboard box contains six M18A1 "Claymore" antipersonnel mines. Tracing the serial numbers reveals that they were recorded as having been expended in a live-fire exercise at Fort Benning, Georgia in 1984.</item>
        <item>A .40 caliber Beretta 96 resting in a foam-lined case, with two spare clips.</item>
        <item>Four cheap cast-potmetal .22 caliber pistols--two revolvers and two shiny, if scratched-up, nickel-plated semiautos with spare magazines and a few partial boxes of .22 ammo. All four are cheaply, crudely made, and have seen better days. A successful ARMORER skill roll will tell the player that the guns are in poor mechanical condition and likely to misfire, jam, or otherwise malfunction when used. Guns will fail to fire and jam on a roll of 1 on 1d6.</item>
        <item>A box of twenty .32 rounds.</item>
        <item>A brand new Schrade pocketknife with a 2" blade.</item>
        <item>Five red dot sights that disappeared from a unit returning from Iraq in 2009.</item>
        <item>A black briefcase, with a form fitting foam lining, containing a Glock 21 .45 ACP pistol, 5 13 round magazines loaded with FMJ ammo, a silencer, a Kydex holster, and a Kydex dual magazine pouch. The Glock contains an RFID chip in the grip. A trace of the Glocks serial number indicates it was purchased by Wackenhut Security. The silencer is of professional quality, but bears no serial number ( and is therefore highly illegal ).</item>
        <item>A small wooden box containing a Russian PMN-2 anti-personnel mine.</item>
        <item>An ammo box with seven M84 stun grenades. They are hidden behind other equipment to prevent someone from tripping over them.</item>
        <item>A fully loaded (10 rounds) russian SVD 7.62mm semi-automatic sniper rifle equipped with a x4 telescopic sight.</item>
        <item>A Harrington &amp; Richardson 733 revolver with a 2 and 1/2 inch barrel, chambered for .32 S&amp;W Long.</item>
        <item>A soft gym bag containing a fully loaded (6 shot) Mossberg Maverick 88 Security 12 gauge pump action shotgun with an 18.5" barrel, as well as a tied-up handkerchief containing six more 12 gauge rounds.</item>
        <item>An extremely compact AR-15 style weapon firing 9mm Parabellum rounds from MP5 magazines, featuring a collapsible stock, compact holographic sight, and an under-barrel tactical flashlight. There are neither manufacturers\' markings nor signs of their removal on the gun or its accessories, suggesting it was fabricated specially for a government black-op.\nA massive suppressor is attached to the weapon, very nearly longer than the barrel itself. However, it is just as efficient as one would expect for its size.</item>
        <item>A two feet long carefully sharpened and fire-hardened hawthorn stake.</item>
        <item>A crate containing an M1917 water-cooled Browning machine gun, in .30-06. Also in the crate are: Four empty 250-round cloth belts, a belt loading machine, an ammunition box, manual, tripod, and water-condensing hoses and can.</item>
        <item>An M1895 Nagant revolver with attached suppressor. It has 4 spent casings and 3 unfired rounds in the cylinder.</item>
        <item>A sword cane with an ornate carved ivory handle.</item>
        <item>The folded-up profiles of bizarre-looking guns, which an appropriate roll will identify as four M6 Aircrew Survival Weapon. They are break-action weapons with folding stocks, with a barrel for .22 Hornet and a barrel for a .410 shell. Included are fifty rounds of the .22 Hornet and 75 .410 shells.</item>
        <item>A Smith &amp; Wesson .357 Magnum.</item>
        <item>A two-feet length of piano-wire tightly tied to two wooden handles.</item>
        <item>A ziplock bag with 3 rounds of old 7.62x39 Russian surplus and a note. The note reads: RIGGED - For enemy use only</item>
        <item>A Millwall brick; a sort of improvised weapon made from newspaper sheets (in this case this particular brick is made from a local newspaper) rolled and folded to create a handle (a haft) and a rounded head at the fold, to be used like a cosh.</item>
        <item>A blue Nike gym-bag containing :\n- one Beretta 92G Centurion 9mm pistol + 2 extra clips.\n- one Glock 34 9mm pistol + 2 extra clips.\n- one Colt Anaconda .44 Magnum revolver.\n- one Ruger MP9 submachine gun + 1 extra mag.\n- one Armscor M30R8 12 gauge shotgun.\n- 4 boxes of 9mm ammunition (200 rounds).\n- 1 box of .44 Magnum ammunition (25 rounds).\n- 1 box of 12 gauge shotgun shells (20 rounds of 00 buckshot)\n- five black ski-masks.</item>
        <item>A plastic bag with six 12 gauge shotgun slugs in it.</item>
        <item>A Ruger Mini-14 bearing an older-model low-light scope, leaned against a wall. Three empty magazines and 100 rounds of ammunition lie on the floor next to the stock.</item>
        <item>A gaudy looking shopping bag that has a Polish-made PM-63 9mm submachine gun inside, along with 5 twenty-five round magazines.</item>
        <item>Four one-pound blocks of C4 plastic explosives. The wrappers on the blocks prominently read "US ARMY."</item>
        <item>An American Arms Gentry 28 gauge double barrelled shotgun with 26-inch barrels.</item>
        <item>On one of the walls is a peg-board on which hang two or three dozen fixed blade knives with sheaths. They are in various styles and range from small and easily concealable to a few approaching short sword dimensions.\nA note pinned to the board reads "Rule #9"</item>
        <item>A second one in a different hand reads "Knives: Killing stuff for 2.5 million years and counting."</item>
        <item>A small .22 caliber derringer, plated in silver, bearing genuine ivory handles, and covered in ornate engravings. The decorations are rather Arabesque, and masterful in craftsmanship, but what seems to have been a dedication has been violently defaced, ruining its value.</item>
        <item>An empty Taurus Model 65 .357 Magnum revolver with a 4" barrel. The gun comes with a cheap leather shoulder-holster. .38 ammunition would work fine in it as well.</item>
        <item>An opened box of .40S&amp;W handgun ammunition. Twelve rounds remains.</item>
        <item>A two litre glass bottle filled with clear liquid. A hand-written label on its side says "Hydrocloric Acid 38%, handle with care".</item>
        <item>A torn cardboard box full of blue guns - near-perfect nonfunctional replicas of handguns made of dense blue plastic used for training drills. These blue guns happen represent Baretta 9mm\'s and Glock 19\'s.</item>
        <item>Inside a tan carrying case in a corner of the Box is a Freedom Arms Model 83 Field Grade .475 Linebaugh revolver with a 7?-inch barrel and Pachmayr grips and a box of 50 rounds of Hornady Custom 400-grain XTP. A rosary - 50 wooden beads - nestled in the case next to the revolver.</item>
        <item>2 FX-05 "Xiuhcoatl" 5.56x45mm NATO assault rifles of Mexican manufacture, with 3 detachable 30-round box magazines each.</item>
        <item>A gold plated AKMS 7.62x39mm assault rifle with faux ivory "furniture" and two extra gold plated magazines.</item>
        <item>A plastic childrens lunch box containing a Beretta 92S 9mm pistol, with six rounds left in the magazine.</item>
        <item>In a wooden presentation case, one Heckler And Koch P7M8 pistol with Karl Nill wood grips. The slides top left edge is engraved with "76 von 500."</item>
        <item>A Ruger No. 1 single-shot rifle chambered in .45-70, sawed down to the point that it can easily be concealed beneath a jacket. A rubber strap has been mounted on the back end of the stock, so that it can be hung from the shoulder and tucked under the arm.</item>
        <item>A set of boxes that hold the components of a disassembled Lahti L-39, a Finnish 20mm anti-tank rifle manufactured during the Second World War. Fully assembled, the rifle is 88 inches long and weighs 109 pounds empty. One of the boxes contains a wooden ski-folding bipod mount that attaches to the bottom of the gun. Two large triangular flat-bottomed steel boxes with carrying straps are among the gear. Inside each of the boxes are two black-metal magazines holding ten rounds each. Each cartridge weighs three-quarters of a pound and launches a projectile the size of an entire 12-ga. shotgun shell. The foot-long 20mm rounds are mostly loaded with black painted pointed steel projectiles. One magazine has been loaded with yellow-painted projectiles that have flat-nosed aluminum fuses screwed into their tips. These are high-explosive rounds.</item>
        <item>A case containing a Thunder 5 five-shot .45 Long Colt/.410 bore revolver.</item>
        <item>A well-worn USMC K-Bar combat knife in a black leather sheath.</item>
        <item>Five switchblades of different models held together by duct tape.</item>
        <item>A modern recreation of an Aztec \'macuahuitl\' (a club lined with obsidian blades).</item>
        <item>An AR-15 rifle fitted with a suppressor and a telescopic sight. Notably, a brass catcher has been fitted over the ejection port, so ejected shells will be collected in a pouch rather than flung on the ground.</item>
        <item>A Remington Model 51 .32 caliber pistol with a loaded magazine.</item>
        <item>Authentic Comanche war lance.</item>
        <item>Leather bandolier with twenty 12 gauge shotgun shells.</item>
        <item>A black plastic box containing a fully loaded Glock 22 .40S&amp;W pistol and two (loaded) extra magazines.</item>
        <item>2 cattleprods and recharger.</item>
        <item>A worn Glock 22 10mm pistol. The gun is fully loaded (15 rounds) and comes with an adjustable shoulder-holster.</item>
        <item>A basic boxcutter.</item>
        <item>An empty Smith&amp;Wesson Model 19 revolver with 6" barrel. It is slightly rusty and could use some maintenance.</item>
        <item>One 9x18mm Makarov pistol with extended threaded barrel, silencer, 5 loaded 8 round magazines of FMJ ammunition, all contained within an oil stained canvas bag.</item>
        <item>An AMT Lightning .22LR target pistol with a integral suppressor, adjustable sights and Crimson Trace Corporation laser-sight grip. Three stainless steel 10-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A Webley Mk VI .455 caliber top-break revolver. 4 of 6 chambers are loaded.</item>
        <item>A Spyderco Delica4 folding knife with 2.875" blade and black handle.</item>
        <item>A Beretta Cx4 9mm carbine, mounted with a Zeiss Z-Point red dot sight, an Insight Tech tactical light/laser sight combo and a Surefire 6p tactical light. Fitted with a single point tactical sling. Comes with five 30-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box containing two glass bottles. One is filled with crystals. It is marked "Hydrocyanic salt". The other contains a colorless liquid and is marked "H2SO4". Yep, this is what you mix in the gas chamber.</item>
        <item>A Hawk Engineering MM-1 grenade launcher. Its chambered in 37mm and is used to disperse smoke and tear gas grenades.</item>
        <item>A fifty round box of 9mm ammunition.</item>
        <item>A well-maintained Kukri</item>
        <item>A fully loaded .44 Magnum Smith&amp;Wesson M29 revolver with 4" barrel, in an adjustable leather shoulder holster.</item>
        <item>A Coca Cola can.\nInside is about 70 grams of C4 surrounded by a wall of 40 nails.\nIgnition is achieved by opening the can like any other soda beverage. A small needle pierces the soft primer of a blasting cap as the lip is bent down, thus igniting the C4 explosive.\nExplosive device inside is surrounded by 8 ounces of vegetable oil to fully replicate a refreshing beverage.\nHandle with care.</item>
        <item>1 Cold Steel "Spetsnaz" shovel</item>
        <item>A metal carrying case that says "From Russia, With Love" on it. Inside is an fully loaded (30 rounds) AK-101 Assault Rifle chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO, with fire selector and folding stock. Also inside the case are two spare magazines, and a shipping receipt in Russian, from a non-existent Russian gun-seller.</item>
        <item>Three-pound sledgehammer - the words "The Tickler" are crudely etched into one side.</item>
        <item>A wooden crate containing packing foam and six Norinco CQ 5.56mm M4 semiautomatic sporter carbines. These are civilianized Chinese "bootlegs" of the US armed forces\' Colt M4 assault rifle, and, while available elsewhere in the world, are quite illegal in the United States. This shipment is mislabelled as "Air Conditioning Units" and slipped across the border from Canada into Detroit.</item>
        <item>Three tear-gas grenades.</item>
        <item>A Harrington &amp; Richardson single shot 16-gauge shotgun.</item>
        <item>Three compact Beretta 9000 semi-auto pistols, chambered for .40 S&amp;W. Two spare 10-round magazines apiece, all stashed inside a padded black pistol case.</item>
        <item>A small prison shank made from a sharp copper wire, with a grip of wound boot lace.</item>
        <item>Stainless steel bowie knife measuring 19 inches overall with a 13 inch blade. Features a solid wood handle, brass guard and backstrap, and a leather belt sheath. Manufactured in Pakistan.</item>
        <item>A Daisy .177 caliber pellet gun rated at 980 FPS. Further inspection reveals it is a bolt action single shot piece with mounted target sights. It comes with a pair of 5-shot pellet holder clips and a small tin of five-hundred pellets.</item>
        <item>Six WWII-era Mk.2 hand grenades inside a small wooden case stuffed with straw.</item>
        <item>A Colt M1911 service pistol, dated 1944. It is obvious that its owner kept it scrupulously clean, with no obvious signs of rust. An image of the Confederate flag has been engraved into the slide, just above the initials J.L.J. Two spare magazines are found with the pistol inside a worn leather bag.\nThe pistol is not loaded, but the bag contains 14 rounds of .45 ACP.</item>
        <item>This item is a large and bulky silencer with standard threads, and will work on a .22, handgun, or pistol-caliber SMG only. It is in need of maintenance and will only work for twelve more shots before it stops suppressing the noise. Disassembling it will reveal that instead of steel baffles or a spiral gas diffuser inside, it is a WWII-era "wet" type unit, with a sheet of asbestos cloth smeared with axle grease wrapped around the perforated central spindle. A successful ARMORER roll will be needed to clean the asbestos cloth without damaging it then reapply the axle grease properly, then reassemble the unit correctly, after which it will work for another very roughly one hundred shots, more with a .22, less with full-auto fire.</item>
        <item>OD green duffel bag containing 1 M4 carbine ( fitted with ACOG, sling and surefire tac light ), 6 30 round magazines, type IV body armor with 4 magazine pouches and 400 rounds 5.56mm ammunition in 20 round boxes on stripper clips.</item>
        <item>A loaded one-shot flare gun.</item>
        <item>A small letter opener stained with blood. It is engraved with "Soap from Corpses Products, Inc. 2009".</item>
        <item>A police issue carrying belt containing steel handcuffs, keys for the handcuffs, rubber gloves, evidence bags, small flashlight, nightstick, a fully loaded Glock 17 9mm pistol and two extra magazines (loaded) for the gun.</item>
        <item>Wrapped in a greasy old oiled cloth are a very worn, rather old-looking semiauto pistol and three magazines that fit it. The only markings on the pistol are "RUBY" stamped on the side of the slide and "7.65mm" on the exposed portion of the barrel visible through the ejection port. No serial number is present, nor is there ammunition for it in the drawer where it was found. A successful ARMORER skill roll will tell the player that tens of thousands of cheaply made pistols like this one were manufactured in an assortment of small factories in Spain and exported to France for military issue during the First World War, that they were not well made by the standards of the time, that parts don\'t necessarily interchange between two similar-looking RUBY pistols, and that it uses the still relatively common .32 ACP/7.65mm Browning Short pistol cartridge. It holds eight in the magazine plus one in the chamber, though it is probably not safe to carry it with a cartridge ca. The user is entitled to a Luck roll to see whether it will jam or misfire when used, or whether it will fire accidentally if dropped.</item>
        <item>A plastic ice cream box containing a fully loaded Glock 17 9mm pistol and a plastic ziploc bag with fourteen 9mm rounds.</item>
        <item>Taser model x26c with holster. Also their are 6 cartridges and 1 extra battery pack fully charged.</item>
        <item>Vintage 1970s Stihl 044 Chainsaw with a full tank of gas.</item>
        <item>A Mosin-Nagant 91/30 rifle with a hex receiver indicating manufacture in Smolensk in 1936. The rear elevation sight is missing and the bolt is hard to move.</item>
        <item>A large Folgers Coffee can with a tight-fitting plastic lid. The coffee can is about three-quarters full of a fine reddish-silver dust and is surprisingly heavy. Yep, it\'s full of home-made thermite.</item>
        <item>Mosin Nagant M44 bolt action rifle with sling. No ammunition is present. The butt of the rifle has dried blood and hair stuck to it and the bayonet is pitted as if by acid.</item>
        <item>Three cases, each containing a Heckler &amp; Koch MP7A1 submachine gun.along with a nine-inch Gemtech suppressor and ten 40-round magazines holding 4.6x30mm Fiocchi CPS "Black Tip" slugs.</item>
        <item>An oily rag wrapped around a worn Llama 1911 Minimax .45 pistol with 3.7" barrel. The small gun is fully loaded (six rounds) but the original neoprene grips have fallen off and been replaced with rubberbands wrapped around the grip.</item>
        <item>A J&amp;R Engineering M80 9mm carbine with a PVC stock; comes with a pair of 30-round magazines.</item>
        <item>A modern metal/plastic hunting crossbow with a small scope and four bolts attached to its top.</item>
        <item>A woman\'s purse containing red lipstick, a small mirror and a fully loaded (7 rounds) Beretta 3032 Tomcat .32 pistol. The small gun has four tiny scores carved into the grip.</item>
        <item>A pair of tonfa - tradition Okinawan martial arts weapons made up of a stick with a handle, used for striking and blocking, usually wielded in pairs. This set are 20 inches long and made from straight-grained Canadian hardwood.</item>
        <item>An empty Smith&amp;Wesson M&amp;P9 9mm pistol.</item>
        <item>A Soviet Spetsnaz Ballistic Shooting Knife produced during the 80\'s.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>