<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_weird_misc">
        <item>A coroner\'s body bag, labeled "Hamilton County Morgue." It is empty, but has a faint rancid smell. Parts of the inside of the bag have been torn, as if something were trying to claw its way out.</item>
        <item>Glued to the wall are dozens of "tart-cards" - flyers left in telephone booths to advertise a prostitute\'s services. These ones recommend "Black Fan Goddess: Masterful Oriental Massages From The Larger Lady". The contact number is for the Toronto area but the line\'s disconnected.</item>
        <item>Bandage made of Human flesh.</item>
        <item>WW1-era gas mask.</item>
        <item>A slightly yellowed antique hand-blown glass bottle, stoppered with a cork, and sealed with green wax. Inside the bottle are three square nails, a Roman coin, a small red flower, and two human thumbnails.</item>
        <item>There is a wooden pallet holding 5 100kg lead ingots. Each one is inscribed with various invocations, prayers &amp; spells protecting against demons &amp;/or devils(strange, they seem to focused inward). A note requests A-Cell be contacted for permanent disposistion.</item>
        <item>In the corner of the Green box sits a professionally made refrigeration unit, cooled by liquid helium. The system runs has a series of generators hooked up to it, allowing it to run during extended power outages. The area is fenced off by chain link fence and has a warning to not mess with the system. Whatever is on ice, someone spent a lot of time and effort insuring it stays that way.</item>
        <item>A small bag that contains 3 pills. Upon inspection the capsules are revealed to have been opened, it\'s contents replaced with blood.</item>
        <item>Three large magnetic cassette tapes, the type that fit into an older computer from the 1970s (an IBM 5100, in fact). The tapes contain "problem solver libraries" written in APL language. A note taped to them states the program will figure coordinates in four dimensions.</item>
        <item>A rubber ball that bounces one inch higher with every bounce.</item>
        <item>A sizable military insignia hangs from the wall of the Green Box; it is easily recognizable as that of the Strategic Air Command.\nCloser examination reveals it to be made of the same material a normal military unit patch would be. Also, in a blatant defiance of common sense and rational thought, it has somehow been sewed onto the wall.</item>
        <item>A stuffed dog mounted on a wood base labeled, "Mr. Kitty."</item>
        <item>A pane of glass with a strange stick symbol etched in the glass</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing eight feet of rolled up 1/2" rope ending in a professionally tied hangman\'s noose.</item>
        <item>Wrapped in a tarp is an old neon sign that continues to flicker despite having no power source. What business the sign belonged too is at the Keepers discretion.</item>
        <item>A set of eight rectangular copper plates (6" by 8"). Each plate is covered in neat etched rows consisting of the 1/4" high letters "A", "C", "G", and "T". The text appears to be a random mix of the letters, but someone knowledgeable in medicine may get the feeling it is (part of) a DNA sequence. At each corner of a plate is a small hole.</item>
        <item>A box of 37 remains - marked Geheimhaven Base 08/15/1936. An island north of Crete that had a Nazi submarine base on it during WW2.\nThe remains are mostly ash, some have a few charred bones in them, but some unrecognizable goo is included. The box, actually the remains, are slightly magnetic and radioactive.</item>
        <item>An icepick. The wooden handle has been carved into a likeness of the Creature from the Black Lagoon.</item>
        <item>A full set of engineering drawings for the 50m Haunebu III flying disc, they appear to be genuine WWII era documents.</item>
        <item>A sealed file folder labeled "Top Secret", "Eyes Only", "Property of the NSA", and "Destroy After Reading". Inside are a series of photo booth pictures of an attractive teenage couple, dressed in alterna-teen fashion, making out in the photo booth. There is absolutely nothing to explain the security classification.</item>
        <item>The back of the Green box has been defaced with the message: "We\'re all in Carcosa Now."</item>
        <item>A dirty, coffee-stained, sealed envelope. If you open it, you will find a sheet of paper with your name, your date of birth and another date six months in the future.</item>
        <item>An x-ray of a two-headed snake labeled "Honduras" with a magic marker.</item>
        <item>An original production iPod, very scratched, with headphones. Any song placed on the device plays backwards and will only play if connected with the headphones it came with. Within the noise of the reversed songs an agent can hear distant quiet words.</item>
        <item>An intricate Voudoun veve to the death goddess Maman Bridjit has been drawn on the floor in a mix of blood, salt and chalk. A dead black rooster rots in its centre.</item>
        <item>One vampire costume, including suit, cape and fake teeth.</item>
        <item>A plastic rifle case, empty except for a notebook containing what appears to be genealogical research around a specific Massachusetts family descended from a sea captain named Morgan Barlowe. One particular name, Matthew Barlowe, is ringed with red. Investigation into that name finds that Matthew Barlowe, age 6, was killed together with two other children two years ago when an unknown sniper opened fire on their kindergarten,</item>
        <item>Fragments of a giant clay statue of a man. Where would be the head shows signs of use of explosive or heavy ordinance. The crate mentions it comes from Prague.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box with "research materials" written on it in black marker,. It contains the following: six bottles of Maker\'s Mark bourbon, several issues of "Modern Drunkard magazin" dating from the late 1990s; "The Disaster Area", a 1992 paperback collection of short stories by J. G. Ballard - the story "Mr. F is Mr. F" has notes and observations concerning vorarephilia scribbled in the margins; printouts from several websites of drawings and images involving bondage, extreme torture, cannibalism, and murder, all represented as consensual and bearing the signature "Dolcett"; several printouts of "furry" art by different artists featuring graphic depictions of vore; a recipe for something called "placenta stew"; "In the Fog", a paperback novel by Issei Sagawa (out of print and valuable); a photocopy of an article on "Lesch-Nyhan syndrome", source unknown; a printout of an article called "Butchering the Human Carcass for Human Consumption", by Bob Arson; and an empty file folder with "report #3412" written on it. The issues of "Modern Drunkard Magazine" seem to be there just for entertainment value; reading the rest of the materials takes 12-15hrs and costs 0/1d2 SAN.</item>
        <item>In the back corner behind some old file cabinets someone has setup a server. The system is has no screen or input devices. The connections to it were run without the knowledge of the storage owners. It has a backup power source inside the server that is not evident to those without some skill related to electronics or computers. Attempts to physically access the system or unplug it will result in the system reformatting itself and its drives.\nThis could be used as a DG asset, a government system or a something unrelated. There are more spook shows going on then DG or MJ12.</item>
        <item>A pamphlet, crudely made, several years old.\nIt purports to a copy of some notes written by one Halpin Chalmers, a 1920\'s writer. Reading through the papers, one can crudely gather that the author had some strange theories about reality, a mix of Eastern mysticism and modern mathematics. There follows a few pages of strange formulas, the only one making any sense is Einstein\'s famous "E=MC^2". The last page references a strange experiment, but nothing else is mentioned.\nThe last page is covered in dried blood.</item>
        <item>An old leatherbound pocket bible. There are several deep stab marks from some sharp triangular implement penetrating about halfway through it. If examining the pages it can be found that the text closest around the stab marks have changed into gibberish.</item>
        <item>A large, menacing-looking machine takes up most of the space in the Green Box. Examination by someone literate in the subject will reveal it to be the stripped-out trash compactor mechanism of a garbage truck, rigged to an external power source and anchored to the floor.</item>
        <item>A small bottle of water with a spray attached to it. Whenever used. blood is spritzed out of it. -1 to Sanity upon first use.</item>
        <item>A leather doctor\'s bag containing a small collection of four aborted fetuses preserved in jars filled with formalin. The jars are marked "A", "B", "C" and "X". The "X" specimen is slightly malformed with vestigial tentacles growing from its chest.</item>
        <item>A extremely large (5" long) but dead cockroach.</item>
        <item>A scrapbook containing three-hundred and thirty-three Polaroid snaps of late-1980s Eastern European streets. Careful study finds the same 1948 Citreon 2CV in the background of each picture. The numberplate is British and this year\'s.</item>
        <item>A commonly-available Motorola pre-paid mobile phone and compatible wall-charger. The screen is cracked and completely unreadable. The balance on this phone never seems to expire or run dry regardless of where a call is placed or for how long, suggesting that the account is still being fed by its previous owner.</item>
        <item>A small wooden case bearing the Miskatonic University seal. Inside is a dusty glass cylinder package swathed in bubble-wrap and tape. The cylinder contains yellowed formaldehyde and parts of a very large (15") insect. The creature can be identified by an entomologist as a eurypterid, an arthropod that has been (supposedly) extinct for abut 250 million years. The jar bears a worn label saying "Specimen Two".</item>
        <item>A transparent plastic box containing hundreds of large dead cockroaches.</item>
        <item>a still-warm bucket of KFC drumsticks.</item>
        <item>A single surgical glove tied up and filled with dead red ants.</item>
        <item>A small chemistry lab stands in the corner of the Green Box, along with a table covered in various bullets and bladed weapons.</item>
        <item>It appears as though some misguided soul has been coating them in pure cholesterol, as though it were some kind of stereotypical poison.</item>
        <item>A bell, a copy of the King James version of the Bible, and a candle all in a cardboard box. The handbell is silver and has a wooden handle. The candle is halfway burned down but appears to have been cut to its currently length. The Bible has most of the New Testament except for the Book of Revelation ripped out or defaced with black paint.</item>
        <item>An olive branch bearing golf ball sized olives and a printout of an e-mail in modern Hebrew from a Knesset member\'s office briefly inquiring to the Agriculture Minister "Per our earlier conversation, WHY would a single station cost so much? You\'ve got to give me something." The olives are dun-colored, but speckled like quail eggs. These fruits are unique to a variety of olive tree grown on an agricultural station outside of Haifa. The olive orchard at the station is a marker for a buried mastaba, which can be accessed through a secret tunnel dug from a nearby dormitory\'s basement. The olive trees were grown from pits recovered from the tomb, and the tomb wasn\'t built by any known human civilization.</item>
        <item>3.5-inch floppy disk containing 4 nude jpegs of Anna Kournikova and a copy of the \'Love Worm\' computer virus.</item>
        <item>2 complete \'Ku Klux Klan\' outfits.</item>
        <item>A small cooling box containing stinking water and four blood bags filled with rotting blood.</item>
        <item>Three syringes in a see-through plastic case.One contains anabolic steroids, one contains blood (Type O Negative), and the last one contains a neurotoxins. A successful medicine check will tell an agent that all three of these syringes have been used at least once before...</item>
        <item>A crouching, man-sized effigy of a grinning frog-like creature poised as if preparing to leap, lovingly crafted out of human faeces and newspaper. The smell is abominable.</item>
        <item>A large glass jar full of smallish irregularly shaped items that look like silver-colored plastic pellets, or possibly small irregular rounded pieces of metal. A hand-written label says "INSTANT SHOGGOTHS! Just add water!"</item>
        <item>One human skull. An electric plug has been affixed to the bottom. Visible inside the skull cavity are two lights, one red, one green. If plugged in, the lights light up in an alternating pattern.</item>
        <item>The corners of the Green Box contain several horrifyingly modified mousetraps. They are all of the largest size on the market, and have been reinforced both structurally and lethally, with small-diameter steel rebar and razorblades respectively. They have also been bolted to the floor, and, most disturbingly, have been baited with what are clearly human fingers and toes.\nIt is unclear what monstrous vermin these traps are intended to catch; none of them have been triggered, and there is no sign of infestation if the investigators look for it.</item>
        <item>A wooden box with a soft lining which contains several dark rocks made of some kind of ore. An analysis reveals them to be of extraterrestrial origin, probably meteorites.</item>
        <item>A Girl Scout merit badge for woodcraft, with dried blood spatter on it.</item>
        <item>An airtight plastic box containing a single sealed vial carefully wrapped in multiple layers of bubble plastic. The vial has about a tablespoon of grey-white powder in it and is labeled: "Bacillus Anthracis, Ames Strain".</item>
        <item>A large Tupperware container with the words "SMEAR BOX" written on top in ink. Inside are three small glassine envelopes filled with cocaine, two vials containing rocks of crack cocaine, several copies of magazines featuring child pornography, a collection of matchbooks from gay bars, some VHS tapes and DVDs of hardcore gay porn movies, several leaflets, flyers and pamphlets of white supremacist propaganda, a poorly printed Jihadist recruitment paper, a USB flash drive loaded with Jihadist webpages/e-mails and two well-worn loaded pistols (a .32 caliber Seecamp LWS and a 9mm Walther P-88) with attached notes detailing the time and place where they were used in different crimes. All items are packaged in different plastic-bags. Also included in the box are a pair of surgical gloves.</item>
        <item>Large Freezer bag with two smaller bags inside, one containing course, thick hairs and the other a 9MM clip filled with silver bullets. The freezer bag is labeled Werewolf, Atlanta 1987.</item>
        <item>A duffel bag containing an archaeology tool kit (containing brushes, picks, tweezers, etc.), some clothing, two sticks of dynamite, a ID card, and $1000 in cash.\nThe ID list one Rose Christopher, a college student who disappeared years ago.\nFurther investigation would show that she was involved with the Wilmarth Foundation, and was MIA during a mission on behalf of the Foundation. The bag was found by a DG agent who was sent to investigate the matter.</item>
        <item>An ornate glass snowglobe with a small bronze plaque which simply reads "dry-88". The \'snow\' is gray like ash, and on closer examination the scene within is a scale replica of the green box itself, current contents included, perfect aside from burn damage on much of the room and its contents, and two occupied black body-bags portrayed as being propped against the wall. The snow globe exhibits no anomalous properties.</item>
        <item>A cylinder, of approximately 5cm radius and 11cm height, of 1cm thick lexan clear plastic, holding some kind of greenish organic-looking thing. It occasionally twitches. The label says "Please wait for death"</item>
        <item>The room is thick with furry-bodied flies and insects, and there\'s the rancid stench of decay. Something has obviously died in here and been rotting away for a long while.</item>
        <item>A black-and-white photograph of an old man with whisker stubble. Anyone who looks at the photo will recall vague childhood memories of knowing him, but will be unable to recall his name.</item>
        <item>Four vacuum-sealed, sterile plastic sleeves of three pre-dosed, one-shot hypodermic syringes with small gauge needles. "HU-210: anti-anx. and anti-dprss.," has been scribbled on the packs in block letters. The seal of Hebrew University in Jerusalem is stamped on the back of the packets along with serial numbers and U.S. Customs and DEA decals (all of this data indicates the drugs are held lawfully by one of the PCs.) Next to the pile of packets are a bottle of rubbing alcohol, a bag of cotton balls, and a red plastic, pint-sized biohazard needle disposal container. A post-it note on the container reads,"NO DRUG TESTS!!! = 9 wks."</item>
        <item>A dead cat has been crucified to the wall of the Green Box.</item>
        <item>Three garbage bags, each has been filled with the shattered remains of a human skeleton.</item>
        <item>A set of photographs representing the Agents in the future, on their leaving of the Green Box (the picture looks like it\'s been taken from a security camera, but none are found on the premises).</item>
        <item>Three rather plain-looking metal urns with screw-on lids. They contain ashes, as well as small blackened pieces of bone and enamel. Each has a small card with a handwritten note on them. The three notes say: "Agent Rufus", "Agent Roark" and "Agent Rose".</item>
        <item>A black, generic case for a Playstation 2 game. Opening the case reveals a pitch black disc, and the game manual, which has had its cover ripped off. A hand-written note, in English, is tucked in front of the manual. It reads, "Play the game if you want, but whatever you do DON\'T BEAT THE FINAL BOSS!"\nReading the manual or playing the game reveals it to be an English port of a Japanese game set in a rural Japanese town where people are being murdered by being thrown into TVs, where if they stay to long they are killed in a most horrific fashion by alien creatures not of this dimension. The main character is a high-schooler who battles these creatures by summoning various mythos entities to serve him, having been taught these abilities by in his dreams by a mysterious man with pure-black eyes, while the trying to balance his school and social life, and is aided by other classmates who gain similar abilities after being thrown in the TV. The game has a very cheery tone for being so horrific.\nAt no point is the name of the game or the manufacturer ever mentioned. All instances of it in the manual are either blank spaces, or have been blacked out. When the game is started, it goes straight to a simplistic main menu which only says "New Game" and "Continue". Playing the game takes 60-70 hours, costs 1/1d4 SAN and grants 5% Occult and 2% Cthulhu Mythos. Keeper\'s discretion what happens if they characters defeat the final boss.</item>
        <item>Several kitchen knives have been stuck into the inside of the Green Box\'s door with seemingly superhuman force.</item>
        <item>A box of Christmas ornaments, marked for destruction. If careful studied the players will observe that the ornaments are not totally wholesome, there are what appear to be depictions of mythos creatures in very stylized form.</item>
        <item>A cardboard box, unmarked except for a label that reads "Cyanide" and filled with individual plastic bottles each containing a single replica of a human tooth. There are three missing from a box of 20.</item>
        <item>The titles to a house in Centralia.</item>
        <item>A sealed vial containing clear liquid marked with a label saying "Holy Water".</item>
        <item>A black and white photo of six young men in suits smiling and standing together in an old chemistry lab. "December 15, 1956" was apparently penned on the negative for the photo. Paperclipped to this is another photo of the same men on a beach. It has the digital time stamp "December 15, 1993." The men have not aged, although all of them appear to have cataract clouded eyes. One man wears a knitted mitten over his right hand, which is odd given the men are wearing shorts, short-sleeved shirts, and sandals. "Dr. Joe Ridley - Progeria Study Group IIa," is penned on the back of both photos.</item>
        <item>A Ronald McDonald suit from the 1970\'s..</item>
        <item>A set of British Army ECBA (Enhanced Combat Body Armor) in desert camouflage for protection against low velocity projectiles, in the pockets which would hold strike plates (back and front) for protection against high velocity projectiles are two hardback copies of Peter F. Hamilton\'s novel "The Neutronium Alchemist."</item>
        <item>A snowball from the North Pole that doesn\'t melt even in a furnace.</item>
        <item>A large wall poster, about 2 feet by 3 feet in size. The poster depicts a very photogenic human baby clutching a .357 Magnum pistol as if it were a teddy bear. The barrel of the gun is in the baby\'s mouth. The caption "Honey? Have you seen my gun?" is printed along the top of the poster, and along the bottom is printed "Always practice gun safety! Keep weapons unloaded and locked up when not holstered!"</item>
        <item>An old suitcase with a damaged zipper, that makes it almost impossible to open. Inside is a bunch of 70\'s suits and apparel. There is a note saying, "Be sure to deliver this to Hunter, at 54 Glebe. Hes expecting them."</item>
        <item>An accordion. It is covered with a layer of fine ash and has a burnt odor, but is still playable.</item>
        <item>A small glass bottle of exotic shape containing a green liquid. It is stoppered with a red wax seal and has a label saying "Ichor of Zhrothros". A closer inspection reveals the bottle to originally be a massproduced perfume bottle, and the content turns out to be colored water.</item>
        <item>A corrugated cardboard shipping box, roughly one foot by one foot by two feet, filled with styrofoam peanuts (packing materials). No matter how many peanuts are removed the box remains filled with them. The only way to stop the flow of peanuts is to open the bottom of the box and flatten it; the moment it is reassembled it refills with the peanuts.</item>
        <item>In the back corner behind some old file cabinets someone has setup a server. The system is has no screen or input devices. The connections to it were run without the knowledge of the storage owners. It has a backup power source inside the server that is not evident to those without some skill related to electronics or computers. Attempts to physically access the system or unplug it will result in the system reformatting itself and its drives.\nThis could be used as a DG asset, a government system or a something unrelated. There are more spook shows going on then DG or MJ12.</item>
        <item>A new paperback copy of "Psilocybin Mushrooms of the World: An Identification Guide" by Paul Stamets. A dehydrator contains a dozen reduced, golden-capped mushrooms on its racks. Two airtight kitchen containers have a dozen more dried mushrooms each. One contains long, spindly specimens with a pinkish colour, and is marked with an embossed red plastic label reading "PERSUASIVE." The other contains dark green specimens resembling shriveled golf balls, and is marked with a blue label reading "ENTICING."</item>
        <item>Rolled sheets meant to be posted onto a 14\' by 18\' billboard. The sheets show a "blivet" (in this case a \'Devil\'s Fork\') and the motto "The Impossible Is True- www.daolothtech.com" The website is non-functioning, but was briefly registered three years ago.</item>
        <item>A slightly worn VHS tape with "B.S. or Not?? NRO-DELTA?" written on the label in black pen. Recorded on the tape are 5 hour long episodes of a conspiracy talk show "Truth Seeking with James Zarella" on Seattle public access cable during 1997. All 5 episodes seem to focus on interviews other conspiracy theorists claiming the US government maintains secret underground bases in the American Southwest with the co-operation of aliens and that US test pilots are secretly flying reverse engineered spacecraft.</item>
        <item>A life-sized body pillow depicting rapper and Law and Order SVU star Ice-T dressed in a tuxedo that looks like it\'s from the early 1990\'s. The body pillow looks like a custom job, and is still wrapped in shipping plastic.</item>
        <item>Bootleg DVD of obscure Japanese anime series called "New Century Gospel." DVD has all 26 episodes plus the two-hour finale, if in somewhat grainy, highly compressed, English subtitled format. The first episode or two make it appear to be a fairly conventional teen-boy-pilots-giant-robot-to-save-Tokyo series, though with a quirky sense of humor, engaging and likable characters, and vastly above-average animation and voice acting. However, as the series goes on, the plot becomes bizarre and byzantine, the mood gets darker and bleaker, and Mythos elements begin to appear--an expedition to the Mountains of Madness in Antarctica, Tokyo besieged by an enormous dhole, the protagonist learns the "giant robots" are actually armored shoggoths summoned and bound by ghastly rituals of human sacrifice and armed with hyper geometrical weaponry, etc. All major characters, but especially the protagonist, break down psychologically under the pressure. The two-hour finale shows the protagonist giving in to despair and committing suicide, and the remaining characters, not to mention all of humanity, dying in graphically hideous ways as the stars become right, and the Great Old Ones return and scour the planet Earth clean of all life. Watching the entire thing is psychologically traumatic: 1d6/2d8 SAN loss, 4% Mythos. Attempting to investigate the stated producers, animators, and voice acting cast of the series is a dead end: every single one of them committed suicide between 1989 and 2007.</item>
        <item>A large ziploc bag containing a blue fountain pen, a pair of surgical gloves, a syringe marked "Paralytic", a package of razors and another (slightly smaller) ziploc bag with four A4 sheets of handwritten suicide notes. The notes are all written using blue ink and with the same style of handwriting, but with slightly different content, as if the writer hasn\'t quite decided on the best text. They are all signed "Sarah".</item>
        <item>A small ziploc bag containing a blackened and slightly deformed silver pendant in the form of a Star of David.</item>
        <item>The center of the Green Box has been converted into a makeshift, but very professional looking, autopsy theatre. While the slab in use is a ping-pong table, all the necessary tools are arrayed out in meticulous order, and a note attached to them reads "Do not disturb, will need this shortly. Thanks in advance."\nTrue to their word, if the party returns after about a day, the table has been sanitized and the tools have been packed up and taken.</item>
        <item>The Green Box has multiple mousetraps scattered around it in improbable locations, including glued to the walls and ceiling.\nSome of them have been baited with human fingers. 0/1 SAN loss.</item>
        <item>Blurry photograph of wolf-like biped with accompanying notes "Savannah, 1987. Investigate further. Precautions to take: ?" and baggy of course grey hair</item>
        <item>A three-tier wedding cake. The little statue of the groom appears to be a deep one.</item>
        <item>A laser grid similar to those used by ghost hunters to look for movement.</item>
        <item>A small cloth bag that, when opened, will reveal a pair of large spiders. They both measure about 6\'\' by 6\'\', and are unnaturally heavy. If you allow them, they will latch themselves onto your hands and dig their fangs into your flesh, making them extremely diffucult to remove. Two back legs secure around your wrist, their middle four legs lay over your thumb, pointer, ring and pinkie fingers, and the remaining front legs wrap around on opposite sides of your middle fingers. This configuration grants you a stronger grip, and with practice you might even be able to climb walls.</item>
        <item>The door handle of the green box is slimy and somewhat sticky. Forensic analysis will reveal that somebody spent way too long licking the doorhandle. Way too long.</item>
        <item>This box contains round envelopes, for circular letters.</item>
        <item>A black cape, with a small label sewn onto the lining that reads, "If Found, Please Return To B. Wayne, Stately Wayne Manor, Gotham City".</item>
        <item>The severed head of a woman, aged about 30, with medium length brown hair. The head is visibly starting to decay, and has an unpleasant but bearable smell. Its eyes are closed and the left ear has a simple gold earring. The right ear is pierced but has no earring.\nAfter the head has been observed for about 30 seconds the eyes and mouth will snap wide open and red smoke will start to pour out of the mouth for two minutes. The smoke smells both sweet and metallic. It is not toxic, but if the head is being viewed in a confined space (e.g. if they are still in the Green Box) the investigators will need to vacate the area because of the volume of smoke.\nThis process only ever happens once. SAN loss 1-3/2-7 for anyone observing; much more if the head is of someone known to the investigators (Keeper\'s discretion).</item>
        <item>A pressure suit from a U-2 spy plane, the suit has several gashes in it as if attacked by some unknown foe.</item>
        <item>A small plastic box filled with brown recluse spiders. The spiders make a small "Scritch-scritch-scritch" noise.</item>
        <item>An aviation chart of the northern half of Ohio, annotated with 89 sets of dates, times, and course data. Research matches the data set to the MUFON database: every annotation is the position and course information of a commercial or civil aviation flight that reported a UFO sighting. The dates range from 1954 to 2001. Pattern analysis reveals no discernible pattern.</item>
        <item>One shovel for each investigator. Attached to each is a note addressing them by name and in their own handwriting</item>
        <item>A well-used Mr. Coffee Advanced Brew 5 Cup Coffee Maker, which seems to make coffee even without adding water, coffee, or a supply of electricity. The coffee maker secretly contains a self-replicating swarm of bio-nanites, which help to increase the density of neural connections within the brain. Mechanically, any character who drinks a cup of coffee from the machine has their INT permanently increased by +1, at the cost of a SAN check (0/1).</item>
        <item>A file containing documents and photos of a Japanese national named "Yasaka Hasta", who appears to be a young, blond male wearing pants, shoes, and a hooded sweatshirt - all yellow. There doesn\'t seem anything strange, though the documents (copies of official Japanese records) were marked as "Likely Faked" in red pen - notes by the investigator.\nFinal notes mention that the investigator was found insane, muttering "What a glorious form for the King".\nIf player character looking through the file seen the Yellow Sign or Hastur, they will lose SAN loss 1/1d6.\nA cardboard box approximately 6" x 8" x 4", sealed with standard packing tape. The box rattles if shaken. If opened, the box is found to contain the desiccated remains of a gray squirrel.</item>
        <item>1d6+2 tactical communication devices, similar to those used by the U.S. Secret Service. A speaker is placed into the left ear of an investigator, while an audio receiver is placed on the inside of either a watch/shirt sleeve. This device allows investigators to communicate with one another over the distance of 1 mile/1.6KM. Unfortunately, these devices are also possessed by the soul of a teenager, who will attempt (and fail) to seduce the PC\'s at the most inopportune time.</item>
        <item>A torn apart bullet-proof vest. While it once may have provided som protection to its wearer it is now a dark-stained mess with several large rips right through it.</item>
        <item>A white-on-mauve t-shirt reading in tasteful block print \'SOCIOPATH WORLD\'. It\'s in remarkably nice condition.</item>
        <item>A brown cardboard box labeled "Evidence, Van, Devil\'s Hill Estate." Inside the box are two half burnt candles, a pile of plastic dolls in various states of disrepair, and a cassette tape. The tape is a looped recording of a woman or child crying. The crying itself sounds fake.</item>
        <item>An Israeli civilian gas mask with biblical verses written on it. If a demon or otherwise unholy creature attacks a person in current contact with the mask, the attack dose one die less damage.</item>
        <item>A pair of jury-rigged stilts (made of 2x4s and wood scraps). The bottom portions are stained blue from some sort of acrid liquid.</item>
        <item>A collection of autopsy photos. The subjects are all women. Stains upon the photos glow under UV light.</item>
        <item>Scorched envelope containing a partially exposed glossy photograph of a man in a robe wearing a crown of large antlers, of a twelve point buck. The man\'s face is obscured by shadow except for the rim of one protruberant eye.</item>
        <item>A small cardboard box containing ten origami animals. A closer inspection reveals that they are all folded from $100 bills.</item>
        <item>Someone\'s taken the time to wallpaper the Green Box with pages from various Bibles. Their bindings and covers are carefully stacked at one side of the Box.</item>
        <item>Six used but clean suits of battledress uniforms in the old US Army "Woodland" pattern camouflage, complete with six kevlar helmets, six gas masks, six pairs of olive drab cloth gloves, and six olive drab load-bearing-equipment vests. The only identifying insignia on them are a circular patch on the left shoulder of each, of dull khaki cloth, showing a stylized Colt Peacemaker revolver logo in black, and, at the top, "MTF Σ 114" (the "Σ" appears to be the Greek letter sigma), and below, "GUNSLINGERS" That unit patch and designation will be wholly unfamiliar to any PC, even those recently or currently in the US military.</item>
        <item>A wooden box about six inches to a side and obviously of amateur make. The top is tightly fitted and requires some effort to open. If opened, the inside is lined with lead sheeting like that used in roofing. There are no labels or notes.?</item>
        <item>The mummified remains of a Delta Green cell which vanished in the late 1980s occupy the interior of this unit. All are in causal poses (seated at a card table reading a book, resting on a cot, etc.). Additionally, there are mummified remains of other animals in the green box-- a small dog (one of the agents pet?), a rat apparently in mid-gnaw on one of the agents, a bird which entered through a hole in one of the walls, etc. In fact, anything once living in the unit seems to have become somehow instantly mummified. Inside the pocket of one of the agents is a small, onyx amulet with the Yellow Sign emblazoned on it. (Whether or not the amulet is the cause is up to the keeper. Agents may not want to stick around to find out for certain, in any event.)</item>
        <item>The mummified severed hand of a small mammal, one finger extended. Field notes indicate it as no longer dangerous.</item>
        <item>When the investigators open the Green Box, they are confronted with a stereotypical time bomb (complete with genuine Semtex explosive) sitting on a crate right in front of them, whose almost cartoonishly large, glowing-green digital counter is somewhere between one and thirty seconds and going down. However, when it hits zero, it simply resets and counts down from thirty again; evidently this was somebody\'s idea of a practical joke.</item>
        <item>A dead man has been crucified to the wall of the Green Box.</item>
        <item>This is an USB-stick. It\'s orginaly black, but has faded due to what seems to be prolonged exposure to the sun. Small, reddish stains can be seen on the casing. If analysed, the stains are rust mixed with bird blood. On the stick, there\'s only one file, a short videoclip in high quality, showing a beautiful peacock wandering in a forest to the song "Ich Will", by Rammstein. If an agent dissassembles the stick after viewing the clip, there will be no electronic parts inside it, only a small amount of dirt.</item>
        <item>Glowsticks. So many glowsticks. Boxes upon boxes, pallets upon pallets of glowsticks. These must have been tens of thousands of dollars, could most likely illuminate five city blocks, and probably took a forklift to bring in. Lord knows why anyone would ever want this many glowsticks.</item>
        <item>A large suitcase containing several silver tubes and a thin folded metal-netting. To one of the tubes a cable is attached and then bifurcating into one grounded connector and one 10" iron spike. By screwing together the tubes, covering the resulting 4\'x4\'x4\' box in the metal netting and grounding it using the cable it is possible to create a small Faraday Cage large enough for a crouching human.</item>
        <item>A 1996 yearbook from a high school in Palo Alto, California. Someone has driven 144 roofing nails through the front cover of the yearbook, affixing the yearbook to the floor of the greenbox. If the agents somehow pry the yearbook loose and pull the nails out, they will find that each nail has been driven through the faces of the photographs of the underclass students.</item>
        <item>A VHS tape that smells distinctly of burning but displays no signs of damage. Approximately fifteen minutes remain on the tape where it was stopped without being rewound.</item>
        <item>A large Bible (King James edition) of the sort you\'d find in a bookcase in someone\'s home. The Bible has been hollowed out and contains only a stack of Polaroid instant photographs that appear to have been taken sometime in the mid-1980\'s. The photographs depict a boy and a girl in their early teens in several compromising positions. Even more disturbingly, both teens show unmistakable signs of the Insmouth Taint... -1/-2 SAN.</item>
        <item>Strange luminescent fungi grow along the walls of the Green Box. Anyone touching their pale flesh-like surfaces will get the feeling they are contracting and expanding, as if they are breathing ...</item>
        <item>An unnervingly large collection of tapeworms has been preserved in formaldehyde and placed in open-top fishbowls all around the Green Box. Every now and then, an investigator might see one of them twitch out of the corner of their eye.</item>
        <item>An altar has been constructed in the center of the Green Box, evidently dedicated to Burt Reynolds. Upon this altar is a holy book of sorts; if read, it appears that it was originally started as a bit of satire, but as the writer\'s mind slowly slipped it became more and more genuine.</item>
        <item>A half-empty jar of Vaseline and a spoon. A Post-it note is attached to the jar which reads \'It\'s delicious. Try some\'.</item>
        <item>A single silhouette target hangs from a clothesline about three-quarters into the Green Box, bearing disturbingly large, scorched holes, though no perceptible damage to whatever is behind it. Whatever weapon was used on the target had the dangerous side-effect of bathing the room in radiation; if the investigators spend more than fifteen minutes at the Green Box, they\'ll begin to develop symptoms of rad poisoning.</item>
        <item>3 foot tall porcelain doll wearing the clothing of one of the agents (female if possible). The eyes of the doll seem to follow the agent at all times. when nobody is looking the doll will disappear and the be behind the agent.</item>
        <item>In a shoe box lies a bunch of cassette tapes and yellowed notes written in a determined hand. The tapes are of popular songs by various artists such as Bob Dylan, The Clash, The Beatles, Elvis, Johnny Cash, Frank Sinatra and Britney Spears. The notes go into detailed analysis of how each song makes references to the Mythos. Up to the Keeper if the notes are accurate enough to invest any Cthulhu Mythos knowledge, or deduct any Sanity.</item>
        <item>A room filled with glass jars and bottles supended by fine cords from the ceiling. Each container is filled with a oily and murky liquid, with mishappen things hidden in its depths.</item>
        <item>A contemporary map of the Chicago Freight tunnels, printed on 11"x17" paper, folded in half and sealed in a large plastic bag. A convoluted route from Milwaukee &amp; Kenzie streets to Illinois and Wells streets is marked in a red felt-tip pen.</item>
        <item>A length of clothesline has been strung across the Green Box. Slung over it are two dead and hideously mutilated cats, their tails tied together. They appear to have fought each other to death.</item>
        <item>A sealed plastic box full of over the counter medicine and vitamin supplements with a handwritten inventory splattered with blood. There are also instructions to ONLY take them in a specific order, but no instructions as to under what conditions they should be taken. The consequences are up to the GM\'s discretion.</item>
        <item>A pack of Juicy Fruit chewing gums, with six sticks left. The sticks have been dosed with powderd LSD, which is not readily appearant unless the gum is perused. Licking the stick will also do teh trick.</item>
        <item>A small black and white photo of JFK wearing a business suit shaking hands with a "classic" grey alien. Something is written on the back: "seems legit...?"</item>
        <item>A single diffuser of liquid with a spray applicator with a post-it note: "Spray whole body (including eyes) and examine if anything turns purple. Warning Highly Toxic. If purple is detected it is imperative that you contact Alpha Cell, 3 uses remaining "</item>
        <item>Much of the back of the Green Box comprises an intricate and unsettling shrine to Santa Muerte, skeletal Mexican saint of the dead. A DNA or dental check on the skeleton itself (complete with rainbow robe, blunt scythe, and gaudy mitre) concludes it\'s the body of DEA intelligence research specialist Manuel Boaz, who went missing while on administrative leave in Missouri in 2008. Boaz was a Delta Green friendly - and A-Cell will be deeply interested in the recovery of his remains...</item>
        <item>A backpack filled with rope. When rope is removed from the pack, it seems to always have more inside it. Despite however much is drawn out, it always seems to be 120 feet worth.</item>
        <item>A cell phone inside of a small padded box. When the box is opened, the cell phone will start to ring. If the cell phone is picked up, opened and answered the user can hear the sound of ringing, opening and then mnore ringing that builds upon itself until it becomes the sound of thousands of echos upon itself. The phone will repeat anything the user says into it in the same manner.</item>
        <item>A copy of the game _ET: The Extra-Terrestrial_ for the Atari 2600. Closer examination of the game cartridge shows that the casing has been forced open and reclosed, with part of the label used to hold the halves of the plastic case together. If the agents open the cartridge they will find that someone has crudely hand soldered an extra chip (an EPROM) to the circuit board. This has ruined the game cartridge by frying the other PROM and singing parts of the circuit board. Enthusiastic agents probing the EPROM will find that it contains only zeroes.\nSomebody\'s seen too many bad spy movies.</item>
        <item>A comfortable Boston Red Socks hoodie. The inside of the hood has a perpetual and very strong smell of garlic.</item>
        <item>A cigarette holder with four expensive cigarettes.. Inside, on top of the cigarettes, is a note which reads: "J - Stay out of sight. Remember not to light three to a match. - J"</item>
        <item>A pair of boots finished with human skin.</item>
        <item>In the refrigerator of this Green Box there are several big glass jars containing what look to be partial and sometimes complete human brains in some kind of solution. Disturbingly, while you know that pathologists and biologists might store tissue samples in formaldehyde, if you open any of these jars they smell like vinegar and garlic. Oh, and most of the jars also have bay leaves and little hot peppers floating around in them along with the brains. The labels don\'t help your peace of mind, either. They have stickers on the lid that say "leftovers" and taped to the front of the refrigerator was a note that said "Take all you want but eat all you take. Love, G-Cell"</item>
        <item>Two perfectly identical Zebra statues. However, people looking at it instinctivly understand one is a white zebra with black stripes, and the other is a black zebra with white stripes.</item>
        <item>A full bucket of Kentucky Fried Chicken - strangely the chicken is still fresh and warm.</item>
        <item>There is a terrified young woman curled up at the back of the Green Box. Caucasian (ATTRACTIVE 11), early-twenties, 5\'3" tall and naked, she appears to be suffering from PTSD and is almost childlike in her actions and need for protection. She speaks no known language, does not seem to understand cultural norms, and has no name. She cannot be traced on any database.\nIf A-Cell is informed, or within 1D3 days otherwise, the agents will be ordered to bring her to a locale in New Mexico for "her own safety". There she will be executed by a Delta Green agent from another Cell. No explanation will be given.</item>
        <item>A large (12x8 inch) photograph of a high-school class. All faces except the teacher\'s have been punched through several times with some sharp instrument. The teacher\'s face has been lovingly cut away with a razorblade.</item>
        <item>An opened four-pack of 500ml cans of a high-caffeine energy drink, with three cans remaining.</item>
        <item>The package is contained within a resealable plastic bag and "watch out, these things will kill you" has been written on the outside in black marker. The cans themselves with within sell-by date and show no signs of tampering.\nIf someone drinks more than half of a can, they will have a moderate heart-attack 2d6 minutes later (which they should survive with medical attention and should die without). If someone drinks two or more cans back-to-back they will have an automatically-fatal heart-attack in 1d6 minutes.</item>
        <item>A small brown paper bag containing a dozen small audio cassettes - the kind you find in an answering machine or dictaphone. The cassettes are marked with dates in black pen, spanning most of June 1992 to May 1993. Listening to the tapes reveals that they are indeed from an answering machine - apparently belonging to one "Mrs. Hargrove". In between the calls from friends and family are long recordings of incessant, unintelligible chanting - much longer than what answering machines usually record.\nThroughout the 1993 tapes, the chanting can be heard in the background of all messages.</item>
        <item>The top half of a well-worn teddy bear, spattered with dried blood. At Keeper\'s discretion, 0/1 SAN loss unless PCs are VERY jaded.</item>
        <item>Every square-inch of the walls, floor and roof of the Green Box have at least one bloody finger-print on it. Checking it against the databases shows they belongs to a Marvin Quells, an FBI-agent who disappeared in 1997. The DNA of the blood is not Marvin\'s though. It matches Mary Roberts, an IRS-agent who also disappeared in 1997.</item>
        <item>A single gold bar with a WW2 era Nazi eagle stamped on the top</item>
        <item>This green box contains three hidden compartments, under the floor boards, in a heating duct in the ceiling, and in the wall behind a refrigerator, constructed years ago by a longtime DG agent suffering from severe paranoia. For each cache that an agent passes close to, give them one chance to find it at 1/10th of their Spot skill. Once one has been found, agents can search for the other two at full skill. For the contents of each cache roll up 10 supernatural items on this generator. The cache contains the one that you think is most likely to get your agents killed or destroy their sanity.</item>
        <item>A manilla envelope sealed with an "EVIDENCE" sticker. If the seal is broken, it contains a half-dozen passports to various countries, some of which no longer exist (East Germany, etc), all bearing the likeness of whoever unsealed the envelope.</item>
        <item>Every object in the Green Box, regardless of size, is arranged in precise rows, labelled, and outlined in chalk or tape to indicate its proper location. Whoever did this seems to be severely OCD, and would likely not appreciate their hard work to be upset by careless visitors.</item>
        <item>Chemturion model 3525 extended wear Protective Suit, plus external air supply. (Large size). Light blue suit containment suit, designed for working with extreme chemical and biological hazards. (Nerve agents, H5N1 influenza, plus whatever MJ12 and the Mi-Go have cooked up this month). There is an integral helmet which has a very large clear faceplate. There is also a barrel of decontaminant solution, used clean the suit before the operator gets out. It is designed to be usable for 4-8 hours at a stretch. There is also a manual on how to use the suit.</item>
        <item>When the door to the Green Box is opened, three fragmentation grenades fall from the top of the door and land at the investigators\' feet, their pins and safety spoons clearly missing. However, none of them explode; when the shock wears off, they notice a crumpled note also fell with the grenades:\"Stay on your toes, those could have been real. Be Seeing You, F Cell."</item>
        <item>A very large X-shaped structure, perhaps eight feet high and finished in slightly smudged black leather with brass rivets. Sturdy steel eyebolts and rings are attached at various locations around the edge of the structure, and appear to have seen quite a bit of use. A pile of worn black silk rope was tossed carelessly upon the base of the bondage device.</item>
        <item>A pack of clasical Tarot cards. If only three cards are dealt, the three will always be Death, The Hanged Man and The Tower.</item>
        <item>A man has been crucified to the wall of the Green Box. He is gagged and in pain, but definitely still alive...</item>
        <item>A collection of coroner reports, notes, and photos from the city the Green Box is located it, in a string-tied red accordion file. The reports relate the details of the deaths of numerous female strippers\' and one transsexual. The official cause of the deaths appears to be "defective" breast implants, but the unofficial, scrap paper notes end with one conclusion, "something was incubating in the implants, and when it hatched it hatched hungry." The file also contains an evidence bag with one bloody and shredded implant.</item>
        <item>A pair of high quality red digital binoculars. When held up to the eyes, an attractive red headed woman slowly begins stripping. Right before her top is removed, several black tentacles tear her limbs off (San loss 0/1).</item>
        <item>A box of moon rocks.</item>
        <item>A jumpsuit of a gray-black fabric. It is one-size-fits-all, and feels satiny to the touch. When worn, the profile seems more generic than before, as if it washed away distinguishing features. It does not cover or affect the wearer\'s face.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a soft piece of pale leather wrapped around six fire-hardened bamboo slivers. There is a faded tattoo (an eagle and the words "Semper Fi") visible in one corner of the leather piece. The slivers are approximately 3" long, very thin and needle-sharp. Some of them have brownish stains on the tips.</item>
        <item>A heavy steel case about 40 x 40 x 30 cm, with a top cover made of thick leaded glass. Inside you see a riveted steel plate from which emerge three human fingers . Occasionally, the fingers twitch. It cannot be opened.</item>
        <item>The inside of the Green Box door has several long claw marks, and parts of it is dented as if something has repeatedly smashed into it.</item>
        <item>Someone has made a tiny safe house at the back of the green box. It\'s basically a pair of large shipping crates, connected and left hollow. It sits in the corner with the wall and back of the storage unit providing protection for two corners. In front there are several sofas stacked up to proved camouflage and protection. On the side several sofas lie stacked. However, perceptive agents will notice they are arranged to make a tunnel large enough for someone to crawl down. At the end of this is a false side which can be removed. Inside is room enough for single person to curl up to sleep or sit. The crates have been lined with insulation to help defeat heat sensors. It has a small fan to keep the air clean, in fact looking behind the unit will show there is a small hose connecting outside or into the buildings ac system. There is also a tv hooked up to a small wireless camera outside the box. The camera is hidden in the light fixtures or in an emergency exit sign. Whether or not this works is up to you. However, someone put a lot of effort into their little pillow fort.</item>
        <item>A set of two tesla coils and a safety chamber. The cell assembled these as protection from beings that exist in higher dimensions. Whether or not it works is up to the GM.</item>
        <item>One broken engine block to an unrecognized vehicle. It is far too heavy to move, and no obvious signs show how the engine ended up here. Players who investigate can find a VIN number printed on one of the parts. Further tracing reveals this engine belonged to the limo used by the Canadian Prime Minister.</item>
        <item>A 10 pound sack of 1930s quarters, they appear perfectly ordinary. However no matter what, they will always land heads, never tails, ever. and never by force, always by pure circumstance.</item>
        <item>Tape from a number of VHS cassettes has been strung around the Green Box, looping around the items and tacked to the ceiling and floor like a spider\'s web.</item>
        <item>A large mural of a rather canine looking Joseph Stalin has been painted on the Green Box\'s wall.</item>
        <item>A huge volume of soil in a closed container. Notes indicate that the earth most likely contains the ashes of Hitler, for future use in a resurrection ritual and some sort of respect.</item>
        <item>A very long leather holdall of English manufacture dating back to the 1920\'s it appears well worn, but otherwise in good condition. Inside is a 2008 Marlin 336 lever-action rifle chambered for .338 Marlin express rounds, three jacketed soft point rounds are in the magazine and one in the chamber, and elasticated butt cuff holds another five. There is also a hand made leather belt rig with an M56 Canteen, a ka-bar fighting knife and a holster for a M1917 revolver with three ammunition pouches. The revolver, manufactured during World War One is fully loaded with FMJ rounds, two of the pouches hold two half-moon clips with similar loads, while the third is empty. The revolver appears to have been recently fired. Also present is a set of Vietnam era tiger stripe fatigues, including a boonie hat. The fatigues appear to have been custom fitted for a tall athletically built woman. A pair of \'nam era jungle boots, size eight, are also present. All of the above items appear brand new. The only item which doesn\'t is a sheet of writing paper which if examined closely appears to be over ninety years old, written on it in neat femmine script are the words, "Stephen, I never stopped loving you. Mary."</item>
        <item>A framed, dust-coated poster-sized black and white photograph of a tall, gangling man in half profile looming over a misshapen dwarf against a featureless background of white and gray. Both men are wearing stiff suits and Homburgs; the freakishly proportioned thin man, whose long fingers appear to possess too many joints and whose slim neck seems too long by a vertebrae or two, is wearing rimless black-lensed glasses while the dwarf is grinning at the camera through a long, forked beard. The photo was likely shot during the Depression era going by the striations and patina of composition, although identification is difficult due to age and yellowing. "R. &amp; friend" is scribbled in a corner.</item>
        <item>A battered cardbox box full of cheap plastic Guy Fawkes masks.</item>
        <item>A brown coin envelope containing a U.S. Kennedy half-dollar coin minted in 1968. The edge of the coin has been precisely notched with three 3mm wide by 2mm deep scores. The back envelope has a list of four typed names. The names correspond to three Secret Service agents who were gunned down on April 4, 1969. The fourth name is of a retired Secret Service agent who lives on a parcel of land near Sandspring, California (a ghost town on the extreme northern end of Death Valley.)</item>
        <item>A hydraulic arm from a garbage truck has been installed in the center of the Green Box\'s floor; it is controlled by a joystick assembly wired to the wall.\nIt doesn\'t seem to have any clear purpose.</item>
        <item>Two plastic buckets with lids containing what first appears to be grayish confetti with some minor pieces of trash in it. On the lids are written "Agent Jonas" and "Agent Jay". A closer inspection reveals that the "confetti" is not made from paper but some other substance, and the trash seems to be things you may sweep up from a sidewalk. A lab test will show that the "confetti" is freeze-dried and flaked human flesh.</item>
        <item>In the corner of the Green box sits a professionally made refrigeration unit, cooled by liquid helium. The unit is only large enough to store a human head inside of it, which is exactly what is currently in storage. The head is from a while male in his late 30\'s. Even frozen the head gives off odd feelings of dread. It would be best for everyone if it remained inside the freezer.</item>
        <item>An old cardboard box with the name of a 1920s-era Boston Gunsmith on it. Inside are 18 hand loaded 12-gauge shotgun shells which are loaded with rocksalt. The box has room for 20.</item>
        <item>Thirteen sets of Hall and Rees Submarine escape apparatus, all fully functional in spite of dating back to 1907. They have, however, all been sprayed florescent yellow. A note placed nearby says, "Instant minions."</item>
        <item>The preserved, severed paw of a bear. The type cannot be easily determined, as it is larger than any bear\'s paw has any right to be. A small person could sit in it comfortably.</item>
        <item>An internal computer hard-drive with a red sticker on it that says "Do NOT connect!". If it is connected to any kind of Linux/Unix controlled hardware a mimetic cryptovirus undetectable by any current anti-virus software will spread from the hard-drive and turn all data on the hardware to gibberish.</item>
        <item>6 kilos of prepared raw meat. Despite the Green Box having been untended for who-knows-how-long, the meat is still fresh and cooler than room temperature.</item>
        <item>The species of meat is left up to the Keeper\'s imagination...</item>
        <item>Collection of 37 dried human ears (all left) on a string necklace.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag, marked "Skoptsi 980722-0023-A", containing the dried up remains of a male genitalia.</item>
        <item>A shrink-wrapped case of Spam from 1997. 24 12oz cans.</item>
        <item>A cadavre of a cow turned all grey (as if drained of "life") with a note saying: Slightly radioactive. Don\'t eat.</item>
        <item>A large, psychotic baboon has apparently broken out of a cage within the Green Box, and violently assaults the first person to walk into it.\nThe animal is merely infected with rabies, but given the setting the Keeper is free to allow the players whatever wild speculation may come to them.</item>
        <item>When the Agents enter the green box, they find a fully-functioning 40-gallon aquarium. The aquarium contains everything it needs, except for fish. A note is taped to the side of it that says "Do Not Disturb. We\'ll be back to pick it up when we have the stuff to drain the water. E Cell." (This note stays even if the Agents are E Cell) In the bottom of the tank are several cartoonish statues of Mythos creatures or entities, such as Cthulhu, Deep Ones or Shoggoths.</item>
        <item>A UNMIL ID card, covered in long dried smears of blood. It belongs to one Yussef Motahar, a Pakistan Army lieutenant reported missing from UN peacekeeping duties in Northern Liberia during 2002.</item>
        <item>A wooden box containing three dozen small plastic animals. Whenever the contents are out of view, the next time they are looked at they will all be facing in different directions than they were initially. A post-it note attached to the top reads "DO NOT TOUCH. H."</item>
        <item>A large sealed jar containing a human heart preserved in formalin. A closer examination reveals that the arteries were torn off rather than cut. A handwritten note attached to the jar says: "Agent Victor".</item>
        <item>Seven plastic squeeze bottles filled with various lubricants. The bottles always appear to be nearly empty, no matter how much lubricant is added to them, but never actually run out.</item>
        <item>All corners of the green box are full of spray-on packing foam, and there is a lingering smell of spoiled milk in the air. There are several items of furniture that appear to have been smashed with a sledgehammer and burned, but it looks as if subsequent visitors to the box have tried to clean away some of the mess. A successful Cthulhu Mythos roll, or simply having experience with such things may let an investigator know that someone has attempted to proof the box against a Hound of Tindalos. Whether they succeeded or not is unclear.</item>
        <item>A 36″x24″x3″ red velvet sheet cake with butter-pecan icing. A 3-D picture of the agents has been applied with red icing and micro nozzle applicators modded to a dot matrix printer.</item>
        <item>A shoebox filled to the brim with golden brown fortune cookies. If cracked open, every single fortune reads: "SAY HAVE YOU SEEN THE YELLOW SIGN?"</item>
        <item>A two foot diameter circular sawmill blade. Strange metallic crystals cover one third of the blade, deforming part of its surface, seemingly growing out of it. Anyone examining it for some time will notice how the light refracts strangely around the crystals, making small parts of the surface seemingly disappear now and then.</item>
        <item>A compact picnic-bag containing a nice plate, fork, knife and spoon, as well as a crystal wineglass. There is also place for a small wine-bottle, but that is occupied by a battery-powered surgical cranium saw.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a green sock-puppet with shiny black button-eyes. There are several dark stains on it.</item>
        <item>A chair set towards the door, with a small table next to it. On the table there is an ash tray with several cigarettes ashed out. One is still smoking and appears to have been hastily put out. There is no other exit to the room.</item>
        <item>An AN/VSS-3 battlefield searchlight and control box with power supply. Produces a 150 million candlepower output beam in infrared or visible light.</item>
        <item>A large teddy bear (3 1/2 feet in height) that is fully done up in bondage gear. From the collar dangles a small tag with the letter \'T\' engraved on it.</item>
        <item>You find a roughly 9\' pike standing up in a brass base. On the pike is a severed head of a youngish man, though it\'s hard to tell due to it being rather mummified and slumped in a frightening, semi-decayed position. 1/1D4+1 Sanity Loss to view for the first time. Forensic analysis always comes up inconclusive, however a best guess is that the unfortunate individual died anywhere from 6 months to 12 years ago. The pike is modern make, in a traditional European style. However background checks reveal that it is probably of Indian manufacture for the reenactor community.</item>
        <item>A small matchbox filled with childrens milk teeth. Written across the box it says: "BAIT".</item>
        <item>A glass jar filled with preserved human eye balls.</item>
        <item>A crude bone flute made from a very long, human-like femur bone. A successful archeology role will reveal the archaic features of a previously unknown proto-human. Strangely, the finger holes are spread unevenly, and are too far apart for modern human hands. Holding it makes the agent hear strange atonal melodies just at the edge of hearing; they seem to be coming from the unnatural and rapidly deepening nearby shadows...</item>
        <item>One DVD-R containing many hours of Japanese hentai pornography. The audio content has been replaced a looped section of a lecture (in English) about marine mammals.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing five bulbs of garlic, a garlic-crusher, an empty test tube and a syringe.</item>
        <item>A shoe box holding 41 ivory cubes, on each face of the cube is a human face, screaming silently, frozen open with ridges of ivory stretching off to the sides, as if it were vacuum packed in plastic. A paper taped to the inside has, written on it, "Remains" and 41 dates.</item>
        <item>A vinyl record of "Wes Montgomery\'s Greatest Hits". Any investigators who play this record are greeted by the complete audio recording of the black box recovered from American Airlines Flight 77, which infamously crashed into the Pentagon on September 11th, 2001. The Keeper should modify the contents of the recording to best suit the adventure.</item>
        <item>A wedding dress, slightly aged, in a clear dress bag laid gently on top of one of the boxes. It is the exact size and design as one belonging to either one of the agents or their significant others.</item>
        <item>There\'s a weird static charge built up in the Green Box, resulting in itchiness, frizzy hair and the odd spark. Anyone touching anything metal grounds the charge - and suffers 2D6 in electrocution damage for their troubles.\nA Know or Electrical roll by an observant agent should work out how to stop this before it happens.</item>
        <item>A small white cardboard box (6"x3"x3") inside of which four used condoms all tightly knotted, one torn open. Holding the condoms upto the light a small thin worm (1") can be seen swiming in the contents. A small postit note has been stuck to the inside of the box it reads "sample collected from subject SHARON under duress. Open in BSL2 (Biosafety Level Containment Level 2) conditions or better.</item>
        <item>There\'s a trapdoor in the Green Box\'s floor with half-a-dozen heavy bolts keeping it shut tight. Opening it uncovers a set of stairs leading into a basement below...</item>
        <item>Everything in the Green Box has been pushed to the back of the room and piled haphazardly to free up as much space as possible. Someone broke into the Green Box in recent memory (not longer than three or four months ago) and set up a compact, very efficient meth lab on a couple of folding card tables. All of the raw materials and spare equipment to cook up batch after batch of bathtub crank are neatly stacked near the door. The burglars don\'t seem to have stolen anything (if the Keeper is feeling merciful) but also don\'t seem to have been polite enough to leave you any of the meth they made.</item>
        <item>A blank DVD box with a bright yellow post-it note stuck between the cover layers is found. On the note is the following writing:</item>
        <item>"Video Evidence-The Heidelberg Case (DGC#/tt0187696) Possible connection with recent incidents in Bratislava?"\nIf the case is opened an unmarked blank DVD is found. Upon closer inspection the disk is burnt and potentially contains information.If the disk is played on a computer or DVD player a movie file automatically plays.\nThe movie file starts off with what looks to be a brightly lit professionally maintained forensic/autopsy room, complete with stainless steel furnishings. Characters who have been through medical school will recognize that it\'s a medical school examination and training theater. The camera is fixated on one table in particular. As the video continues two individuals in full modern surgical gear, who\'s identities are obscured by masks and eyewear, bring in a cadaver from off camera and begin to prep it for dissection. The individuals seem calm, rational and in control of their actions in a manor that seems to be of a standard medical study procedure. Not much is said during the preparation however a keen ear will detect that on occasion German is spoken. Characters who know German will be able to identify that anything said is in relation to the procedure and gathering related data. To characters who went through medical school, this seems like much the same they had to deal with back in the day, except something is not right; however they can\'t put their finger on what is wrong. As the video progresses one of the individuals goes off camera and turns on some music to work by. The music is extremely upbeat and very positive; a combination of jazz style tunes and light vocals. In an odd way the music adds a very creepy factor to the setting. After returning, both individuals begin to dissect the cadaver. People without medical backgrounds or experience with dead people will automatically make a 0/1D4 Sanity roll when the realization that this is an actual procedure and not a staged setup sets in, People with a medical background are fine, however something continues to be not right. As the procedure goes into a more in depth study, the characters with a medical background will begin to see what is wrong. The "cadaver" is not behaving like a dead person should. There are several IVs stuck in the body, and odd movements can be seen. As the body is opened up and organs removed and examined methodically the true horror hits everyone watching. The "cadaver" is actually a living victim! To top it off, the individuals performing the operation are taking detailed notes and data as to how the victim\'s body is functioning while slowly continuing the brutal procedure in a cold, calculated scientific manor. At this point everyone watching the video takes 2/1D10 sanity roll as the poor victim is vivisected and the subject of a gruesome living study. The horror culminates with the victim slowly waking up and realizing his situation. The combination of extreme torture, upbeat music, cold scientific methodical research, and hapless victim unable to do anything culminates in a painful scream of fear that casuses all watching the video to take a further 3/1D10 sanity roll. Promptly one of the torturers tapes the victim\'s mouth shut and proceeds at their heinous chore. The victim is awake in panic a good 10 minutes as he is slowly carved up and studied methodically, scientifically, and with no remorse. Mercifully the video ends before the final moments of death in a sudden blaze of white noise. However the horror of what has been seen cannot be forgotten easily.</item>
        <item>A pair of black leather gloves - with 6 fingers.</item>
        <item>A burned CD of Reverend D.C. Rice\'s "Complete Recorded Works in Chronological Order (1928-1930)" The CD is sleeved in a handmade duct-taped and corrugated cardboard case with a crude illustration of an angel stepping on a the neck of a red cartoon devil. The case is a little too well crafted and precious; it\'s more the kind of "authentic" thing a Williamsburg hipster would counterfeit as ironic homage. The music compilation contains all 20 known recorded performances from the Rev. D.C. Rice, an impassioned country-blues gospel singer. These are some of the finest blues-gospel recordings of their era. In red grease pen on the back of the case is written: "Triangle Green, The Lord knows you\'ve done as well as you can. Listen to the Reverend and take comfort from the protection of His rod and His staff. You may rest easy at the end of your day to the sound of \'On the Battlefield for my Lord.\'In Christ, D."</item>
        <item>The Green Box is strewn with empty bottles of mineral water, and a lot of the items are damp - as if someone has been through and "baptized" them...</item>
        <item>a 5 1/4 inch BASF diskette in a thin clear plastic bag. There is a small adhesive label on the diskette cover. Written on the label in dark blue fountain pen ink are \'3/16/86\' and \'FWSF - master\'. If the disc is loaded into a computer a strange, swirling abstract pattern will instantly appear on the screen. The pattern has an inexplicably horrifying quality; anyone viewing it for the merest instant will lose 1-3 SAN. The pattern will run for 10 seconds only; the computer will then shut down. All data on the machine\'s hard drive will be corrupted beyond recovery. The hard drive itself will subsequently be found to be unusable, and beyond repair.</item>
        <item>Splotched with dried blood, a lilac coloured envelope has been tidily opened. It\'s addressed to 1375 May Avenue, Atlanta, GA, 30316 and postmarked 2.13.2008. There is no return address. Inside is a Valentine\'s Day card. Inside the card are 13 local press clippings of goats born in 2007 with notable deformities in Georgia. Each clipping has an address penned at the top; a few have Polaroid photos of the kids stapled to the clipping.</item>
        <item>Drywipe marker board with an Elementary Sudoku grid annotated and overlaid on both transparent map of Amsterdam\'s redlight district &amp; an abstract of the European Internet.</item>
        <item>Six cans, each containing six ounces of liquid, ala canned broth. The labels have been taken off, but a sticky-note on each says the same thing.\n"Special Rations".\nThese cans can easily be opened thanks to a pop top, and contain a liquid that looks a lot like beef broth, with nothing else in it. Drinking this mixture provides someone with 500 calories, and 1/3rd of their daily required vitamins and nutrients. The taste differs depending on who eats it, but can be summed up as: The best flavor in the world. Real food kind of sucks compared to this liquid.</item>
        <item>A small pile of bent, misshapen crowbars. Closer examination suggest that they must have been used by an impossibly strong person against an impossibly strong object, in which the crowbar was the weakest link in the circumstances.</item>
        <item>A small unmarked carboard box. Inside are 500 grams of lab-grade sulphur (in a bottle marked "Carolina Scientific"), potassium nitrate (in a similar container), and a plastic jar from the "American Herbals Co." labled "Franincense/Olibanum". Also inside is a porcelain mortal and pestle.</item>
        <item>A small handfull of grayish rocks. A successful Know roll will reveal them to be pieces of meteoric iron ore.</item>
        <item>A small worn, and with dark red stains, leather bag, tied shut by leather strings. it\'s hiding some kind of content, as it\'s quite full, which feels like perhaps small smooth pebbles. when opened and examined it will show to contain teeth, childrens teeth, a rather large quantity of them, smooth, fine, childrens (primary, deciduous, \'fall\', \'milk\') teeth, all in quite perfect condition.</item>
        <item>A blue Coleman cooler, duct-taped shut. Inside are a jumble of commerical freezer-packs (now all room temperature) and a foul-smelling alkaline sludge. A few human teeth are scattered about inside as well. The cooler\'s interior is scored by several deep scratches.</item>
        <item>A ziplock bag willed with gold dental fillings.</item>
        <item>12 liters of blood in mason jars. Some of the jars are still warm.</item>
        <item>A well-thumbed November 1982 issue of Reader\'s Digest Magazine, Cover has been defaced by some sort of acid.</item>
        <item>A cigar box containing a straight razor and several polaroids of a pair of teens dressed for prom.</item>
        <item>A unicycle wrapped in Christmas lights stands erect in the center of the Green Box, flashing gaudily until unplugged. A taped-on note claims it is "magic", but does not expound on this theory; in reality it has no characteristics that differentiate it from any other Christmas-light-wrapped unicycles the PCs may encounter.</item>
        <item>A greenish soapstone statue. Statue depicts a humanoid being with a bulbous, octopus-like head, a wreathe of tentacles around the mouth, and bat-like wings kneeling on a plinth. The being\'s hands are on its knees, and it seems to have a malevolent expression. The statue is about 10 cm. high.</item>
        <item>A blood stained cardboard folder labeled \'Leak?\'. Contents: (1) A DVD of "Underworld: Evolution", with the words \'NRO-Delta got whacked!\' written on the cover in black marker. (2) An 100 page typed document, which discusses similarities between certain events in the film and a failed NRO-Delta operation code-named NEPTUNE FLASH which took place \'somewhere in the Balkans\'. The report concludes that the similarities are pure coincidence and recommends no further action. Neither author or recipient are identified.</item>
        <item>An acoustic guitar, with blood-stains on the strings at the spots where a person would place their hands, as if the person who used it had played it until their fingers bled.</item>
        <item>Box with 10 rounds of .50 caliber Raufoss Mk 211 ammunition with an elder symbol on the box.</item>
        <item>A stuffed black cat</item>
        <item>One 16 oz. shampoo bottle with the words "Holy Water" scrawled on it in black paint pen. The bottle is about 1/2 full.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a pair of blood spattered clogs with mysterious runes carved into their soles.</item>
        <item>What appears to be a mock-up of an advanced model of prosthetic hand. Even a cursory examination shows that this is an artist\'s model and not made to actually function, but the PCs can swear they see it twitch or move in the corner of their eye, only for it to be exactly as the left it when they look.</item>
        <item>An issue of Action Comics #1, mint new expect for a large sticker "Property of the Anhenherbe\'s library" glued on the cover.</item>
        <item>Everything inside have been painted blue, the same hue of blue, eveything is blue</item>
        <item>A plastic bin. Taped to the top is a sheet of notebook paper saying "We\'re in a hurry. Could the next person please burn this stuff? DO NOT READ!" in a woman\'s handwriting. The bin holds a US Postal Service bag containing thousands of envelopes bearing the return address "Richmond-American Awards Company" and the addresses of a random assortment of people. They are all unopened. If examind the contents appear to be a standard form-letter offering a cash prize (of indeterminable size) if the reader calls a certain telephone number. Interspersed into the regular text are short strange sentences from some occult text. It mentions the "faceless devourer". (At the Keeper\'s discretion the text is from Vol. 12 of the Revelations of Glaaki.)</item>
        <item>A black and white photograph taken some time ago. It shows a shirtless, muscular bald man holding a weapon, as if he was hunting for something. On his chest a star-shaped symbol. Those with knowledge of the Mythos would know it to be the Elder Sign.</item>
        <item>A strange glowing orb that makes quiet beeping sound at any person in the green box. If someone knows binary code they can speak to the orb who\'s name is odium and may fallow the group because the box is vary weird odium baleves herself to be human.</item>
        <item>A large cardboard packing box filled with used tubes of lip balm from seemingly every manufacturer. A pad of graph paper plots some sort of test of each tube. Exactly what was being tested and which tube performed the best is impossible to determine (and least in part due to extensive blood stains and seemingly random scribbles across the face of each chart.)</item>
        <item>A group of three standard-issue FBI kevlar vests, all three of which have been thoroughly ruined.\nEach vest clearly has scorch marks on the outside of it, and one has been penetrated by what looks like high-powered rifle rounds. If one were to examine the inside of that vest, they would find that it was soaked in blood at one point. Another vest looks fine from the front, but the back has been partially shredded, it looks like by long pieces of metal. The last vest is covered in a layer of sand and rock dust, and has multiple scores where it absorbed the impact of bullets.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing the complete skin of a human male. A forensic investigation indicates he was a caucasian in his thirties with brown hair, and the skin was removed while he was still alive using some sort of very thin and sharp blade. A DNA test give no matches in the databases.</item>
        <item>A DVD of three hours of confocal laser scanning microscope video. The high magnification scans seem to be of various tissue types and longitudinal cross sections of some very irregular cells. At the very end there?s a two second flash of a thing on a gurney in a well lit surgical theater.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>