<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="green_box_supernatural_weapons">
        <item>An M2 Carbine with a mounted M3 infrared sniper scope and backpack carrier for the scope\'s power source. Included are two 30 round magazines, a 50 round box of 30 carbine ammo, a flat metal box, and a yellowed piece of paper.\nInside the metal box is a filter designed to clamp over the IR spotlight part of the scope. The filter appears to be an iridescent blue piece of glass set in a plastic ring. However, touching the filter reveals it to be a yielding, gel-like material. Anyone who touches the filter with bare skin for more than a few seconds will experience powerful waves of nausea. Prolonged exposure will cause the handler to be prostrated with vomiting and chills. Scientific examination of the filter will reveal nothing noteworthy about the filter\'s properties or place of origin.\nThe piece of paper is dated May 1951 and is a typewritten set of instructions for the weapon It indicates that the filtered spotlight is the primary means of damage against the subjects [subjects are GM discretion] but burst-fire from the rifle is the most effective means of compounding lethality and producing fatal injury. Furthermore, it is stated that the filter will not affect the scope\'s low-light vision capacity, but reduces its accuracy to inside 100 meters.\nBeneath the typed instructions is a nearly illegible hand-written annotation: "Warning: This weapon\'s receiver may be faulty. Sustained automatic fire could potentially damage the carbine\'s ability to fire, or cause an open-breach explosion. D. - November 3, 1970."</item>
        <item>A large police issue evidence bag containing a pair of iron Tekko-Kagi hand claws which have been chained together using two pairs of handcuffs. The claws are covered in dried blood. [Anyone removing the handcuffs and putting on the hand claws must succeed with a POW vs POW 16 roll or go berserk, attacking the nearest living persons until the claws are removed or 1d6 victims have been killed. The claws do 1d6 damage and the wearer gets two attacks each round.]</item>
        <item>A lead pipe with strange symbols burnt into the sides. Anyone hit in the head by the pipe (no matter how lightly) will die from a brain tumor within a year, so long as nothing else kills them first,</item>
        <item>Two small boxes of the type used to hold hand-loaded, match-grade ammunition. One contains 20 .308win rounds, and the other, 12 .50BMG rounds. The bullets in each are painted with a fine, intricate scrawl of interlocking symbols that cannot be rubbed or scraped off.\nAttempts to closely examine the symbols result in the examiner losing 15 minutes of time, (0/1 insanity if they notice) after which the scrutinized rounds will have returned to the boxes of their own accord, re-assembling themselves to do so if necessary. Possible improved function against unusual threats is left to the Keeper\'s discretion.</item>
        <item>A dagger made of a metal of an unusually green hue. Can be used to damage non-corporal beings, ie. ghosts.</item>
        <item>A wooden harpoon with a wrought iron head, of the type in use in the 1860s whaling industry. Still in excellent condition, it is perfectly normal except when it is within fifty feet of a Deep One, when it begins to vibrate. Should the wielder attack a Deep One with it the harpoon unerringly misses.</item>
        <item>Inside a foam-lined gun case is a Desert Tactical Arms SRS chambered in .338 Lapua Magnum. Attached to the top of the weapon is a black box which looks like some kind of advanced electronic sight, except the front of it has no opening. Looking through the scope, however, reveals a black, shadowy landscape where living things are illuminated by some kind of inner light. Anyone who knows anything about the concept of Auras or Aura reading might call it an "Aurascope"\nInanimate objects are nothing but dark outlines, with living beings being highlighted by a unique colored glow. Plants or fungi radiate various shades of green. Native Earth creatures glow blue, with humans, and oddly enough dolphins, if anyone cares to check, glowing the brightest, an almost electric blue color. Alien creatures, such as Mi-go or Greys have a pinkish, almost violet color. Summoned mythos creatures, like Byakhee glow bright red, and humans tainted by the Mythos (Such as Cultists or Sorcerers) have a sickly, yellow-green color. Keepers may also give other entities not mentioned specific colors of auras. Looking at something that doesn\'t have a normal Green or Blue Aura for the first time costs 1/1d4 SAN. The scope normally provides a view of the area of approximate dimensions of the space you can see with one eye, but has a dial on the side which can be used to increase the zoom up to x10. The Aurascope can be removed from the SRS with some tools, and placed on a different gun, though the using it on any other weapon incurs a 10% penalty to the user\'s skill, for some reason. The box itself can even be disassembled with a screwdriver, which reveals it to be nothing more than a cheap hard plastic casing for a series of crystal lenses of various sizes and materials. It can be put back together and will function, so long as all the components end up in exactly the same place. The design cannot be copied however, and even perfectly mimicking the size and substance of the crystal lenses will produce no results. In addition to being useful for finding non-humans, any firearm equipped with the Aurascope gains an interesting property. The bullets coming out of the gun, while not having their ability to harm expanded in any way, will penetrate any mundane or magical defenses the target has, striking them directly. Creatures which are intrinsicly immune to mundane weapons are still unharmed.</item>
        <item>A single shot .22 derringer, about the size of ones palm. Covered in strange symbols, the gun will fire normally. however, the user will be instantly killed, while the one hit with the bullet will go through the pain, but take no damage. The Shooter\'s Autopsy will find the .22 bullet located wherever the bullet hit the victim. 0-1d6 sanloss</item>
        <item>A brown cloth which covers a long spear. The spear is long, and barbed, with runes etched along the shaft and blade which glow with faint violet light. Analysis of the weapon shows it appears to be made from bone, possibly of a fish, but no species of fish are large enough to make the spear from. A History or Occult check should draw comparisons to Cu Chulainn\'s Gae Bolg, Odin\'s Gungir, and the Lance of Longinus.\nWhen wielded, the spear will always unerringly strike the heart of the target, reversing causality (It creates an "effect" then changes reality to find the "cause"), where it deals 1d10+DB damage, ignoring all forms of defense or armor. Then, on half DEX, the wielder may rip the spear out of the target, using the barbs, for an additional 1d6 damage. Each use of the spear costs the wielder 1d6 Magic Points. The spear can only harm creatures with hearts, or similar organs. 1/1d6 SAN once its effect is realized. 0/1 SAN to see the spear make a particularly mind-boggling strike.</item>
        <item>A 1938-vintage Mosin-Nagant M91/30 rifle, mounted with a telescopic scope. Any person seen through this scope will be perceived as dying horribly, torn apart by machine-gun fire, slowly being crushed to death by a fallen statue, screaming in terror while cradling their exposed intestines, and the like, and all the while a voice seemingly belonging to the rifle\'s first owner soliloquizes about the horrors he saw at Stalingrad. The shooter feels an intense urge to put the person in the crosshairs out of their misery with the rifle.\n1/1d6 SAN loss when seen for the first time, and 0/1 SAN loss when used again. A note on the inside of the rifle case indicate it is infested with several human, and one distinctly non-human, spectral presences.\nHowever, use of the scope doubles one\'s impale chance, from 20% of skill to 40% of skill, if one speaks Russian, due to the whispering spirit of the Soviet sniper choosing to serve as a spotter in battle.</item>
        <item>A rusty, unidentifiable revolving grenade launcher similar in design to the Milkor MGL, though apparently constructed sometime near the turn of the 20th century. It holds five large brass-cased grenades containing the Powder of Ibn Ghazi. Once the rounds are fired, they are almost impossible to reproduce due to both the unique design and the esoteric payload.</item>
        <item>A Roman lance, carbon dated to about ~28BC.\nHas been demonstrated to penetrate all known forms of armor, including steel, ceramic, composite (chobham-type), carbide nanoweave and [REDACTED]. Use on living subjects results in immediate and apparently irrevocable death.\nMost individuals in close proximity to the object report feelings of dread and a low hum emanating from the object, which has not been corroborated by sensor data.</item>
        <item>A metal baseball bat that has been covered in eldritch symbols, including an elder sign on the head. Does 2d6 damage to supernatural enemies, but lowers dexterity by 1.</item>
        <item>A sub-machine gun similar to the MP-40, stamped with the Nazi war eagle on both sides. However, instead of a normal 32-round rectangular magazine, there is a bizarre mass that twists back upon itself almost like a Klein bottle in ways that should be geometrically impossible; 1/1d4 SAN loss upon first seeing the weapon.\nThe multi-dimensional magazine essentially never runs out of ammunition, but costs the user 1/1d2 SAN after they fire 1d100+20 bullets and realize it has yet to run out.\nUnfortunately, this was only possible by cutting a deal with inhuman allies; whenever this weapon is fired in anger, a Star Vampire will arrive 1d6 rounds later, hostile to all parties. A note hinting at this is taped to the weapon, scrawled in German.</item>
        <item>An obsidian knife, all of one piece with the handle wrapped in leather and all placed into a canvas bag tied with a piece of string. Old stains cover the blade, which is of average sharpness for a blade of its type. If used against another creature of human size or smaller, however, match the wielder\'s POW against the target\'s. If the wielder wins, all defensive actions taken by the target against the knife (and only the knife) are at half normal strength. If the target wins, all offensive actions by the wielder using the knife are at half-normal strength. This penalty remains in place until either the wielder or the target changes their POW score, in which case a reroll occurs. Finally, if the knife is used to kill a sapient being, the wielder gains a point of POW, to a max of 25.</item>
        <item>One silver .38 special round engraved with twisting symbols. If fired it will hit its target and do double damage.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a human femur intricately carved with squiggly runes. (A successful Mythos-roll will identify a tenuous connection in the runes to Yog-Sothoth) The Bone feels heavier than it should be and turns out to be of approximately the same hardness as titanium. Striking a living creature will shatter any bone in the area closest to the hit (in reality a small amount of bone-marrow explosively vaporizes), dealing 3d6 damage (in addition to any STR bonus. Armor is ignored and Impales are applicable as bone-splinters cut into nearby organs). The Bone also extracts 2 MP from its holder each time this effect occurs. If the bone is used to strike a killing blow it instead extracts all the victim\'s MPs, using them to strengthen the bones of its wielder (increase his Hit Points with 1), as long as he is no more than 10 feet from the Bone. This effect is cumulative with further kills. If the Bone is ever more than 10 feet from a wielder whose Hit Points have been increased in this way TWICE the amount of gained Hit Points are permanently removed as his bones turn brittle like glass. Regaining the Bone will not return these Hit Points.</item>
        <item>A talwar sword of Afghan manufacture, whose hilt glows faintly with a blood-red aura. Taking up this sword in anger creates a psychological, and perhaps even physiological, change in the user. The user slowly becomes obsessed with revenge against a specific enemy (real or perceived), and forgoes all normal human needs as he or she hunts down this individual; exhaustion, starvation, dehydration, disease, hypothermia, blood loss, etc. seem to have no effect on the wielder, and he or she is spurred on by inhuman rage in this vendetta, ignoring all but the most lethal or disabling of wounds.\nHowever, once the enemy has been slain (invariably with the sword, it seems absurd to the wielder to use any other weapon), all of these ailments crash down all at once, probably lethally.</item>
        <item>A Ruger P-85 9mm semi-automatic pistol inside a wad of greasy McDonalds burger wrappers. Examination reveals the magazine is sealed into the gun and there is no ejection port, but the pistol has a limitless amount of ammunition. However, each trigger pull costs the shooter 0/1 Sanity loss.</item>
        <item>A highly polished Colt Peacemaker revolver which wouldn\'t look out of place in the hands of a Western movie protagonist. Like a Western protagonist\'s gun, it will seemingly move of its own accord and aim itself for any difficult trick-shots, such as shooting a gun out of an enemy\'s hands or severing a hangman\'s rope.\n0/1d2 to observe this tendency enough to rule out statistical anomalies, and 1/1d6 to feel it literally twist itself about in the shooter\'s hand.</item>
        <item>A large (7") curved knife with a bone handle of modern manufacture in a Denver Police Department evidence bag. If touched, the knife will cause sanity draining nightmares unless it is soaked in human blood each day. The knife can be positively IDed as belonging to a Colorado man responsible for 5 deaths (by dismemberment) in 1982.</item>
        <item>A magic wand in the style of the Harry Potter series. If broken or cross sectioned it will lose its powers. It will also reveal that it has some Mythos creatures part inside of it. Rather then the part of some fictional magical creature. If it can be used by a PC it would help in spell casting. However, it offers no San protection. Nor would it shield the user from the effects of the spell. Doesn\'t have to be useful because after all: the wand chooses the wizard. No member of the party may qualify.</item>
        <item>A ziploc bag containing a single 12 gauge shotgun shell and a post-it note saying "Emergency Use Only! Danger!". Anyone opening the shell will find several thin layers of strangely shaped metal foil separated by glyph-covered papers filling the top of the shell. The metal foils are a mixture of silver, gold, palladium and lead.Separating the foils make the shell useless. [Firing the shell will create a 12\' cone of collapsing non-linear space ahead of the gun, dealing 10d6 of damage to anything in the cone (also ignoring armour). Unfortunately a similar, though weaker, cone will extend 6\' in the opposite direction, dealing 5d6 to anyone behind the gun, including the shooter.]</item>
        <item>An unadorned iron mace, wrapped in bloodstained newspaper from three years ago. This weapon can be used to hit creatures immune to regular weapons, but will remain bloody for a number of days equal to the points of damage it inflicts thereafter. There is no evident source to the blood, which simply beads on the weapon if observed long enough. Examining the interior with X-rays, or physically splitting it reveals nothing unusual.</item>
        <item>a large claymore blade rests solemnly on a shattered jade and stone pillar, the blade is black and scarlet like smoke on the morning sea, red etchings on it read ex oblivion. the blade deals 4d4+db if a creature is killed by this blade it is transported to a extra planer space where nothing exists except you. sanity lose by seeing this happen is 7/4d4.</item>
        <item>A sealed blue envelope made of a heavy plastic and containing an oily substance. If opened, neither the plastic nor the oil resemble anything the investigator is familiar with. If the sealed envelope is exposed to a temperature of zero degrees centigrade or less for twenty four hours any creature whose exposed skin touches it will freeze solid in a matter of seconds; this effect lasts for twenty four hours, after which the envelope returns to room temperature and becomes inert. It may be reused indefinitely by refreezing it.</item>
        <item>A small obsidian dagger, roughly 10 cm long and 3 cm wide. The haft, roughly 5 cm long, is wrapped with red leather; the blade is etched with several strange symbols. (Said symbols state the weapon is sacred to Nyarlathotep; realizing this costs 1d4/1d10 SAN).\nStabbing someone with the dagger inflicts no actual damage; the blade penetrates but no blood is shed. The victim suffers excruciating pain and must make a POW roll to do anything except writhe and scream in agony. Once the dagger is removed the pain instantly stops; both attacker and victim lose 1d4/1d8 the first time this happens, with 1/1d4 for each subsequent occurrence..</item>
        <item>A revolver of indeterminate make. Its design incorporates elements from several models, which may lead anyone who knows anything about firearms to guess this is a custom-made weapon. The frame of the revolver has a dark, gunmetal gray color, with a dull finish. The most unique part of its look, is the grip and cylinders, which are a lighter color, and almost look like some kind of ivory, or bone. Strange swirly glyphs and symbols are etched into both. Normally such material would break when used, but anyone who grasps the grip of the pistol instinctively feels like it\'ll fire.\nIf opened up, it is found to be chambered in .357 magnum and have six shells present. If dumped out, a random number of shells are spent. If the gun is emptied but not reloaded, next time a player looks at the gun, they will discover a random number of chambers loaded with live rounds. 0/1 SAN for this event.\nWhen fired in combat, the weapon will always be loaded with a random number of bullets, though the wielder may need to fire a couple times to find a live round. These rounds appear in the gun at random times and in random amounts, and will do so even if shells are still left in the gun. When drawn by its owner in need, however, a live round is always ready. 1/1d6 SAN once someone realizes this.</item>
        <item>A beautifully balanced medieval broadsword, with a double-edged blade of pattern-welded steel and a hilt of leather-wrapped brass with small gemstones set into the pommel. When this weapon is within seven yards of a Mythos creature immune to mundane weapons, even if the creature is on the opposite side of a wall or otherwise invisible the gemstones in the hilt may be seen to glow dimly. Also, if the wielder of the sword wins a quick contest of POW vs. his Mythos opponent, this sword will inflict half damage to Mythos creatures normally immune to mundane weapons--at the price of draining one point of POW from the wielder for every hit point inflicted in this manner (and failing the quick contest means the sword is ineffectual against such creatures, though the gems will still glow in their presence). Striking the killing blow vs. Mythos creatures will return d6 times the hit points inflicted by the last blow to the wielder as POW, however. Realizing what\'s happening is 1/1d4 SAN loss for observers, 1d4/2d6 for the user.</item>
        <item>A 19th-century rapier that shimmers oddly in the light. It is completely incapable of cutting through living things, and passes through inanimate objects without interacting with them, but it can deal damage to incorporeal entities.</item>
        <item>A crude dagger made from a black, obsidian-like material with one end wrapped in yellow cloth to make the handle. Symbols appear on the blade when fresh blood touches it. Those who see the symbols will be imparted with unearthly knowledge and a manic need to see more.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a 4\' long piece of black iron chain. The 1 1/2" long links are quite crude and obviously hammered into shape by hand. A closer examination will show tiny star-like shapes etched into the links. [Whipping someone with the chain will deal 1d6+STR bonus damage. Wrapping the chain around the fist and lower arm will enable the wielder to punch for 2d6+STR bonus damage, as well as doubling his chance of parrying close combat attacks with that arm. BUT in this last case there is a great risk involved. If the chain wrapped around the arm is used to kill someone it will absorb the MP of the victim and use it to meld with the arm of the wielder, making it impossible to remove without serious surgery. Each midnight thereafter it will feed on the wielder, absorbing 1d4 CON. CON lost in this way is not returned as long as the chain is still melded to the wielder. At zero CON the wielder dies as a shriveled mummy-like corpse and the chain drops off.]</item>
        <item>A samurai sword wrapped in duct-tape so as to be sealed into its scabbard. Anyone managing to draw it suddenly believes themselves to be a 17th century samurai, and randomly attacks anyone nearby while yelling in accurate Tokugawa-era Japanese. This continues until either the sword is removed from their sight or they are killed. Curiously, the weapon is a rather poor quality demonstration piece made in Nagoya in 1994.</item>
        <item>A large automatic pistol which somewhat resembles the Mauser C96, but cannot be recognized as any specific model or design. There are no manufacturer\'s markings anywhere on the weapon; certain elements of its design, like the box magazine and stripper clip feeding, suggest the early 20th century, but it also features materials like space-age polymers and titanium alloys in its construction.\nThe first investigator who picks it up feels a voice in his or her head, whispering "I\'ll never leave you...never betray you...always protect you..." over and over again. After about thirty seconds, this fades, and the weapon\'s properties begin to manifest:\nSo long as the investigator is alive, anyone besides him or her that attempts to fire it will always find it misfires or malfunctions. This never occurs for the owner. In addition, if the weapon is ever confiscated, it will reappear in a hiding place easily accessible to the owner within a few hours, which causes a 1/1d4 SAN loss if it were to do so in a way that would be impossible through normal means. Should the owner die, however, the weapon returns to its original state, swearing loyalty to the first person who picks it up.\nThe weapon appears to be chambered for the .30 Carbine round, but the rounds that come with it are literally filled to the brim with powder. No matter how hot-loaded the ammunition fired from it is, it will never rupture or malfunction, implying an incredibly strong construction.</item>
        <item>A green thermos, duct taped shut, wrapped in plastic, and marked with a BioHazard label. If opened, it is found to be full of a foul-smelling grey liquid containing a proto-mater slurry. Anyone coming into contact with the liquid will die a very painfully death from an unknown hemorrhagic disease in 1d4+1 days. Someone has written "do not touch!" in marker on the thermos itself.</item>
        <item>A BB gun loaded with 5 pellets. When fired, the pellet will pierce any armor, from Kevlar vests to tank armor, but will only do 1d4 damage against living flesh. Trying to remove the pellets or reload the gun cause the weapon to become inoperable.</item>
        <item>A vintage fireman\'s axe from the 1900s. Carefully etched in the surface of one of the faces is an active elder sign. While it keeps entities from seizing or moving the axe, it does no extra damage, nor does it have any properties as a supernatural source of damage.</item>
        <item>A black sheathed katana with Crimson runes etched on its blade, sits on a alter willing all who see it to wield it for good or evil. Once the blade is drawn it must taste blood or force its weirder to kill or commit suicided. The blade dealers 2d10+4+db, this blade is also sentiment and can communicate with its welder according to the rulings of the keeper.</item>
        <item>Two dozen unmarked silver aerosol cans filled with argotypoline, which can be used as an accelerant. A notecard is left next to them indicating the contents. It adds, "If you need something to burn very, very hot and very, very fast, then this is just the juice." There\'s also a few unlisted, arcane ingredients in the mix, which add a 20% chance per can applied of summoning fire vampires which will completely consume whatever is coated.</item>
        <item>A 3 foot staff of silvery metal with a softball sized sphere at one end. While it can be used as an effective club, it also emits a droning sound in the presence of Deep Ones that affects their nervous system to make them dull and slow-witted (halves all their normal skills) when within 30 feet of the staff. Unfortunately it needs to be re-charged after 10+d10 rounds use by bathing the sphere in at least 1 liter of human blood or it will cease working.</item>
        <item>A traditional Nepalese knife or Khukri, in its holster. Once unsheathed, it enters its "active state" where any holder gets a 20% boost to DEX and a 60% higher change of doing CRITICAL damage. The weapon can only be returned to its holster after it has drawn blood. If the holder attempts to sheath the weapon without using it in combat, he has to make a POW roll. If it fails, the holder\'s hand moves as of its own accord and inflicts a small cut on the opposite forearm for 1 HP worth of damage, before automatically returning the knife to its sheath. Lose 1/1d6 SAN once the holder realises what\'s happening.</item>
        <item>A plastic evidence bag containing a heptagonal crystal, 1\' long and 2" in diameter. One end is blunt, the other one pointed. The crystal is semi-opaque with a violet tint and feels slightly warm to the touch. Along the sides of it strange three-dimensional signs fades in and out of existence. [By spending 1MP the crystal\'s wielder can activate it for 5 rounds. During this time anything touched by the crystal\'s tip will separate to a depth of 1\', creating a rift that widens 2" each round until it is 24" wide, and then closes by 2" each round until the rift no longer exist. Disappearing material is "folded" into another dimension and reappears unharmed. Living creatures subjected to this are also physically unharmed, though the shock of existing in several dimensions more than usual makes the victim lose 1D10 SAN and become unconscious for 1d6 rounds after returning to his or her normal state. Witnessing these effects cost 0/1 SAN if done on unliving materials, and 1/1d6 if done on a living creature. Not so much a weapon as a Mi-Go hyper-dimensional tool.]</item>
        <item>A US diplomatic bag containing a small (5" tall) crystalline pyramid shot through with metallic filaments. There is also a ziploc bag with a blood-stained notebook in it. The notebook contains a sketch of the Pyramid and a rambling description of its history from 4000BC to present day. It also describes how to activate the Pyramid through a complex series of gestures and MP expenditure. [Activating the Pyramid costs 8MP and 1d6 SAN. The Pyramid will then become insubstantial and sink straight down 33\'. Three rounds later it will pulverize all inorganic material in a flattened sphere 60\' wide and 30\' high around it. This usually leads to a massive collapse of the overlying area, leaving the end result looking somewhat like a large sinkhole.]</item>
        <item>A masterfully-forged bronze sword, appearing to be of pre-Alexandrian Greek design. An inscription runs the length of the blade in ancient Greek, reading along the lines of "Death to all the enemies of the one who bears me."\nIf it is picked up and carried, the inscription will gradually alter itself over a period of days or weeks, becoming more and more specific and personal to those currently seen as \'enemies\' by the wielder. As an example, one day it might be directed at bankers and taxmen, with whom the wielder has been having issues; the week after it might concern the specific IRS agent who authorized the recent tax fraud investigation concerning the wielder. Even if the wielder itself does not know this information, the sword seems to find out.\nNaturally, as the inscription changes, so does the attitude of the wielder. What might have started out as a general vindictiveness towards the IRS refines itself into a psychotic vendetta against that specific agent, and if not stopped, the wielder will eventually seek out and slaughter that specific \'enemy\'.</item>
        <item>A long wooden chest containing an ancient, but extremely well-preserved, egyptian Khopesh. The 24" sword is made from bronze and has a full metal grip. Along the hooked blade egyptian hieroglyphs and imagery show warriors surrounding and attacking a tree-like monster (a Dark Young of Shub-Niggurath for those who succeed with a Mythos roll, or has met one before). There are iridiscent stains along the blade and on the grip. [The sword does 2d6 damage, plus any STR bonus, even to Mythos-creatures who normally take only minimal damage from physical weapons. The drawback is that anyone touching the sword with their bare skin for more than a few moments will be infected with an incurable wasting sickness, losing 1 CON each week, as their metabolism shuts down, until they die at zero CON.]</item>
        <item>A foam-lined attache-case containing a weather-beaten, unloaded WA-2000 rifle, chambered in .300 Winchester Magnum. Its wooden stock is engraved with the word "SERAFIN" in simple script. Mounted is a telescopic sight constructed of unpolished dark metal. Casual examination of the sight-picture would suggest that the scope is inoperative, showing nothing but pitch-blackness and lacking a reticule of any kind. When aimed at a living creature, a magnified silhouette of the target appears consisting of bluish-green wisps of fire, despite whatever obstructions should block line of site. When fired, the target is struck in a lethal location with the mundane ammunition, regardless of range, with the trajectory appearing to alter of its own accord to strike however many victims are inside the sight-picture, through whatever cover they are sheltered behind..\nDisassembling the scope or separating it from the rifle render it completely inoperable and irreparable. The rifle, however, is fully functional so long as it is maintained adequately, even with the scope removed. The means by which the scope and rifle operate together is a mystery, but one can determine under close scrutiny and after trial-and-error that the range of this device has no discernible limitations, besides a permanent 18x zoom, nonadjustable due to a distinct lack of dials on the device.</item>
        <item>A single 7.62 FMJ bullet. If touched, the next time it is out of sight the bullet vanishes - apparently permanently. However, if the person who touched it is ever killed by a firearm, the autopsy will find the killing shot was inflicted by that very same 7.62 slug...</item>
        <item>An elegantly crafted Elephant Gun, with gold and silver engravings along the barrels in strange, almost hypnotic patterns. The stock of the weapon has some kind of inscription, also in gold, in no known language.\nShells fired from this gun do no physical damage to the target, but rather call for an Opposed POW roll between the wielder and target. The one who fails the opposed roll looses 1d6 Magic Points. If a target is rendered unconscious by the gun, the wielder regains 2d6 magic points.</item>
        <item>A medieval broadsword of the type used by the crusaders during the first crusade. The hilt is wrapped in coarse leather. The blade is engraved with the text DEUS VULT. The sword is magical and will deal damage to non-corporal beings, e.g. ghosts.</item>
        <item>The passenger door of a white pickup truck, evidently very old due to its hand-crank window and overall appearance. Roughly scratched into the outside with a key or nail, over and over again, is everyone\'s favorite catchphrase "CTHULHU FHTAGN".</item>
        <item>A twisted punch-dagger made of some unidentifiable coral. It\'s ergonomically weird, seemingly made for inhuman hands, and deals an extra 1d6 in damage with each successful punch. It deals 2d6 if the user has Deep One blood...</item>
        <item>This is a speargun engraved with glowing blue runes. It is damp at all times and comes with three similarly engraved spears. When a spear strikes a target, it does 1d6 damage before summoning a white whale to swallow target whole.</item>
        <item>A six foot long trident made of a strange gray metal; the haft is engraved with strange writing and scenes of what appear to be lizard men fighting Deep Ones. It is razor sharp and functions normally, except when used against Deep Ones, whom it strikes unerringly. The weilder loses 1/1d3 SAN if he recognizes the figures on the haft and an additional 1/1d4 if he realizes the weapon is intended for use against the Deep Ones.</item>
        <item>A short baskethilted broadsword with a cloudy crystal blade and organic seeming guard. When swung it produces the sound, just audible, of a basso profundo singing without words.</item>
        <item>A somewhat rusty, but still sharp sickle (18th century manufacture) with a well-worn grip. Careful examination will detect small flecks of dried blood. (It has had the spell \'Bless Blade\' cast upon it.)</item>
        <item>An American Civil War-era Model 1860 Light Cavalry saber. Still sharp but with strange yellowish stains along the blade. Anyone cut by it or who touches one of the stains with an open wound will contract a mysterious disease that slowly rots away the victims skin. This has no cure and the victim will permanently lose 1d3 APP and 1d3-1 HP (due to additional infections) each week.</item>
        <item>A mi-go lightning gun. It looks a bit like a large fleshy walnut trailing three green vines, but if picked up, the vines wrap up the holder\'\'s arm and telepathically recognise when he wants to fire. The first time this is done, SAN loss 1/1d3. For subsequent uses it\'s 0/1d3. When seen in the Green Box it\'s being held in a slightly transparent toolkit normally used to hold drill bits. A stapled bundle of papers nearby (apparently written by a doctor or botanist from the terminology used) explains the general principle behind the weapon\'\'s use, but seriously recommends leaving it alone due to an unspecified "physiological reaction" in test subjects.</item>
        <item>A Colt M1917 .45 ACP revolver in very poor condition: the muzzle is caked with what appears to be dried blood and gray matter, the original blueing has given way to a patina of rust, the front blade sight has been sheared off, and the words "DI DI MAU" carved roughly into the wooden grips. The cylinder catch refuses to budge, meaning the gun cannot be unloaded nor reloaded.\nAnyone who holds this pistol feels a slight compulsion to put it to their head. If they lose focus while the gun is in their hand, they will eventually realize that their hand has raised and the muzzle is now pressed against their temple. This is accompanied by the faint, far-off sounds of men screaming in a shrill Asian language that only the wielder can hear.\nEven though the cylinder is stuck in the frame, it can still spin. If inspected, it is revealed that there is still a cartridge in one of the chambers. If the trigger is pulled, there is a one-in-six chance the gun will fire -- regardless of if the bullet in the cylinder has already been fired or not. Once fired, the bullet will always strike the nearest person to its point-of-aim in the head; without fail, and regardless of the firer\'s skill or aim.</item>
        <item>A 17th century Turkish dagger, well-maintained and wrapped in a plain leather sheath. So long as the weapon\'s edge is covered in warm human blood once a week, it will remain surgically sharp and shine brightly; no other efforts will condition or sharpen the blade.</item>
        <item>An unremarkable .32 semi-automatic pistol. The last person to have held it, however, will haunt it as a ghost when they die. The current ghost (a young suicidally-depressed woman named Sandra Blewsky) has haunted the gun for some 24 years and will use her ghostly powers either to get the next person who touches it to kill themselves or otherwise die, possibly by distracting them during a gunfight. If Sandra manages it, she will be able to pass on to wherever ghosts go. The recently deceased agent will then serve as Sandra\'s replacement.</item>
        <item>A peculiar rosewood staff, carved with what appears to be ivy. While not a particularly impressive mundane weapon, it nevertheless inflicts regular damage on any supernatural creature - including ghosts and Mythos beats.</item>
        <item>A Yithian lightning gun - made from landfill electronics junk.</item>
        <item>A padlocked metal box used to store radioactive material. It contains an organic flesh-like orb glistening with oily colors. This is a Deep One shoggoth controller. If removed from the lead-lined box it begins to attract any shoggoth within twenty miles to the bearer, and they\'ll probably be upset when they get there...</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>